<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Mike Oldfield - Ommadawn [AC-3 5.1 448 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/mike-oldfield-ommadawn-ac-3-5-1-448-kb-s.236823/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/9c/ea/UHZf9XR3_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/9c/ea/UHZf9XR3_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Rock, Folk, World, &amp; Country</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Folk Rock, Prog Rock, Art Rock, Modern Classical, Celtic, Folk, African</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1975 (this release: 2010)</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">DVD, AC-3 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
<i><b>Ommadawn</b></i> is the third studio album by English musician, multi-instrumentalist and songwriter Mike Oldfield, released on 3 November 1975 on Virgin Records.<br>
<br>
By the end of 1974, Oldfield had been propelled to worldwide fame due to the unexpected critical and commercial success of his debut studio album, <i>Tubular Bells</i> (1973). He followed it with <i>Hergest Ridge</i> (1974), which generated a more negative critical reaction in comparison, which disappointed him but led to a creative period as he vowed to deliver a follow-up that was "worthwhile and successful", proving he was not a one-hit wonder with the success of <i>Tubular Bells</i>. When Oldfield started to work on new music for <i>Ommadawn</i>, he wanted to avoid professional studios and persuaded his label, Virgin Records, to install a 24-track studio at The Beacon, his home in Kington, Herefordshire. Oldfield recorded <i>Ommadawn</i> at The Beacon between January and September 1975; the African drums were recorded at The Manor in Shipton-on-Cherwell, Oxfordshire, where Oldfield had recorded <i>Tubular Bells</i> and <i>Hergest Ridge</i>. The Manor was chosen as there was insufficient space at The Beacon to accommodate the instruments and equipment. Oldfield is credited as the album's sole producer and engineer.<br>
<br>
Shortly after Oldfield started to record, his mother died. He later recalled that working on his new music provided the only source of comfort for him at the time. He faced further problems several months in when he had almost finished recording side one, when the recording tape started to shed its oxide layer, causing irreparable damage. Virgin delivered a machine so that copies of the master tape could be made and Oldfield could carry on working, but the same problem occurred on the new tape. This left Oldfield no choice but to start again using a new brand of tape. He believed that the many overdubs he had put down on the track had worn it out. Oldfield felt depressed to start over at first, but he then noticed that "something clicked inside of me" and realised that his previous takes had become good practice for the final ones. "All the musical pieces fell into place and the results sounded marvellous." The original version of side one was released on the 2010 remaster as "Ommadawn (Lost Version)". Excerpts from the scrapped version were previously used in Oldfield's interview on Tony Palmer's documentary series <i>All You Need is Love</i> and the 1977 film <i>Reflection</i>.<br>
<br>
The cover photograph was taken by David Bailey. The album's title came about at the end of its production. Oldfield spotted a collection of words that Irish musician Clodagh Simonds had made up, one of them being <i>ommadawn</i>, and decided to use it. Oldfield in 1975 rejected a claim that the title comes from the Irish Gaelic word <i>amadán</i> or <i>omadhaun</i>, meaning "fool". Later, however, he said it did mean "idiot."<br>
<br>
<b>Release Info</b><br>
This release is muxed from the Deluxe Edition DVD, released in June 2010.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Ommadawn (Part One) <span style="color: #0059b3">19:04</span><br>
02. Ommadawn (Part Two) + On Horseback <span style="color: #0059b3">17:21</span><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>