<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ CAP] - AXS - Metal Massacre: The Story Behind the Legendary Album (broadcasted 2023-10-28)]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/axs-metal-massacre-the-story-behind-the-legendary-album-broadcasted-2023-10-28.237376/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
I don't know of any scene release, but I'm pretty sure someone must have ripped it and put it online somewhere.<br>
<br>
I'm eternally grateful to whoever makes it available here, or points me in the correct direction to obtain it elsewhere.<br>
<br>
"This year’s lineup is headlined by the premiere of <b><i>Metal Massacre: The Story Behind the Legendary Album</i></b>, making its network debut on October 28 at 9pE. Packed with all-star interviews, rare photos, the film tells the story of the groundbreaking 1982 <b><i>Metal Massacre</i></b> vinyl compilation-a sonic celebration of the burgeoning Los Angeles Metal scene, which helped launch the careers of iconic acts <b>Metallica</b> and <b>Ratt</b>, and ultimately led to the birth of the legendary independent record label <b>Metal Blade Records</b>. The film boasts priceless commentary and anecdotes from <b>Metal Blade</b> founder <b>Brian Slagel</b> and his friend and collaborator John Kornarens, two metalheads with a dream who made <b><i>Metal Massacre</i></b> a reality; as well as <b>Metallica</b> members <b>Lars Ulrich</b> and <b>James Hetfield</b>; <b>Ratt</b> frontman <b>Stephen Pearcy</b>; and <b>Black N’ Blue</b> singer <b>Jamie St. James</b>, among many others."
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Winged]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>