<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - Sophie Ellis-Bextor - Bittersweet (Freemasons Mixes)]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/sophie-ellis-bextor-bittersweet-freemasons-mixes.238071/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Hi. Does anyone have the MP3's for all the Freemasons mixes of Sophie Ellis-Bextor's single Bittersweet that they'd be able to upload here, please? I remember when the song first came out all these remixes were available to buy as MP3 downloads and I'm sure I had them but can't find them anymore. Probably on my old computer and I forgot to transfer them over. They no longer seem to be available anywhere. When I check on Amazon and Itunes for MP3 purchases the only version of Bittersweet available is the original album version, which I'm not keen on at all. I think the Freemasons versions totally lifted the song to a different level and as well as a 3.30 mins (approximately) radio edit remix there's also one of around 4.30 or 5 mins version and a long club mix version nearly 9 minutes long, all by Freemasons. I don't care for the Jodie Harsh mixes of the song, only the Freemasons. I know I could just download them from YouTube but the sound quality isn't very good, I'd love to have the proper original MP3's that were originally released. I don't understand why these great mixes aren't even on any streaming sites to listen to!<br>
<br>
Hope someone can help or direct me to where I can buy the MP3's if there is a site I don't know about! Thanks in advance.
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Pant-hooting Chimp]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>