<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Introductions &amp; Farewells】Hi all! Hello! Hallo!]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/hi-all-hello-hallo.241741/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Hi all,<br>
<br>
Nice to meet you! My name is Evert! <b>Evert</b> is a Dutch and Swedish short form of the Germanic masculine name "Everhard" (alternative Eberhard). It is also used as surname. I'm a huge music collector. I own more then 400+ physical albums and a lot of digital music. Currently I am busy to catalogue (?) my music. I use a program for it. In that program you can add several information such as release date, music company, record studio etc. But also composers, writers and so on.<br>
Very addictive program. And you can play your music directly from out of that program in, for example, Apple Music.<br>
<br>
Back in the days (the 80's, 90's etc.) when there was no internet, we had Music Stores where I every Saturday went to listen to new albums and I pre-ordered import CD's and Maxi CD Singles. That was my excuse to go to that music store on the next Saturday <img src="styles/default/xenforo/smilies/exciting-48.png" class="mceSmilie" alt=":D" title="Big Grin    :D"> LOL!<br>
That expanded my collection with, sometimes, five of the same cd singles but it slightly was different cause there was an extra remix or number on it. <br>
<br>
Here is a print screen of my collections program for you to share <img src="styles/default/xenforo/smilies/big_smile-48.png" class="mceSmilie" alt=":)" title="Smile    :)"><br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/gJ5KqhP.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/gJ5KqhP.png" style=""> <br>
<br>
I recently started again with this program and I know have catalogued 572 albums, singles etc.<br>
I have a lot more to do!<br>
Oh, and that program is called collectorz.<br>
You find it here: <a href="https://collectorz.com/" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://collectorz.com/</a><br>
Perhaps you already know it but it is a Dutch program and very populair because you also can download the same program for movies, comics and books.<br>
<br>
If you are looking for specific music let me know I have a lot if iTunes (Apple Music) Albums ready to share.<br>
And, if I made some grammar or spelling mistakes, let me know. I am not a native English speaker <img src="styles/default/xenforo/smilies/exciting-48.png" class="mceSmilie" alt=":D" title="Big Grin    :D"><br>
<br>
Happy collecting!<br>
<br>
Best wishes Evert
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[EvertNL]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>