<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ VID] - Taylor Swift NOW 1080p]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/taylor-swift-now-1080p.237490/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Hi, does anyone happen to have all 13 episodes of Taylor Swift NOW, the streaming service launched by Taylor Swift in partnership with the American mobile telecommunications company AT&amp;T and DirecTV? The episodes would be as follows:<br>
<br>
0. Introduction: Taylor Swift welcomes viewers to her new channel and talks about the videos they'll be able to watch, at home or on the go, with the new Taylor Swift NOW exclusively on AT&amp;T.<br>
<br>
1. That One Time I Surprised My Fans: Two fans are on a mission to get a hug from Taylor. When she finds out, she challenges them with an online video, classic Taylor! Will they do what it takes to get a hug from Taylor Swift? Tune in and find out!<br>
<br>
2. That One Time On A Video Shoot (Part 1): Taylor talks about her music videos and shares stories you haven't heard before. Plus, see what it was like to film these videos, including behind-the-scenes footage of some of her biggest hits.<br>
<br>
3. That One Time I Was Nostalgic: Every now and then Taylor dedicates a song to her family. Through personal lyrics and home videos, she shares her love and gratitude for those who have been there from the beginning.<br>
<br>
4. That One Time I Had A Photoshoot: See how Taylor prepares for the release of Speak Now with photo shoots for the album and various magazine covers. Also, don't forget to watch the behind-the-scenes video with Peter Max, one of Taylor's artistic heroes.<br>
<br>
5. That One Time I Unplugged: Exclusive acoustic performance of Taylor singing "How You Get the Girl" at the GRAMMY Museum in Los Angeles.<br>
<br>
6. That One Time I Went On Tour (Part 1): Watch as an 18-year-old Taylor embarks on her first worldwide tour with the Fearless Tour. Then, get ready for rehearsals for her second worldwide tour, Speak Now, plus behind-the-scenes footage of Taylor and her band around the world.<br>
<br>
7. That One Time On A Video Shoot (Part 2): Taylor talks about her music videos and shares stories you haven't heard before. Plus, see what it was like to film these videos, including behind-the-scenes footage of some of her biggest hits.<br>
<br>
8. That One Time I Totally Got Into Character: Telling stories through characters and costumes is one of Taylor's favorite things.<br>
<br>
9. That One Time When We Were OVER: Taylor shares some untold stories from her first music video, "Tim McGraw."<br>
<br>
10. That One Time I Went On Tour (Part 2): Watch special highlights from Taylor's third sold-out tour, the RED Tour, and hear an untold story from her shows in Nashville. Then, see behind-the-scenes videos from her biggest tour to date, The 1989 World Tour.<br>
<br>
11. That One Time On A Video Shoot (Part 3): Taylor talks about her music videos and shares stories you haven't heard before. Plus, see what it was like to film these videos, including behind-the-scenes footage of some of her biggest hits.<br>
<br>
12. That One Time I Talked About My Music: Taylor shares the intimacy of her creative process, including her songwriting, collaborating with producers, what it's like in the studio, and creating an album's packaging.<br>
<br>
13. That One Time I Did A Special Event: Taylor Swift performances are definitely special events! Tune in and discover what Taylor has in store for her fans."
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[speaknowhp]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>