<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Rihanna - Good Girl Gone Bad: Reloaded [QOBUZ CD 16-bit/44.1kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/rihanna-good-girl-gone-bad-reloaded-qobuz-cd-16-bit-44-1khz.242813/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 22px"><b>Rihanna - Good Girl Gone Bad: Reloaded [QOBUZ CD 16-bit/44.1kHz]</b></span><br>
<br>
<img src="https://imgur.com/D510zgo.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://imgur.com/D510zgo.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ALBUM REVIEW</b></span><br>
When you've released a pair of albums containing a few monster singles and a considerable amount of unsteady, unassured material, why mess around the third time out? From beginning to end, Good Girl Gone Bad is as pop as pop gets in 2007, each one of its 12 songs a potential hit in some territory. Unlike Music of the Sun or A Girl Like Me, neither Caribbean flavorings nor ballad ODs are part of the script, and there isn't an attempt to make something as theatrical as "Unfaithful." There is, however, another '80s hit involved: just as "SOS" appropriated Soft Cell's version of "Tainted Love," "Shut Up and Drive" turns New Order's "Blue Monday" into a sleek, forthcoming proposition, one that is as undeniable and rocking as Sugababes' 2002 U.K. smash "Freak Like Me" (a cover of Adina Howard's 1995 hit that swiped from another '80s single, Gary Numan's "Are Friends Electric?"). "Shut Up and Drive" is part of an all-upbeat opening sequence that carries through five songs. Rihanna knows exactly what she wants and is in total control at all times, even when she's throwing things and proclaiming "I'm a fight a man" amid marching percussion and synthesizers set on "scare" during "Breakin' Dishes." The album's lead song and lead single, "Umbrella," is her best to date, delivering mammoth if spacious drums, a towering backdrop during the chorus, and vocals that are somehow totally convincing without sounding all that impassioned -- an ideal spot between trying too hard and boredom, like she might've been on her 20th take, which only adds to the song's charm. The album's second half is relatively varied and a little heavier on acoustic guitar use, but it's not lacking additional standouts. Three consecutive Timbaland productions, including one suited for a black college marching band and another that effectively pulls the romantically codependent heartstrings, enhance the album rather than make it more scattered.<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ABOUT THE ALBUM</b></span><br>
<ul>
<li>1 disc(s) - 15 track(s)</li>
<li>Total length: 00:56:55</li>
</ul><ul>
<li>Main artists: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/interpreter/rihanna/36240" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Rihanna</a></li>
<li>Composer: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/composer/various-composers/573076" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Various Composers</a></li>
<li>Label: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/label/def-jam-recordings/download-streaming-albums/1304" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Def Jam Recordings</a></li>
<li>Genre: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/genre/pop-rock/download-streaming-albums" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Pop/Rock</a></li>
</ul>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div><b>Password: musicasylum</b>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Mu$iC @$YLUM]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Green Day - 21st Century Breakdown [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/green-day-21st-century-breakdown-qobuz-hi-res-audio-24-bit-96-0khz.242812/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 22px"><b>Green Day - 21st Century Breakdown [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]</b></span><br>
<br>
<img src="https://imgur.com/Vjwfev6.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://imgur.com/Vjwfev6.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ALBUM REVIEW</b><br>
</span><br>
American Idiot was a rarity of the 21st century: a bona fide four-quadrant hit, earning critical and commercial respect, roping in new fans young and old alike. It was so big it turned Green Day into something it had never been before -- respected, serious rockers, something they were never considered during their first flight of success with Dookie. Back then, they were clearly (and proudly) slacker rebels with a natural gift for a pop hook, but American Idiot was a big album with big ideas, a political rock opera in an era devoid of both protest rock and wild ambition, so its success was a surprise. It also ratcheted up high expectations for its successor, and Green Day consciously plays toward those expectations on 2009's 21st Century Breakdown, another political rock opera that isn't an explicit sequel but could easily be mistaken for one, especially as its narrative follows a young couple through the wilderness of modern urban America. Heady stuff, but like the best rock operas, the concept doesn't get in the way of the music, which is a bit of an accomplishment because 21st Century Breakdown leaves behind the punchy '60s Who fascination for Queen and '70s Who, giving this more than its share of pomp and circumstance. Then again, puffed-up protest is kind of the point of 21st Century Breakdown: it's meant to be taken seriously, so it's not entirely surprising that Green Day fall into many of the same pompous tarpits as their heroes, ratcheting up the stately pianos, vocal harmonies, repeated musical motifs, doubled and tripled guitars, and synthesized effects that substitute for strings, then adding some orchestras for good measure. It would all sound cluttered, even turgid, if it weren't for Green Day's unerring knack for writing muscular pop and natural inclination to run clean and lean, letting only one song run over five minutes and never letting the arrangements overshadow the song. Although Green Day's other natural gift, that for impish irreverent humor, is missed -- they left it all behind on their 2008 garage rock side project Foxboro Hot Tubs -- the band manages to have 21st Century Breakdown work on a grand scale without losing either their punk or pop roots, which makes the album not only a sequel to American Idiot, but its equal.<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ABOUT THE ALBUM</b></span><br>
<ul>
<li>1 disc(s) - 18 track(s)</li>
<li>Total length: 01:09:09</li>
</ul><ul>
<li>Main artists: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/interpreter/green-day/53549" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Green Day</a></li>
<li>Composer: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/composer/green-day/53549" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Green Day</a></li>
<li>Label: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/label/reprise/download-streaming-albums/7398" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Reprise</a></li>
<li>Genre: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/genre/pop-rock/download-streaming-albums" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Pop/Rock</a></li>
</ul>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div><b>Password: musicasylum</b>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Mu$iC @$YLUM]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>