<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Nirvana - MTV Unplugged In New York [AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/nirvana-mtv-unplugged-in-new-york-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz.225713/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/5b/b0/2UJdfue6_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/5b/b0/2UJdfue6_o.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<b>Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Rock</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Folk Rock, Acoustic, Grunge</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1994 (DVD release: 2007)</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">DVD (Remux)</span><br>
Format: <span style="color: #0059b3">AC3 16-bit 48 kHz 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>MTV Unplugged in New York</b>" is a live album by American rock band Nirvana, released on November 1, 1994, by DGC Records. It features an acoustic performance recorded at Sony Music Studios in New York City on November 18, 1993, for the television series <i>MTV Unplugged</i>.<br>
The show was directed by Beth McCarthy and aired on the cable television network MTV on December 16, 1993. In a break with <i>MTV Unplugged</i> tradition, Nirvana played mainly lesser-known material and covers of songs by the Vaselines, David Bowie, Lead Belly and Meat Puppets. Unlike prior <i>MTV Unplugged</i> performances, which were entirely acoustic, Nirvana used electric amplification and guitar effects during the set. They were joined by rhythm guitarist Pat Smear and cellist Lori Goldston, alongside Meat Puppets members Cris and Curt Kirkwood for some songs.<br>
<br>
<i>MTV Unplugged</i> was released after plans to release the performance as part of a live double-album compilation titled <i>Verse Chorus Verse</i> were abandoned. It was the first Nirvana release after the death of singer Kurt Cobain seven months prior. It debuted at number one on the US <i>Billboard</i> 200 and was certified 8x platinum by the RIAA in 2020. It won the Best Alternative Music Performance at the 1996 Grammy Awards, making it Nirvana's only Grammy Award win, and has since been ranked one of the greatest live albums of all time. The performance was released as a DVD in 2007.<br>
<br>
Nirvana rehearsed for two days, at SST Rehearsal Facility, in Weehawken, New Jersey. The rehearsals were tense and difficult, with the band running into problems performing various songs. During the sessions, Cobain disagreed with MTV about the performance. Producer Alex Coletti recalled that the network was unhappy with the lack of hit Nirvana songs, and with the choice of the Meat Puppets as guests, saying: <i>"They wanted to hear the 'right' names – Eddie Vedder or Tori Amos or God knows who."</i><br>
The day before filming, Cobain refused to play, but he appeared at the studio the following afternoon. Cobain was suffering from drug withdrawal and nervousness at the time; one observer said, <i>"There was no joking, no smiles, no fun coming from him ... everyone was more than a little worried about his performance."</i><br>
<br>
Reviewing the <i>MTV Unplugged in New York</i> DVD release in 2007, the <i>Los Angeles Times</i> wrote that it "deserves a place on the rock TV history shelf alongside the informal, sit-down section of Elvis Presley's epic comeback special in 1968". In June 2020, the 1959 Martin D-18E guitar used by Cobain at the <i>Unplugged</i> concert was sold at Julien's Auctions for US$6 million to Peter Freedman of Røde Microphones, making it the most expensive guitar ever sold at auction.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. About A Girl (03:16)<br>
02. Come As You Are (03:54)<br>
03. Jesus Doesn't Want Me For A Sunbeam (04:45)<br>
04. Dumb (02:52)<br>
05. The Man Who Sold The World (03:57)<br>
06. Pennyroyal Tea (04:12)<br>
07. Polly (03:05)<br>
08. On A Plain (3:31)<br>
09. Plateau (04:08)<br>
10. Lake Of Fire (02:52)<br>
11. All Apologies (03:46)<br>
12. Where Did You Sleep Last Night? (05:15)<br>
<br>
<b>Release Info</b><br>
This is a remux of the "Original MTV Version" section on the DVD (less noise, more music).<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - Gabriela Rocha - EP]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/gabriela-rocha-ep.225714/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<a href="https://tidal.com/browse/track/66417814" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://tidal.com/browse/track/66417814</a><br>
<br>
<img src="styles/default/xenforo/smilies/red_heart-48.png" class="mceSmilie" alt=":love:" title="hearts    :love:">
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Piperpilar]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>