<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>sharemania</title>
 <link>http://www.sharemania.us/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Singles (lossy)】MP3 - A$AP Rocky Trunks Mp3 Download]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/a-ap-rocky-trunks-mp3-download.281889/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					A$AP Rocky Trunks Song Download<br>
<br>
A$AP Rocky has shared “Trunks” and “Both Eyes Closed,” two new songs that he made for the soundtrack to Highest 2 Lowest, the new Spike Lee movie in which he stars alongside Denzel Washington and others. Listen to the tracks below.<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
Highest 2 Lowest hits U.S. theaters today (August 15). It’s the first feature film from Spike Lee since 2020’s Da 5 Bloods, and it’s the first one to star Denzel Washington since 2006’s Inside Man. A$AP Rocky plays an antagonist in Highest 2 Lowest named Yung Felon.<br>
<br>




<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
	<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
	<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>A$AP Rocky has been teasing the new album Don’t Be Dumb for years, but a firm release date for the Testing follow-up is not currently set. He recently shared the single “Pray4DaGang,” and, last year, dropped “Highjack” and “Ruby Rosary.”<br>
<br>
[Intro]<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back, uh<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back, uh<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Chorus]<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back, uh<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Back)<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back, uh<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Back)<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Post-Chorus]<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (Uh), yeah (Uh), yeah, yeah, uh<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (Uh), yeah (Uh), yeah, yeah, uh (What's up?)<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah (Get him), yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh (Get him back)<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Verse 1]<br>
<br>
At thirty-five and I'm still a purty guy<br>
<br>
honeypot never dry, you know shawty certified<br>
<br>
Pancake-ass niggas stay turnin' sides (Uh-huh)<br>
<br>
Cookie cutter niggas, soda pop, yeah, they Canada Dry, uh (Uh-huh)<br>
<br>
phyuk a fight, nighty-night if we shoot the five<br>
<br>
Who we bop, hit 'em low, nigga, shoot him high<br>
<br>
Suit and tie, they crossed the boy so many times, feel crucified (Yeah)<br>
<br>
Bumpin' Koopsta Knicca in my coupe, my doors still suicide<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Refrain]<br>
<br>
Shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony (Uh)<br>
<br>
Shoutout-shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
Shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony (Ooh, uh)<br>
<br>
Young felon nigga uptown, phyuk who tellin' me (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Chorus]<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
All gold fronts from the front to the back (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Ooh, uh-huh)<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Post-Chorus]<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (Uh), yeah (Uh), yeah, yeah, uh<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah (Uh), yeah (Uh), yeah, yeah, uh (What's up?)<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah (Get him), yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh (Get him back)<br>
<br>
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, uh<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Verse 2]<br>
<br>
BBL, think they built<br>
<br>
They strainin' when they trainin' in the gym<br>
<br>
They think they Wilt Chamberlain<br>
<br>
Can't name a bitch who honeypot I ain't killed (For real)<br>
<br>
You lame as shit, we ain't forget<br>
<br>
The muscles, they ain't real, yeah, yeah, uh<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Refrain]<br>
<br>
Shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony<br>
<br>
Shoutout-shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony<br>
<br>
Shoutout-shoutouts to my felons, boy, we caught another felony (Shoutout the felons, uh)<br>
<br>
Young felon nigga uptown, phyuk who tellin' me (Ooh, ooh)<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Verse 3]<br>
<br>
Of course, I ride around the bros<br>
<br>
Of course, I'm sellin' out my shows<br>
<br>
Of course, I slime and wipe my nose<br>
<br>
Of course, your honor, I can't go to court<br>
<br>
My baby mom want child support<br>
<br>
phyuk college, can't enroll no course<br>
<br>
She celebrate and pop the cork, of course<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Bridge]<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Uh, uh)<br>
<br>
Nigga got a grudge, motherphyuker, where ya at? (Uh, uh, give it to 'em)<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back (Where they at? Put it up)<br>
<br>
Nigga try to front, we gon' leave 'em where he at (Brrt, back)<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
[Outro]<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back<br>
<br>
(I got niggas in they cell, goin' crazy in the jail, well)<br>
<br>
Pack out the trunk from the front to the back<br>
<br>
(Tell the judge, "Don't be holdin' grudge, suck-suck my nuts")<br>
<br>
(I'd rather be a thug) I'd rather be a thug<br>
<br>
(I'd rather be a thug) I'd rather be a thug<br>
<br>
(Send bullets than a hug) I don't give no phyuk<br>
<br>
(Yeah, hate and no love) Pack out the trunk from the front to the back<br>
<br>
(Niggas in they cell, goin' crazy in the jail, well)<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to the real ones, the ones who never tellin')<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to my fellas, shoutouts to my fellas)<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to the real ones, the ones who never tellin')<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to my fellas, shoutouts to my fellas)<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to the real ones, the ones who never tellin')<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to my fellas, shoutouts to my fellas)<br>
<br>
(Shoutouts to the fellas, the ones who never tellin')
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[mimiagen]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【HD Live Performances】WEB-RiP - CAMILA CABELLO SUMMER SONIC 2025 TOKYO DAY 2]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/camila-cabello-summer-sonic-2025-tokyo-day-2.281890/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					<img src="https://iili.io/FmmdMYB.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://iili.io/FmmdMYB.png" style=""> <br>
<br>




<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
	<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
	<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Cruel Summer]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Movies &amp; TV Shows】Alien earth season 1 download]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/alien-earth-season-1-download.281888/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					Alien: Earth is the latest sci-fi series crafted by Noah Hawley, serving as an ambitious prequel to the original Alien film franchise.<br>
<br>
Premiering Tuesday, August 12, it centers on Wendy (Sydney Chandler), the first human-alien hybrid, who leads a high-stakes investigation into the crash site of a mysterious spaceship.<br>
<br>
Alien earth season 1 episodes <br>
<br>
AVAILABLE HERE<br>
<br>




<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
	<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
	<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>Joining Chandler are notable actors—Timothy Olyphant, Alex Lawther, Samuel Blenkin, Essie Davis, and a talented ensemble cast—taking the Alien mythology into bold new territory
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[mimiagen]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - Justin Bieber - SWAG (Clean Album) flac]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/justin-bieber-swag-clean-album-flac.281887/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					Qobuz I believe has this clean in flac, as their other versions have the parental guidance logo.<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/album/swag-justin-bieber/n1i04durvkavb" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/album/swag-justin-bieber/n1i04durvkavb</a><br>
<br>
Thanks guys<br>
<br>
Edit: I see someone has posted this here already, however links are dead. If anyone could share any version clean it would be appreciated.
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ThenAndNow52]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>