<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Toto - Toto IV [E-AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz | 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/toto-toto-iv-e-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz-1024-kb-s.227194/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/dc/f1/h86zhFhh_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/dc/f1/h86zhFhh_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Rock</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Pop Rock</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1982</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">SACD DSD 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Toto IV</b>" is the fourth studio album by American rock band Toto, released in the spring of 1982 by Columbia Records.<br>
<br>
The lead single, "Rosanna", peaked at number 2 for five weeks on the <i>Billboard</i> Hot 100 charts, while the album's third single, "Africa", topping the Hot 100 chart, became the group's first and only number 1 hit. Both songs were hits in the UK as well, reaching number 12 and 3, respectively. The fourth single, "I Won't Hold You Back", also peaked within the top ten on the Hot 100, at number 10, but atop the <i>Billboard</i> Adult Contemporary charts for three weeks. It also went into the top 40 in the UK. With the success of "Africa", the album climbed back into the top 10 in early 1983 on both sides of the Atlantic.<br>
<br>
<i>Toto IV</i> received three Grammy Awards in 1983 including Album of the Year, Producer of the Year for the band, and Record of the Year for "Rosanna". It reached number four on the <i>Billboard</i> 200 album charts in the United States, shortly after its release. It also reached the top ten in other countries, including Canada, Australia, New Zealand, the Netherlands, Italy, Norway, the United Kingdom, and Japan. It was also the last Toto album to feature their original bassist David Hungate until his return in 2014 (with the release of their 2015 album <i>Toto XIV</i>) when he was replaced by Mike Porcaro after the band’s recording of the album, and also the final album to feature original lead vocalist Bobby Kimball until his comeback in 1998 (with the release of the 1999 album <i>Mindfields</i>).<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Rosanna 05:31<br>
02. Make Believe 03:43<br>
03. I Won’t Hold You Back 04:53<br>
04. Good For You 03:17<br>
05. It’s A Feeling 03:05<br>
06. Afraid Of Love 03:52<br>
07. Lovers In The Night 04:25<br>
08. We Made It 03:56<br>
09. Waiting For Your Love 04:12<br>
10. Africa 04:55<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>