<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - ZARD - The 10th Compilation Album - «Zard Single Collection: 20th Anniversary» [FLAC 16Bit/44.1kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/zard-the-10th-compilation-album-%C2%ABzard-single-collection-20th-anniversary%C2%BB-flac-16bit-44-1khz.227560/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/NzWnLNY.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/NzWnLNY.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
<span style="font-family: 'Book Antiqua'"><span style="font-size: 15px"><b><b>ZARD</b> </b>was a Japanese pop group under B-Gram RECORDS. Around the release of their third album, HOLD ME, all the band members had left except Izumi Sakai (坂井泉水, born on February 6, 1967). ZARD then became the solo project of Izumi, writing all the music and lyrics herself. According to an episode of Music Station in 2005, ZARD has sold a combined total of 35,450,000 copies, making her the #8 best selling artist in Japan.<br>
<br>
ZARD also performed several songs that have been chosen as Japanese anime themes such as Meitantei Conan, Dragon Ball GT, and Slam Dunk. Since their debut, ZARD released 42 singles and 17 albums in total. Izumi's vocals are considered by many critics a high point of ZARD's music, which revolve around ballads.<br>
<br>
Sakai was diagnosed with cervical cancer in June 2006; the cancer went into remission, but despite this onset, on April of 2007, the cancer was on the move again. On the 26th of May, while being treated for this cancer, Sakai fell three meters from a hospital staircase while returning to her room from a routine walk around the hospital. She was found at 5:40am. She suffered severe trauma to the back of her head (brain contusion), and on 3:10pm she died due to the cerebral contusion. The slippery surface of the staircase due to rain the previous day was blamed for her fall. Some rumors about suicide were being considered, but in the end discarded.<br>
<br>
On June 27th 2007, a memorial funeral was held at Aoyama Cemetery.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/qw3h65T.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/qw3h65T.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
A CD-BOX set containing most of the singles and coupling songs from the 1st single «</span>Good-bye My Loneliness»<span style="font-size: 15px"> to the 45th single «</span>Honestly Ienakute featuring Mai Kuraki».<span style="font-size: 15px"><br>
«</span>It hurts so much you are overflowing»<span style="font-size: 15px">, «</span>Kono Namida Hoshi ni Nare»<span style="font-size: 15px">, «</span>Get U're Dream» secret track<span style="font-size: 15px"> version, «</span>Heart ni Hitote ~Piano Instrumental Version~<span style="font-size: 15px"> », «Yakusoku no 5 songs of "Nai Koi» are not included in this work.<br>
All songs are digitally remastered, LP size special package specification, deluxe 104P booklet, bonus disc with participating songs are included.<br>
Most of the songs included in this work overlap with </span>the CD-Box<span style="font-size: 15px"> «</span>ZARD Premium Box 1991-2008 Complete Single Collection».<span style="font-size: 15px"><br>
Released at the same time as the 20th anniversary photo book «ZARD Portfolio du 20eme anniversaire» (four in total) including unreleased photos.<br>
The single versions of «Good Day» and «</span>Sekai wa Kitto Mirai no Naka»<span style="font-size: 15px"> were not included in the album for a long time, but they are finally included in this work.<br>
In addition, this work is the only one other than the single that contains the 41st single's double A-side song «</span>Karatto Ikou!».<br>
<span style="font-size: 15px">Although it did not rank in the Oricon chart , it was ranked in according to </span>SoundScan Japan's<span style="font-size: 15px"> survey, and ranked 7th in its first appearance for the week.</span></span><br>
<span style="font-family: 'Book Antiqua'"><span style="font-size: 15px"><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div></span></span>​</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[WithLoveSNSD]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>