<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Tiësto - Elements Of Life [BDrip 24-bit 96 kHz 5.1]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/ti%C3%ABsto-elements-of-life-bdrip-24-bit-96-khz-5-1.225438/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/27/70/Wn76EUND_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/27/70/Wn76EUND_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic</span><br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Trance, Progressive Trance</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">2007 (Blu-ray release: 2014)</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Blu-ray, DTS-HD MA 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Elements of Life</b>" is the third studio album by Dutch DJ Tiësto, released on 6 April 2007. The album contains collaborations with Jes of Motorcycle, Julie Thompson of Holden &amp; Thompson, Charlotte Martin, Christian Burns, BT and Maxi Jazz of Faithless. BT collaborates with Tiësto for the first time since "Love Comes Again" and Faithless's rapper Maxi Jazz is featuring on "Dance4Life". The album has more tracks featuring vocals than previous albums (excluding the remixed <i>Just Be</i>).<br>
The album was nominated in the category "Best Electronic/Dance Album" at the 50th Grammy Awards. In April 2007 the album moved 72,000 units according to Nielsen SoundScan. The album also received gold certifications in Belgium, Hungary, Netherlands and Romania.<br>
<br>
During the production of the album Tiësto in several cases sent a demo with the music to certain artists, and they replied back with the lyrics and vocals and other duration times. In the case of Christian Burns from BB Mak, Tiësto met him through MySpace and got in contact with him and the production of the single "In the Dark". The album consists of rock, trance and experimental music, which shows the style Tiësto has grown throughout the years since his previous albums which contained lyrics, <i>In My Memory</i> and <i>Just Be</i>. Producer Brian Transeau collaborated with Tiësto in three tracks, he composed "Bright Morningstar" and "Sweet Things", he also performed the vocals in the single "Break My Fall". Together, they produce more tracks which were not released in the album, and Tiësto has mentioned they would work again during the coming summer.<br>
<br>
<i>"It's a very experimental piece of work and combines the style of rock with trance and electronic, this is the first time that I have combined these different genres. I have always liked rock music so it made sense."</i><br>
— Tiësto<br>
<br>
In December 2014, the album was reissued as a High Fidelity Pure Audio Blu-ray Disc, featuring a brand new 9.1 Auro-3D mix as well as a 5.1 DTS-HD Master Audio track. Both surround mixes are presented at 24-bit/96 kHz resolution.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Ten Seconds Before Sunrise <span style="color: #0059b3">07:31 </span><br>
02. Everything <span style="color: #0059b3">07:01 </span><br>
03. Do You Feel Me <span style="color: #0059b3">06:02 </span><br>
04. Carpe Noctum <span style="color: #0059b3">07:02 </span><br>
05. Driving To Heaven <span style="color: #0059b3">04:42 </span><br>
06. Sweet Things <span style="color: #0059b3">05:44 </span><br>
07. Bright Morningstar <span style="color: #0059b3">08:21 </span><br>
08. Break My Fall <span style="color: #0059b3">07:14 </span><br>
09. In The Dark <span style="color: #0059b3">04:37 </span><br>
10. Dance4Life <span style="color: #0059b3">05:21 </span><br>
11. Elements Of Life <span style="color: #0059b3">08:08 </span><br>
Bonus Track<br>
12. He's A Pirate (Tiësto Remix) <span style="color: #0059b3">07:00 </span><br>
<span style="color: #000000"><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div></span>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>