<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ VID] - Once Upon A Studio (2023) 1080P or 4K]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/once-upon-a-studio-2023-1080p-or-4k.230486/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Is someone able to get that Disney short that aired last night on ABC? They put it up on Disney Plus as well?
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[BbbDdd345]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】MP3 - Geri Halliwell Horner Rosie Frost and the Falcon Queen audiobook]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/geri-halliwell-horner-rosie-frost-and-the-falcon-queen-audiobook.230487/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://i.postimg.cc/T1dLd0F9/AA1hKd7H.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.postimg.cc/T1dLd0F9/AA1hKd7H.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
Review<br>
"This book mixes elements of fantasy with history, mystery, and adventure, but it is, at its core, a coming-of-age story. Rosie blossoms when she starts to let her walls down, and the supporting characters who eventually become her friends round out the story. The school and the island are fantastic settings: readers will be bursting to visit Bloodstone Island, with its rare creatures and old secrets. If an English boarding school on an island full of wild, rare animals isn?t enough to grab readers, Rosie Frost, an empowering new heroine, certainly will." ?School Library Journal<br>
<br>
"This contemporary, girl-power story has light paranormal and fantastical elements and is fueled by a captivating mystery and adventure. It also features quick pacing, fun and engaging worldbuilding, and a lead character who is easy to root for. Exuberant, action-packed, and warmhearted." ?Kirkus Reviews<br>
<br>
"[A]n effervescent fantasy series . . . smart twists rooted in real-life history add excitement, and Anne Boleyn?s indomitable spirit literally and figuratively haunts this lively debut, inspiring Rosie and propelling the tale?s feminist, eco-preservationist message." ?Publishers Weekly<br>
About the Author<br>
Geri Halliwell-Horner is an accomplished singer, writer, producer, and actress who is widely recognized for her iconic place in British pop culture as an original member of the record-breaking girl group the Spice Girls. As Ginger Spice, Geri played a formative role in the band as they became one of the biggest-selling girl groups of all time. She is the successful author of the Ugenia Lavender book series in the UK and continues to work with the Royal Commonwealth to promote prospects through literacy to Commonwealth citizens. She was awarded an honorary doctorate of letters at Sheffield Hallam University and is an outspoken supporter of animals and an ambassador of the London Zoo. You can visit Geri Halliwell-Horner online at RosieFrostBooks.com or follow her on Instagram @TheRealGeriHalliwell and on Twitter @GeriHalliwell and on Facebook at Facebook.com/GeriHalliwell.<br>
<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[o7m0]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>