<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Interviews / TV shows / Others】FEED - Europe's Ariane 6 Rocket Inaugural Flight from French Guiana (1080i) (Feed) (9/7/24) [MAVERICK]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/europes-ariane-6-rocket-inaugural-flight-from-french-guiana-1080i-feed-9-7-24-maverick.249431/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><b>Europe's Ariane 6 Rocket Inaugural Flight from French Guiana (1080i) (Feed) (9/7/24) [MAVERICK]<img src="https://i.postimg.cc/Bvvxkh6d/Europe-s-Ariane-6-Rocket-Inaugural-Flight-from-French-Guiana-9-7-24.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.postimg.cc/Bvvxkh6d/Europe-s-Ariane-6-Rocket-Inaugural-Flight-from-French-Guiana-9-7-24.png" style=""></b>​</div>Launch update, 9 July 16:00 CEST: As part of standard operations in the Ariane 6 preparation after mobile gantry removal, routine checks in the ground segment equipment showed a small issue in a data acquisition system. It has now been resolved. Liftoff is now scheduled no earlier than 16:00 local time (21:00 CEST), with the live stream starting at 15:30 local time (20:30 CEST). This is a big moment for Europe, as the rocket will ensure our guaranteed, autonomous access to space – and all of the science, Earth observation, technology development and commercial possibilities that it entails. With many features brand new to Ariane 6, we’ll be able to carry more and take it further, while sustainably disposing of the launcher's upper stage to prevent it becoming space debris. Phase 1: From ground to orbit The first phase of Ariane 6’s flight will launch the rocket off Earth and into space with the thrust from the main stage powered by the Vulcain engine together with the force from the two powerful P120C boosters. Phase 1 includes the separation of the main stage from the upper stage and the first boost of the upper stage’s Vinci engine, which inserts it and its passengers into an elliptical orbit 300 by 700 km above Earth. The first flight of Ariane 6 will have three phases, each of which will demonstrate various abilities for Europe’s newest heavy-lift rocket. Phase 2: Upper stage reignition and satellite deployment The next phase is when Ariane 6’s newest feature is put to the test: reignition of the upper stage. In phase 2, the Vinci engine will re-fire, changing Ariane 6’s orbit from elliptical to circular. This will be followed by the deployment of the rocket’s eight satellites and the activation of its five onboard experiments. Phase 3 : Tech demos, deorbiting and capsule separation The final phase in Ariane 6’s inaugural flight will be to push the cryogenic upper stage to its limits and validate its ability to perform under microgravity conditions. The final phase will initiate the controlled deorbit of the upper stage back through Earth’s atmosphere over the South Pacific ‘NEMO point’, to prevent it from becoming space debris. Moments later, the two reentry capsules onboard will separate from the upper stage, and all three will make their safe descent back home.<br>
<img src="https://i.postimg.cc/xCfMQnG1/Europe-s-Ariane-6-Rocket-Inaugural-Flight-from-French-Guiana-1080i-Feed-9-7-24-MAVERICK.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.postimg.cc/xCfMQnG1/Europe-s-Ariane-6-Rocket-Inaugural-Flight-from-French-Guiana-1080i-Feed-9-7-24-MAVERICK.jpg" style=""><br>
<div style="text-align: left"><b><b>Airdate: 9/7/24</b></b><br>
​</div>
<div class="ToggleTriggerAnchor bbCodeSpoilerContainer">
<button type="button" class="button bbCodeSpoilerButton ToggleTrigger Tooltip JsOnly" data-target="> .SpoilerTarget"><span>Spoiler: <span class="SpoilerTitle">Media Info:</span></span></button>
<div class="SpoilerTarget bbCodeSpoilerText">
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div></div>
</div><div style="text-align: left">
<div class="ToggleTriggerAnchor bbCodeSpoilerContainer">
<button type="button" class="button bbCodeSpoilerButton ToggleTrigger Tooltip JsOnly" data-target="> .SpoilerTarget"><span>Spoiler: <span class="SpoilerTitle">Download (Gofile):</span></span></button>
<div class="SpoilerTarget bbCodeSpoilerText">
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div></div>
</div></div><div style="text-align: center"><b><b>Please Note: This File is 20.3GB<br>
Please Note: This File Has Been uploaded to Gofile, because its free fast upload and download speeds Grab it while you can, Admin should reupload My files to google drive (so the link "last's longer")</b></b><br>
<br>
<b>Please Credit Me Maverick if you are going to upload my files elsewhere!</b><br>
<br>
<b>New Content will only Be Uploaded from this Account <a href="https://sharemania.us/members/176676/" class="username" data-user="176676, @Maverick">@Maverick</a></b><br>
<br>
<b>Enjoy <img src="styles/default/xenforo/smilies/big_smile-48.png" class="mceSmilie" alt=":)" title="Smile    :)"></b>​</div><div style="text-align: left">​</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Maverick]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>