<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Documentaries】WEB-DL - BTS Monuments: Beyond the Star (1080p)]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/bts-monuments-beyond-the-star-1080p.241424/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://lumiere-a.akamaihd.net/v1/images/p_disneyplusoriginals_bts_poster_rebrand_08fec985.jpeg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://lumiere-a.akamaihd.net/v1/images/p_disneyplusoriginals_bts_poster_rebrand_08fec985.jpeg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Featuring never-before-seen interviews, performances and behind-the-scenes moments with RM, Jin, SUGA, j-hope, Jimin, V and Jung Kook, BTS Monuments: Beyond The Star will take audiences on an in-depth journey across the band’s 10-year career, highlighting their highs and lows for the first time ever in a captivating docuseries format.<br>
<br>
Also featuring appearances from HYBE Chairman Bang Si-Hyuk, and BEYOND THE STORY : 10-YEAR RECORD OF BTS author Kang Myeongseok, BTS Monuments: Beyond The Star looks back on the band’s key moments over the years, showing how the band came to be, what it was like preparing for their debut, what it was like winning best new artist at the 2013 Melon music awards, highlighting their struggles during the “Danger” period, discussing their first concerts, their debut at the American Music Awards and the Billboard Music Awards, what it was like becoming stars in America, speaking at the UN, performing at the Rose Bowl Stadium, the excitement of performing at London’s Wembley Stadium and more.<br>
<br>
The upcoming docuseries also shines a spotlight on highly personal moments from their past, including how they felt about meeting each other for the first time; their initial contract renewal process; the difficulties of isolating during COVID; as well as other more lighthearted moments including j-hope’s surprise birthday party and Jung Kook’s high school graduation ceremony.​</div><br>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center"><b>STARRING<br>
</b><br>
RM, Jin, SUGA, j-hope, Jimin, V, Jung Kook<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div></div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[jemelphilippe]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>