<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Tipper - Surrounded [24-bit 96 kHz 5.1]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/tipper-surrounded-24-bit-96-khz-5-1.225447/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/22/2a/vvOvdN9a_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/22/2a/vvOvdN9a_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Glitch, Downtempo, Ambient, IDM</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">2003</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">DVD-A, MLP 24-bit 96 kHz 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Surrounded</b>" is the fourth studio album by Tipper, released in 2003. David Alexander Tipper (or Tipper for short) is a British composer, producer and DJ, specialized in electronic music that ranges from ambient, through trip hop, to uptempo nu skool breaks. His live performances consist largely of his own unreleased compositions, and he is noted for scratching his own sounds over his music, creating a live element of turntablism stemming from prowess early in his career as a vinyl DJ.<br>
<br>
Tipper is widely respected as a surround sound composer, releasing one of the first albums composed, produced, and intended for the DualDisc format, in addition to providing content for multichannel music industry leaders DTS, Inc. His talents at sound design (his work is included in several of the major music making software programs), and in digital audio mastering, are also in great demand. His catalogue has been consistently licensed for use as background in a variety of mainstream television programmes, and also featured in commercials and cable television projects.<br>
<br>
In 2003, Tipper began composing tracks for what would become his first “Tipper” album intended entirely as a surround sound listening experience. Surrounded began on an Apple iMac with an aftermarket soundcard and a dream. While on a North American tour with several other techno DJs, Tipper assembled this somber, melodic collection of low-intensity electronic music that eventually caught the ears of 5.1 Entertainment’s Richard Dashut. The album was mixed in surround and released by fledgling 5.1 venture MyUtopia Recordings. Eventually nominated as Best Album Intended for Surround Sound this downtempo album also marked a turn in Tipper's musical output away from the nu skool breaks genre which he was more widely associated with.<br>
Late 2004 saw his <i>Surrounded</i> album re-released as a DualDisc title, and this in turn led to the creation of a MP3 Surround Sound Player, by mp3 rights holders Fraunhofer Society. Regarded as one of the foremost composers in the multichannel realm, Tipper continues to provide content for a number of companies who use his highly detailed productions to demonstrate their own advanced technologies.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Middle Of Nowhere <span style="color: #0059b3">(2:24)</span><br>
02. California Rolls <span style="color: #0059b3">(3:14)</span><br>
03. Tear Strips Off <span style="color: #0059b3">(4:13)</span><br>
04. Screw Loose <span style="color: #0059b3">(3:51)</span><br>
05. Over The Coals <span style="color: #0059b3">(4:12)</span><br>
06. Forty Winks <span style="color: #0059b3">(5:15)</span><br>
07. Rotundus Maximus <span style="color: #0059b3">(6:08)</span><br>
08. The Glasshouse <span style="color: #0059b3">(2:53)</span><br>
09. No Dice <span style="color: #0059b3">(4:22)</span><br>
10. Just As The Sun Went Down <span style="color: #0059b3">(3:49)</span><br>
11. Adrift For Days <span style="color: #0059b3">(4:44)</span><br>
Bonus Tracks (M4A)<br>
12. Illabye <span style="color: #0059b3">(4:38)</span><br>
13. Technicolor <span style="color: #0059b3">(7:07)</span><br>
<br>
<b>Release Info</b><br>
The bonus tracks are not on the DVD-Audio part and are Dolby Digital tracks (AC-3 5.1 muxed to M4A).<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>