<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Esteban - Enter the Heart [E-AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/esteban-enter-the-heart-e-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz.225268/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/cf/a1/B74qJso3_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/cf/a1/B74qJso3_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre:<span style="color: #0059b3"> Latin</span><br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Flamenco</span><br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1998</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">DTS-CD</span></b><br>
<br>
Esteban who was born in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania; is the stage name of guitarist Stephen Paul. He is a graduate of the prestigious Carnegie Mellon University, where he majored in classical guitar. Then he studied in Europe with legendary guitar wizard Andres Segovia. Esteban has gained traction and commercial success by demonstrating his instructional DVDs and guitars on QVC and HSN and is most recognizable by his bolero hat, luxurious hair extensions and sunglasses.<br>
<br>
When Esteban performs you can feel the heart. Whatever he plays, the depth of feeling is present - And in "Enter the Heart", every selection is replete with this intensity... this passion.<br>
<br>
Esteban's carreer has its beginnings with the dedications on this album: "Avenida Concha Espiña" is dedicated to Spanish, classical guitar legend Andres Segovia who gave Esteban his endorsement and many cherished memories. Avenida Concha Espiña is the street in Madrid on which Segovia lived and which Esteban walked many times, to Segovia's fourth floor studio during his years with "The Master".<br>
<br>
The first track, "Enter the Heart" is dedicated to the incredible Brazilian guitarist, Laurindo Almeida, who pioneered the Gamba/Bossa Nova jazz movement. Esteban taught with Almeida tolo Laurindo at "Almeida's Guitar World" in Studio City, CA and learned to love the Brazilian Styles.<br>
<br>
"Flamenco Wind" is dedicated to Vicente Gomez, Esteban's first teacher, who sponsored Esteban in his first concert. Gomez, a wonderfully versatile guitarist, performed in many films including, "Blood and Sand","Snows of Kilamanjaro" and more during the 40's and 50's, he also had his own national radio show which brought the Spanish guitar to many thousands who had never heard it before.<br>
<br>
This album is an eclectic mosaic of surpassing beauty and demonstrates Esteban's amazing versatility as an artist - to be felt in the heart... from his heart.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Enter the Heart <span style="color: #0059b3">05:43</span><br>
02. Veracruz Express <span style="color: #0059b3">03:37</span><br>
03. Flamenco Wind <span style="color: #0059b3">08:23</span><br>
04. San Antonio Sunset <span style="color: #0059b3">04:59</span><br>
05. Bag Jam <span style="color: #0059b3">03:43</span><br>
06. Mediterana <span style="color: #0059b3">04:50</span><br>
07. Silver Raine <span style="color: #0059b3">06:33</span><br>
08. Blue Lotus <span style="color: #0059b3">11:12</span><br>
09. Sedona Sunrise <span style="color: #0059b3">04:44</span><br>
10. Avenida Concha Espina <span style="color: #0059b3">05:33</span><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>