<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Remi Wolf-Big Ideas|Qobuz Hi Res 24bit /48kHz]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/remi-wolf-big-ideas-qobuz-hi-res-24bit-48khz.249799/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://i.imgur.com/SAgA0pd.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/SAgA0pd.jpg" style=""><br>
<b><span style="font-size: 22px">Remi Wolf-Big Ideas<br>
</span><br>
Released on 7/12/24 by</b> <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/label/remi-wolf-ps/download-streaming-albums/2066891" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><b>Remi Wolf PS</b></a><br>
<b>Main artists: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/interpreter/remiwolf-10003629317/3629317" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Remi Wolf</a> <br>
Genre:</b> <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/genre/pop/download-streaming-albums" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><b>Pop</b></a><br>
​</div>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div><div style="text-align: center">Cinderella<br>
Soup<br>
Motorcycle<br>
Toro<br>
Alone in Miami<br>
Cherries &amp; Cream<br>
Kangaroo<br>
Pitiful<br>
Wave<br>
When I Thought Of You<br>
Frog Rock<br>
Just the Start<br>
Slay Bitch - Bonus Track<br>
​</div><br>
Remi Wolf's sophomore album, <i>Big Ideas</i>, delivers big on the promise of her first (2021's <i>Juno</i>) and a handful of pretty great EPs—including <i>We Love Dogs!</i>, a remix collection featuring guests like Beck, Hot Chip, Sylvan Esso and Kimbra. While it's possible to identify the Northern California singer-songwriter's (who briefly competed on <i>American Idol</i> as an 18-year-old) influences, Wolf is also a breath of fresh air: living in her own delightfully weird bubble and making music that doesn't sound exactly like anything else right now. R&amp;B-flavored "Cinderella"—joyous with a playground-style chant ("Low tide, moon's so bright/ Moving my hips from left to right/ My, my, check my phone/ Feel it in my belly when you're driving home"), brassy horn blare and whistle blasts—is totally ready for a TV commercial or movie montage. "Cherries and Cream" is a dark, sludgy swirl with a neo-soul center, topped off with a dash of flute. Wolf is an intriguing songwriter, but the songs would only be half as enthralling without her big, charismatic voice. It's wrapped in fuzz for "Kangaroo," which finds her putting on a bratty affect à la classic British New Wave; there's also an explosion of sax skronk for good measure. It's gleeful fun, as is shiny, off-kilter "Frog Rock" and "Toro"—a feel-good-summer track with clicky beats, roller-disco bass and bright flashes of heat whenever Wolf totally cuts loose. Her emotions run high, too, on "Soup" which employs '80s dance floor beats and synth (shades of Robyn here) as she wails, "I don't want to live without you." Wolf, who is open about her bisexuality, ADHD and alcohol struggles, sings songs about sex (the Snail Mail-esque "When I Thought of You"), her bike (old-school R&amp;B love ballad "Motorcycle") and making out at Chicago's legendary venue Empty Bottle ("Cherries and Cream"). "Alone in Miami," meanwhile, is evocative with references to crypto bros, cocaine, sushi and "playing DJ in the Escalade." Pulled by a dark undertow and Wolf going emo throat-shredder, it's an Instagram-versus-reality portrait of being young but unable to shake ennui. And the 28-year-old sounds so much younger on the unvarnished, Moldy Peaches-esque acoustic folk number "Just the Start"—then gets turned into a cartoon chipmunk for the disco goof "Slay Bitch," which sounds like the song equivalent of the tongue-out-wink emoji. © Shelly Ridenour/Qobuz
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Jackrousey]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>