<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Hans Zimmer - Inception (Music From The Motion Picture) [EAC3 5.1 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/hans-zimmer-inception-music-from-the-motion-picture-eac3-5-1-1024-kb-s.238320/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/fc/f5/11zvmWgh_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/fc/f5/11zvmWgh_o.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<b>Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic, Classical, Stage &amp; Screen</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Score, Contemporary</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">2010</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Inception Two-Disc Blu-ray, thanks Chris.Brown</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Inception: Music from the Motion Picture</b>" is the soundtrack to the 2010 film of the same name directed by Christopher Nolan, released under Reprise Records on July 13, 2010. Hans Zimmer scored the film, marking his third collaboration with Nolan following <i>Batman Begins</i> and <i>The Dark Knight</i>.<br>
<br>
The movie uses music almost throughout the entire film. There is not one scene where background music is not utilized to enhance the atmosphere or tone of the story. Hans Zimmer’s original scores in Inception are consistently adding to the feel of the film.<br>
<br>
According to Zimmer, the soundtrack for <i>Inception</i> is "a very electronic score". Nolan asked Zimmer to compose and finish the score as he was shooting the film. The composer said, "He wanted to unleash my imagination in the best possible way". At one point, while composing the score, Zimmer incorporated a guitar sound reminiscent of Ennio Morricone and was interested in having Johnny Marr, former guitarist in the influential 80s rock band The Smiths, play these parts. Zimmer's reported inspiration was finding a synthesizer track that he had written similar to Marr's guitar style. Nolan agreed with Zimmer's suggestion, and then Zimmer approached Marr, who accepted his offer. Marr spent four 12-hour days working on the score, playing notes written by Zimmer with a 12-string guitar.<br>
<br>
For inspiration, Zimmer read <i>Gödel, Escher, Bach: An Eternal Golden Braid</i> by Douglas Hofstadter because it combined "the idea of playfulness in mathematics and playfulness in music". Zimmer did not assemble a temp score but "every now and then they would call and say 'we need a little something here.' But that was OK because much of the music pieces aren't that scene-specific. They fall into little categories". While writing the screenplay, Nolan wrote in Édith Piaf's "Non, je ne regrette rien" but almost took it out when he cast Marion Cotillard, who had just completed an Oscar-winning turn as Piaf in the 2007 film <i>La Vie en rose</i>. Zimmer convinced Nolan to keep it in the film and also integrated elements of the song into his score; in particular, the film's iconic brass instrument fanfare resembles a slowed-down version of the song's instrumentation.<br>
<br>
A 10 track lossless surround mix of the score was released on the second disc of a 2-disc Blu-ray release of Inception. The soundtrack was nominated for several awards, including an Academy Award, a Golden Globe, a Grammy and a BAFTA.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. "We Built Our Own World" <span style="color: #0059b3">01:55</span><br>
02. "Dream Is Collapsing" <span style="color: #0059b3">02:28 </span><br>
03. "Radical Notion" <span style="color: #0059b3">03:43 </span><br>
04. "Old Souls" <span style="color: #0059b3">07:44 </span><br>
05. "528491" <span style="color: #0059b3">02:23 </span><br>
06. "Mombasa" <span style="color: #0059b3">04:54 </span><br>
07. "One Simple Idea" <span style="color: #0059b3">02:28 </span><br>
08. "Dream Within a Dream" <span style="color: #0059b3">05:04 </span><br>
09. "Paradox" <span style="color: #0059b3">03:25</span><br>
10. "Time" <span style="color: #0059b3">04:35 </span><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>