<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Instrumentals / Karaoke (lossy)】MP3 - Request - Laura Pausini - Nuevo Official Instrumental]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/request-laura-pausini-nuevo-official-instrumental.232883/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Does anyone here have official instrumental for Nuevo by Laura Pausini from this limited single? <a href="https://www.discogs.com/release/14861990-Laura-Pausini-Nuevo" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Laura Pausini – Nuevo (2019, CD) - Discogs</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[hnata1240]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers - Catch A Fire (Remastered 50th Anniversary ) (2023) [HIGHRESAUDIO HRA 24bits/96.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/bob-marley-the-wailers-catch-a-fire-remastered-50th-anniversary-2023-highresaudio-hra-24bits-96-0khz.232882/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b><img src="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2023/11/03/ncx8xc-catchafire-preview-m3.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2023/11/03/ncx8xc-catchafire-preview-m3.jpg" style=""> </b><br>
<b><img src="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" style=""> </b><br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<b>Album info</b></span><br>
<b>Album-Release:</b><br>
2023<br>
<br>
<b>HRA-Release:</b><br>
03.11.2023<br>
<br>
<b>Label:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/label/view/5723888e-235f-4ab0-a4ec-f22657d4b574/UMC+%28Universal+Music+Catalogue%29" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">UMC (Universal Music Catalogue)</a><br>
<br>
<b>Genre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/World%20Music" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">World Music</a><br>
<br>
<b>Subgenre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/World%20Music/Worldbeat" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Worldbeat</a><br>
<br>
<b>Artist:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/artist/view/8063dbc5-9c69-4012-8ead-ca665be85c1c/Bob+Marley+%26+The+Wailers" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Bob Marley &amp; The Wailers</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;source=web&amp;rct=j&amp;opi=89978449&amp;url=https://www.highresaudio.com/album/view/ncx8xc/bob-marley-the-wailers-catch-a-fire-remastered-50th-anniversary&amp;ved=2ahUKEwiI4vHC4uKCAxXSpZUCHfg-ADQQFnoECBEQAQ&amp;usg=AOvVaw2FVJKvdF0fH5jMYzy4paOX" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">"Catch A Fire (Remastered 50th Anniversary )"</a><br>
<br>
Tracklist:<br>
01 Concrete Jungle<br>
02 Slave Driver<br>
03 400 Years<br>
04 Stop That Train<br>
05 Baby We've Got A Date (Rock It Baby)<br>
06 Stir It Up<br>
07 Kinky Reggae<br>
08 No More Trouble<br>
09 Midnight Ravers<br>
10 Slave Driver (Jamaican Extended Version / 2023)<br>
11 400 Years (Jamaican Extended Version / 2023)<br>
12 High Tide Or Low Tide (Jamaican Alternate Version / 2023)<br>
13 Stir It Up (Jamaican Alternate Version / Take 1 / 2023)<br>
14 No More Trouble (Jamaican Extended Instrumental / 2023)<br>
15 Stir It Up (Jamaican Extra Organ Version) 48kHz<br>
16 No More Trouble (Jamaican Extended Version / 2023) 48kHz<br>
17 Stop That Train (Working Mono Version) 48kHz<br>
18 Slave Driver (Live At The Sundown Theatre, Edmonton, UK / May 1973) 48kHz<br>
19 Get Up, Stand Up (Live At The Sundown Theatre, Edmonton, UK / May 1973) 48kHz<br>
20 Stop That Train (Live At The Sundown Theatre, Edmonton, UK / May 1973) 48kHz<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b>Info for <i>Catch A Fire (Remastered 50th Anniversary )</i></b></span><br>
<br>
<br>
Catch a Fire is the fifth studio album by the reggae band The Wailers (aka Bob Marley and the Wailers), released in April 1973. It was their first album released by Island Records.[4] After finishing a UK tour with Johnny Nash, they had started laying down tracks for JAD Records when a disputed CBS contract with Danny Sims created tensions. The band did not have enough money to return to Jamaica, so their road manager Brent Clarke approached producer Chris Blackwell, who agreed to advance The Wailers money for an album. They instead used this money to pay their fares back home, where they completed the recordings that constitute Catch a Fire. The album has nine songs, two of which were written and composed by Peter Tosh; the remaining seven were by Bob Marley. While Bunny Wailer is not credited as a writer, the group's writing style was a collective process. For the immediate follow-up album, Burnin', also released in 1973, he contributed four songs. After Marley returned with the tapes to London, Blackwell reworked the tracks at Island Studios, with contributions by Muscle Shoals session musician Wayne Perkins, who played guitar on three overdubbed tracks. The album had a limited original release under the name The Wailers in a sleeve depicting a Zippo lighter, designed by graphic artists Rod Dyer and Bob Weiner; subsequent releases had an alternative cover designed by John Bonis, featuring an Esther Anderson portrait of Marley smoking a "spliff", and crediting the band as Bob Marley and the Wailers.<br>
<br>
The Catch a Fire Tour, which covered England and the United States, helped generate international interest in the band. Catch a Fire peaked at number 171 on the Billboard 200 and number 51 on the Billboard Black Albums charts. Critical acclaim has included the album being listed at number 126 on Rolling Stone's 500 Greatest Albums of All Time, second only to Legend among five Bob Marley albums on the list. It is regarded as one of the top reggae albums of all time.<br>
<br>
The group title Bob Marley and the Wailers being used on Bob Marley solo albums has created a lot of marketing and identity confusion for The Wailers' catalog. This follows the confusion generated by their company Tuff Gong Records (registered in 1973) and the similarly-named Tuff Gong International (registered by the Bob Marley Estate in 1991); this resulted in the 1999 Tuff Gong Settlement Agreement, which sought to separate the group's catalog from Bob Marley's solo catalog. The dual releases of Catch a Fire under both group names is where this marketing confusion began.<br>
<br>
Critical acclaim has included the album being listed at number 126 on Rolling Stone’s 500 Greatest Albums of All Time, It is regarded as one of the top reggae albums of all time.<br>
<br>
"Catch a Fire was the major label debut for Bob Marley and the Wailers, and it was an international success upon its release in 1973. Although Bob Marley may have been the main voice, every member of the Wailers made valuable contributions and they were never more united in their vision and sound. All the songs were originals, and the instrumentation was minimalistic in order to bring out the passionate, often politically charged lyrics. Much of the appeal of the album lies in its sincerity and sense of purpose -- these are streetwise yet disarmingly idealistic young men who look around themselves and believe they might help change the world through music. Marley sings about the current state of urban poverty ("Concrete Jungle") and connects the present to past injustices ("Slave Driver"), but he is a not a one-trick pony. He is a versatile songwriter who also excels at singing love songs such as his classic "Stir It Up." Peter Tosh sings the lead vocal on two of his own compositions -- his powerful presence and immense talent hint that he would eventually leave for his own successful solo career. More than anything else, however, this marks the emergence of Bob Marley and the international debut of reggae music. Marley would continue to achieve great critical and commercial success during the 1970s, but Catch a Fire is one of the finest reggae albums ever. This album is essential for any music collection." (Vik Iyengar, AMG)<br>
<br>
<b>Bob Marley, </b>guitar, vocals<br>
<b>Peter Tosh, </b>organ, guitar, piano, vocals<br>
<b>Bunny Wailer, </b>bongos, conga, vocals<br>
<b>Aston "Family Man" Barrett, </b>bass<br>
<b>Carlton "Carlie" Barrett, </b>drums<br>
<b>Rita Marley, </b>backing vocals<br>
<b>Marcia Griffiths, </b>backing vocals<br>
<b>Additional musicians:<br>
John "Rabbit" Bundrick, </b>keyboards, synthesizer, clavinet<br>
<b>Wayne Perkins, </b>guitar ("Concrete Jungle", "Baby We've Got a Date (Rock It Baby)", "Stir it Up")<br>
<b>Robbie Shakespeare, </b>bass ("Concrete Jungle")<br>
<b>Tommy McCook, </b>flute<br>
<b>Jean Alain Roussel, </b>piano, keyboards<br>
<b>Winston Wright, </b>organ<br>
<b>Francisco Willie Pep, </b>percussion<br>
<b>Chris Karan, </b>percussion<br>
<br>
Digitally remastered<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<i><b>LINK:</b></i><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[SkyBlur]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - John Vincent III - Songs For The Canyon (2023) [HIGHRESAUDIO HRA 24bits/48.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/john-vincent-iii-songs-for-the-canyon-2023-highresaudio-hra-24bits-48-0khz.232884/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2023/11/17/mt7pv6-songsforth-preview-m3.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2023/11/17/mt7pv6-songsforth-preview-m3.jpg" style=""> <br>
<img src="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" style=""> <br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b>Album info</b></span><br>
<b>Album-Release:</b><br>
2023<br>
<br>
<b>HRA-Release:</b><br>
17.11.2023<br>
<br>
<b>Label:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/label/view/49f0c1c1-4169-4bff-bd70-275326c88a81/Concord+Records" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Concord Records</a><br>
<br>
<b>Genre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/Songwriter" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Songwriter</a><br>
<br>
<b>Subgenre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/Songwriter/Folk-Rock" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Folk-Rock</a><br>
<br>
<b>Artist:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/artist/view/aa7eed90-f8d6-49ac-a51f-ca92278e0e3c/John+Vincent+III" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">John Vincent III</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;source=web&amp;rct=j&amp;opi=89978449&amp;url=https://www.highresaudio.com/en/album/view/mt7pv6/john-vincent-iii-songs-for-the-canyon&amp;ved=2ahUKEwj5nbrX5OKCAxX4qpUCHTR7CJMQFnoECAgQAQ&amp;usg=AOvVaw3S1419NX2hehYkovm4jK11" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">"Songs For The Canyon"<br>
</a><br>
Tracklist:<br>
01 Highway Woman<br>
02 Lincoln, NB<br>
03 Dandelion<br>
04 Bluebird Singing<br>
05 When She Leaves<br>
06 Juniper And Yellow<br>
07 I Lit A Fire<br>
08 That’s Just The Way It Is, Babe<br>
09 More Than Alive<br>
10 On And On<br>
11 Rolling Stone<br>
12 Money And My Pride<br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b>Info for <i>Songs For The Canyon</i></b></span><br>
<br>
<br>
Following his acclaimed, self-released 2019 album Songs From The Valley, John Vincent III returns with Songs For The Canyon. Co-produced by John Vincent with Tom Elmhirst (Adele, David Bowie, Beck), Tony Berg and Ryan Hadlock, Songs For The Canyon is a massive leap forward from a traditional artist who has already built a diehard fanbase on the strength of his classic, stripped-down, indie-folk tinged sound.<br>
<br>
Currently boasting over 1.8M monthly streams, John Vincent III earned immediate attention and critical applause with a series of self-released singles and EPs, followed by his breakthrough 2019 debut album, Songs From The Valley. The Houston, TX-raised, Los Angeles, CA-based singer-songwriter celebrated the LP’s success with nearly non-stop touring, returning home just as the pandemic struck the world over. Rather than sit still, Vincent and his partner, photographer/filmmaker Kaitlyn Renee, packed up their Ford Transit van and hit the road, spending eight months together (along with a new puppy) exploring America in their home-on-wheels. Though Vincent tried his best to tune out the world around him, he found himself writing songs for the sheer joy of writing songs, not thinking about structure or intricate chords, but simply relating the extraordinary experience he was living.<br>
<br>
Vincent returned to Los Angeles and pushed his songcraft even further, tightening and adapting and refining until his songs revealed their true identities. The resulting Songs For The Canyon proves a massive leap forward for Vincent, his evocative lyricism and wistful melodic gifts now even more detailed and emotionally rich than ever before. Recorded with top producers in studios on both coasts (including New York City’s famed Electric Lady Studios), songs such as “Bluebird Singing,” the incandescently orchestrated “Dandelion,” and the foot-stomping, solo acoustic “That’s Just The Way It Is, Babe” see the talented troubadour driving his heartfelt, stripped-down sound towards new sonic vistas inspired by the classic folk-rock of Laurel Canyon. Marked by its open-armed storytelling and timeless musical approach, Songs For The Canyon serves as an undeniable milestone for John Vincent III, standing tall as both a warts-and-all chronicle of his recent adventures and confident signpost towards future musical journeys.<br>
<br>
“This album feels like waking up at 2 am to someone knocking on the van window and telling us we can’t be parked there to sleep, and our dog chewing up our clothes,” John Vincent III says. “There were times I felt like I was on top of the world, and others when I was crying about how the album just wasn’t coming together.<br>
<br>
“To the people who have supported my career, even during my time away, I want them to know that this album was therapeutic. It was just me trying to figure out what the hell I was going through. Maybe I still don’t even have the answers, but I tried my best to create something that was as honest as possible and hopefully worth the wait.”<br>
<br>
<b>John Vincent III</b><br>
<b><br>
<br>
<br>
<i>LINK:</i></b><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[SkyBlur]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>