<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Twenty One Pilots - Clancy (2024) [HIGHRESAUDIO HRA 24bits/44.1kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/twenty-one-pilots-clancy-2024-highresaudio-hra-24bits-44-1khz.245937/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b><img src="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2024/05/23/ncqt4s-clancy-preview-m3.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://storage.highresaudio.com/2024/05/23/ncqt4s-clancy-preview-m3.jpg" style=""> </b><br>
<img src="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://www.highresaudio.com/img/logo/logo-hra-lp.png" style=""> <br>
<br>
<br>
<b>Album info</b></span><br>
<b>Album-Release:</b><br>
2024<br>
<br>
<b>HRA-Release:</b><br>
24.05.2024<br>
<br>
<b>Label:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/label/view/10658694-ac9b-41f2-8a09-623a09c2fcf9/Fueled+By+Ramen" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Fueled By Ramen</a><br>
<br>
<b>Genre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/Rock" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Rock</a><br>
<br>
<b>Subgenre:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/genre/Rock/Adult%20Alternative" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Adult Alternative</a><br>
<br>
<b>Artist:</b> <a href="https://www.highresaudio.com/en/artist/view/e963ca97-9e22-446c-a9c1-c1ecac08cfda/Twenty+One+Pilots" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Twenty One Pilots</a><br>
<br>
<b>Album including</b> Album cover<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&amp;source=web&amp;rct=j&amp;opi=89978449&amp;url=https://www.highresaudio.com/album/view/ncqt4s/twenty-one-pilots-clancy&amp;ved=2ahUKEwitj_uw07mGAxXTFLkGHXgTDg8QFnoECBEQAQ&amp;usg=AOvVaw0gDp-8AqMyKSXReCdAchsR" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">"Clancy". Album of Twenty One Pilots buy or stream.</a><br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b>:<br>
01 Overcompensate<br>
02 Next Semester<br>
03 Backslide<br>
04 Midwest Indigo<br>
05 Routines In The Night<br>
06 Vignette<br>
07 The Craving (Jenna's version)<br>
08 Lavish<br>
09 Navigating<br>
10 Snap Back<br>
11 Oldies Station<br>
12 At The Risk Of Feeling Dumb<br>
13 Paladin Strait<br>
<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b>Info for <i>Clancy</i></b></span><br>
<br>
<br>
Twenty One Pilots new album, Clancy, which will be released May 17th. The alternative pop-rock duo, made up of vocalist Tyler Joseph and drummer Josh Dun, have long been candid about anxiety and depression, themes often represented in Joseph’s lyrics as he sings, raps and occasionally screams while Dun drums at an incredible pace.<br>
<br>
Those topics have existed since the beginning of their career, but reached new creative heights on 2015’s “Blurryface,” when the duo introduced a new concept album series that would carry them to 2018’s “Trench,” 2021’s “Scaled and Icy,” to its ambitious conclusion: 2024’s “Clancy.”<br>
<br>
For those of you who haven’t been following the narrative with each release, here’s a summary: In the cement-walled city of Dema on the lush continent of Trench, Nico, an embodiment of insecurity also known as Blurryface, controls the confined citizens with a group of mystical leaders called the Nine Bishops. Joseph is a citizen who gets out, is tracked down, escapes again, joins a rebellion, is recaptured and escapes again.<br>
<br>
Having amassed over 33 billion streams worldwide and over 3 million tickets sold across global headline tours, the Columbus, OH based duo of Tyler Joseph and Josh Dun have established themselves as one of the most successful bands of the 21st century and redefined the sound of a generation. Co-produced by Joseph and Paul Meany, Clancy marks the final chapter in an ambitious multi-album narrative first introduced in the band's 2015 multi-Platinum breakthrough, Blurryface. Furthermore, Clancy’s forthcoming release on May 17th coincides with the 9th anniversary of Blurryface, which was released exactly nine years prior to the day.<br>
<br>
Twenty One Pilots extended the ambitious concept laid out in Blurryface with their 2018 Platinum-certified album TRENCH. Featuring the multi-Platinum and Platinum singles “Chlorine,” “My Blood” and the GRAMMY® Award-nominated “Jumpsuit,” the album graced spots on “Best of” year-end lists by Billboard, KERRANG!, Alternative Press, and Rock Sound—who placed it at #1.<br>
<br>
The duo’s 2021 epic Scaled And Icy debuted at No. 1 on Billboard's Top “Rock Albums” and “Alternative Albums” charts while landing at No. 3 on the “Billboard 200,” marking the biggest opening week for a rock album in 2021. The record is highlighted by the #1 Alternative Radio hits “The Outside,” “Saturday,” and “Shy Away,” the latter of which ascended to #1 at the format in just three weeks, placing the duo in an elite group of acts with multiple songs to rise to #1 at the format in three weeks or less including: U2, R.E.M., The Cure, Linkin Park, Red Hot Chili Peppers, and Foo Fighters.<br>
<br>
Twenty One Pilots, have shifted music and culture as an incomparable creative force and with an ever-evolving vision. The Columbus, OH duo—Tyler Joseph and Josh Dun— have tallied over 33 billion global streams and counting, sold north of three million tickets worldwide, notched dozens of multi-Platinum certifications, and even claimed a spot in the Guinness® Book of World Records. In historic fashion, their quadruple-Platinum breakout LP, Blurryface, took flight as “the first album to notch a RIAA Gold or Platinum certification for every one of its songs,” while Vessel followed suit and achieved the same distinction. They elevated to rarified air as “one of only 18 artists to earn multiple RIAA Diamond certifications,” going Diamond with “Stressed Out” and “Heathens.” 2018’s Platinum-certified Trench extended the ambitious concept laid out in Blurryface and delivered the multi-Platinum and Platinum singles: “Chlorine,” “My Blood” and the GRAMMY® Award-nominated “Jumpsuit.” They followed Trench with their Gold-certified LP Scaled And Icy, achieving “the biggest opening week for a rock album in 2021” by capturing #1 on the Billboard Top Rock Albums and Top Alternative Albums charts and crashing the Top 3 of the Billboard 200. Beyond rapturous headline shows at arenas and festivals worldwide, Twenty One Pilots have notably architected an immersive world without comparison, originating a multi-album conceptual arc across Blurryface, Trench, and Scaled And Icy. Exactly nine years to the date of the Blurryface album release, they complete this story on their seventh full-length offering, Clancy [Fueled By Ramen], out May 17, 2024. Led by the single “Overcompensate,” the LP signals the dawn of another era for Twenty One Pilots and alternative rock music at large.<br>
<br>
<b>Twenty One Pilots</b><br>
<br>
<br>
<div style="padding-left: 30px">Total Runtime 47:14<br>
<br>
​</div>LINK:<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[SkyBlur]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>