<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Red Velvet - Chill Kill - The 3rd Album (Tidal Max 24bits)]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/red-velvet-chill-kill-the-3rd-album-tidal-max-24bits.232148/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/59/fd/AYv7LKvh_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/59/fd/AYv7LKvh_o.jpg" style=""><br>
Chill Kill is the third full-length album by Red Velvet. It will be released on November 13, 2023 with "Chill Kill" serving as the album's title track.<br>
<br>
The physical album comes in 19 versions: 2 Bag versions, 2 Photobook versions, 5 Packages versions, 5 Poster versions, and 5 SMini versions.<br>
Knock Knock (Who’s There?)" is described as a dance song, combination of strings, bells and bass “like clockwork”, starts with a knocking sound, shows essence of “velvet music”.[5]<br>
<br>
"Underwater" is described as a slow-tempo R&amp;B genre song. It features a heavy, groovy, and a dreamy synth sound. The vocal harmony of Red Velvet complete the fantastic atmosphere of the track. The lyrics compare the infinite love to distant and deep water. [6]<br>
<br>
"Will I Ever See You Again?" is described as a overwhelming synth drop with moderated vocals, energetic beats, and lyrics that show a calm and positive attitude to move forward under any circumstances.[7]<br>
<br>
"Nightmare" is described as a medium tempo RnB with heavy string orchestration, retro swing rythm, lyrics express how even if the long night comes, if we remember the shining moments when we were together, the nightmare will disappear and the bright morning will come again.[7]<br>
<br>
"Iced Coffee" is described as an R&amp;B ballad song, emotional strings and guitar, transparent EP sound, expresses how one falls in love endlessly with the other person just like seeking iced coffee in the cold winter.[5]<br>
<br>
One Kiss is described as an provocative dance song, combines bass and synth sounds, addictive hook, fast paced groove, explosive singing, bold lyrics of stealing the hearts of strangers with a single kiss and making it our perfect secret.[5]<br>
<br>
"Bulldozer" is described as an dance song, heavy and intense bass, addictive hooks. Red Velvet's low vocals, coolly expresses the attitude of breaking down without stopping the limits or blocks placed by another person.[7]<br>
<br>
"Wings" is described as an up-tempo R&amp;B genre song. The track has jazz elements alongside a warm and refreshing piano, bells, and synth sounds. The lyrics talk about comparing their attitude towards life to the birth and flight of butterflies. Simply, a message about hope and support.[6]<br>
<br>
"Scenery" is described as an acoustic ballad genre song. Guitar melodies and soft vocals that give the listeners a cozy feeling. The lyrics talk about taking out and drawing our precious memories.[6]<br>
<br>
<span data-s9e-mediaembed="youtube" style="display:inline-block;width:100%;max-width:640px"><span style="display:block;overflow:hidden;position:relative;padding-bottom:56.25%"><iframe allowfullscreen="" loading="lazy" scrolling="no" style="background:url(https://i.ytimg.com/vi/xlyrt5eAtKI/hqdefault.jpg) 50% 50% / cover;border:0;height:100%;left:0;position:absolute;width:100%" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/xlyrt5eAtKI"></iframe></span></span><br>
<br>
<b><span style="font-size: 18px">Track list</span><br>
</b><br>
"Chill Kill"<br>
"Knock Knock (Who's There)"<br>
"Underwater"<br>
"Will I Ever See You Again?"<br>
"Nightmare"<br>
"Iced Coffee"<br>
"One Kiss"<br>
"Bulldozer"<br>
"Wings"<br>
"Scenery (품경화)"<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Eric Lyn]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>