<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】Dolby Atmos - Boris Blank - Resonance [E-AC3 JOC 5.1 | 16-bit 48kHz 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/boris-blank-resonance-e-ac3-joc-5-1-16-bit-48khz-1024-kb-s.243988/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/3b/55/8VjcZSy5_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/3b/55/8VjcZSy5_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Ambient, Electro</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">2024</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Blu-ray</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Resonance</b>" is the third (solo) studio album by Swiss artist and musician Boris Blank, released on February 16, 2024. Blank was born on 15 January 1952 in Bern, Switzerland and he is known for his work in the musical duo Yello with Dieter Meier. He is the musical part of Yello. He composes the songs and is responsible for the characteristic sound, having the reputation of a perfectionist. Blank considers himself as a constructor of music, starting composing with manipulation of self-recorded samples and finishing the tracks with the participation of invited professional musicians.<br>
<br>
Prior to his musical career, Blank worked as a truck driver. As a child he was very interested in music, but had no formal training. He never learned to read musical notation but always was interested in producing new sounds and samples. Blank began experimenting with tape loops and echo effects as a teenager. He recorded water sounds from a bucket of water and played sounds on a homemade bamboo flute. It was in this period he met Carlos Perón. Later, they formed Yello, with Dieter Meier as a conceptualist, vocalist and lyricist.<br>
<br>
He also composes and produces solo music, under the name Avant Garden, which is strictly intended for licensing to the film and TV production industry. This music is handled by Extreme Music.<br>
<br>
As a member of the Swiss cult band Yello, Blank has been shaping the development of electronic music for over four decades. Even as an established solo artist, the sound visionary has anchored his unmistakable DNA in global pop culture, which is still quoted by current acts today.<br>
<br>
With “Resonance” he defies the laws of space and time with a weightless fusion of ambient, trance and electro! The twelve tracks on “Resonance” were originally commissioned for the FORTYSEVEN thermal spa near Zurich, designed by Swiss star architect Mario Botta. Stefan Bock and Stefan Zaradić from IAN Records used the “Spatial Sound Wave” system developed by the internationally renowned Fraunhofer Institute to create an elaborately staged 3D soundscape with meditative sounds for wellness and relaxation. A completely new challenge for the notorious sound researcher, who ventures into previously undiscovered worlds of sound on his new album.<br>
<br>
<i>“I’ve always had a great affinity for wide, open spaces such as factory halls, underground car parks or even the mountains – and for the acoustic resonance that these spaces create,” says Boris Blank about the inspiration for “Resonance”. “Every room has its own unique vibrations. I like to penetrate these spheres and make them tangible with the help of music. The bigger, the more interesting. My aim this time was to make the spaces as big and wide as possible.”</i><br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Vertigo Heroes Part I <span style="color: #0059b3">3:44 </span><br>
02. Resonance <span style="color: #0059b3">3:56 </span><br>
03. Ninive <span style="color: #0059b3">5:04 </span><br>
04. Time Bridges <span style="color: #0059b3">6:08 </span><br>
05. Defying Gravity <span style="color: #0059b3">5:42 </span><br>
06. Angel Base <span style="color: #0059b3">4:00 </span><br>
07. Elements Of Life <span style="color: #0059b3">5:27 </span><br>
08. Respiro Di Mare <span style="color: #0059b3">4:24 </span><br>
09. Najade <span style="color: #0059b3">3:26 </span><br>
10. North Of Eden <span style="color: #0059b3">9:41 </span><br>
11. Vertigo Heroes Part II <span style="color: #0059b3">5:12 </span><br>
12. Mirage <span style="color: #0059b3">3:46 </span><br>
<br>
<b>Release Info</b><br>
The source is of this release is the lossless Dolby Atmos track from the Blu-ray release of Resonance.<br>
Encoded to "Dolby Digital Plus with Dolby Atmos" with Dolby Media Encoder.<br>
<br>
<div class="ToggleTriggerAnchor bbCodeSpoilerContainer">
<button type="button" class="button bbCodeSpoilerButton ToggleTrigger Tooltip JsOnly" data-target="> .SpoilerTarget"><span>Spoiler: <span class="SpoilerTitle">Media Info</span></span></button>
<div class="SpoilerTarget bbCodeSpoilerText">
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeCode">
<div class="type">Code:</div>
<pre>General
Complete name                  : 01. Vertigo Heroes Part I.m4a
Format                         : MPEG-4
Format profile                 : Apple audio with iTunes info
Codec ID                       : M4A  (isom/M4A /mp42)
File size                      : 28.1 MiB
Duration                       : 3 min 46 s
Overall bit rate mode          : Constant
Overall bit rate               : 1 038 kb/s
Album                          : Resonance
Album/Performer                : Boris Blank
Track name                     : Vertigo Heroes Part I
Track name/Position            : 1
Performer                      : Boris Blank
Genre                          : Electronic
Recorded date                  : 2024
Cover                          : Yes
pub                            : IAN Records (7)
STYLE                          : Ambient, Electro
MEDIATYPE                      : Blu-ray (Blu-ray Audio, Multichannel) (Deluxe Edition)
COUNTRY                        : Germany
CATALOGNUMBER                  : 0602458932362

Audio
ID                             : 1
Format                         : E-AC-3 JOC
Format/Info                    : Enhanced AC-3 with Joint Object Coding
Commercial name                : Dolby Digital Plus with Dolby Atmos
Codec ID                       : ec-3
Duration                       : 3 min 46 s
Bit rate mode                  : Constant
Bit rate                       : 1 024 kb/s
Maximum bit rate               : 1 081 kb/s
Channel(s)                     : 6 channels
Channel layout                 : L R C LFE Ls Rs
Sampling rate                  : 48.0 kHz
Frame rate                     : 31.250 FPS (1536 SPF)
Compression mode               : Lossy
Stream size                    : 27.7 MiB (99%)
Service kind                   : Complete Main
Default                        : Yes
Alternate group                : 2
Complexity index               : 16
Number of dynamic objects      : 15
Bed channel count              : 1 channel
Bed channel configuration      : LFE</pre>
</div></div>
</div><br>
<b>Note to the peeps @ RuTracker: Give credit if you post the work of someone else!</b><br>
- Hurby4 aka ADHDerby<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>