<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Metallica - Master of Puppets (Remastered) [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/metallica-master-of-puppets-remastered-qobuz-hi-res-audio-24-bit-96-0khz.242575/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 22px"><b>Metallica - Master of Puppets (Remastered) [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]</b></span><br>
<br>
<img src="https://imgur.com/gwqyw3n.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://imgur.com/gwqyw3n.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ALBUM REVIEW</b></span><br>
<br>
Metallica, a band stronger than The Beatles? Without a doubt if you consider sound power, but in terms of remastered editions featuring “a few” bonuses, the award might also go to the Four Horsemen if you compare the “Deluxe” edition of their third album to the Fab Four’s <i>Sgt. Pepper’s Lonely Hearts Club Band Anniversary (Super Deluxe Edition)</i>. In it, you’ll find the equivalent of no less than ten fully-packed CDs for this <i>Master Of Puppets</i> that many consider, rightly or wrongly, as Metallica’s own <i>Sgt. Pepper's</i>. Well, it’s true that you’ll struggle finding any defect in the armour of such a monument. And its lengthy gestation period, highlighted through archives at various stages of development, will no doubt reinforce the belief that the band was touched by grace at this very moment in their history.<br>
<br>
A few rare critics begrudge this album for not having been as surprising as its two predecessors. Indeed the general structure of <i>Master… </i>, as well as the majority of its titles, can be compared with <i>Ride The Lightning</i> from the first frantic title <i>Battery</i>, in the same vein as <i>Fight Fire With Fire</i>, to the epic final of <i>Damage Inc.</i>, wildly evoking a sped-up version of <i>Creeping Death</i>. There is also a false ballad halfway through, <i>Welcome Home (Sanitarium)</i>, reusing in essence the same ingredients as <i>Fade To Black</i> and the finely chopped instrumental of <i>Orion</i>, with a very vague similarity with <i>The Call Of Ktulu</i>… However while this third attempt can be seen as a synthesis of the previous two, <i>Master…</i> is by far the most accomplished in the sense that, for the first time, Metallica had the time and means to refine and polish their compositions to the point of almost perfection. Even when compared with recent productions, the album is technically inevitable and unrivalled.<br>
<br>
<i>Master Of Puppets</i> only brings division among fans when discussing its ranking among Metallica’s best albums − although it would always make the podium. The new approach offered here might sway a few more votes for the first position. But beyond a well deserved and convincing highlight of the quality of <i>Master…</i>, this album is also the undeniable accomplishment of the Cliff Burton era. An easily discernable period in the sense that the bass was beautifully put forward. And for good reason! Far from being a simple bass player, Cliff was both a driving force in terms of creativity and inspiration as and a generous and calm character, balancing and “harmonising” the relations within Metallica. As we’ll see later, his mediating role would have more than once been useful between Lars Ulrich and James Hetfield. Some even wonder if Kirk Hammett didn’t just stop getting better after this album, without Cliff’s mental and instrumental boosts.<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ABOUT THE ALBUM</b></span><br>
<ul>
<li>1 disc(s) - 8 track(s)</li>
<li>Total length: 00:54:44</li>
</ul><ul>
<li>Main artists: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/interpreter/metallica/62542" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Metallica</a></li>
<li>Label: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/label/blackened-records/download-streaming-albums/996388" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Blackened Records</a></li>
<li>Genre: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/genre/metal/download-streaming-albums" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Metal</a></li>
</ul><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div><b>Password: musicasylum</b>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Mu$iC @$YLUM]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>