<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - ZARD - The 12th Compilation Album - «Zard Forever Best: 25th Anniversary» [FLAC 24Bit/96kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/zard-the-12th-compilation-album-%C2%ABzard-forever-best-25th-anniversary%C2%BB-flac-24bit-96khz.227639/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center">fifty-twofifty-two<img src="https://i.imgur.com/lm4Dhi2.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/lm4Dhi2.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
<span style="font-family: 'Book Antiqua'"><span style="font-size: 15px"><b><b>ZARD</b> </b>was a Japanese pop group under B-Gram RECORDS. Around the release of their third album, HOLD ME, all the band members had left except Izumi Sakai (坂井泉水, born on February 6, 1967). ZARD then became the solo project of Izumi, writing all the music and lyrics herself. According to an episode of Music Station in 2005, ZARD has sold a combined total of 35,450,000 copies, making her the #8 best selling artist in Japan.<br>
<br>
ZARD also performed several songs that have been chosen as Japanese anime themes such as Meitantei Conan, Dragon Ball GT, and Slam Dunk. Since their debut, ZARD released 42 singles and 17 albums in total. Izumi's vocals are considered by many critics a high point of ZARD's music, which revolve around ballads.<br>
<br>
Sakai was diagnosed with cervical cancer in June 2006; the cancer went into remission, but despite this onset, on April of 2007, the cancer was on the move again. On the 26th of May, while being treated for this cancer, Sakai fell three meters from a hospital staircase while returning to her room from a routine walk around the hospital. She was found at 5:40am. She suffered severe trauma to the back of her head (brain contusion), and on 3:10pm she died due to the cerebral contusion. The slippery surface of the staircase due to rain the previous day was blamed for her fall. Some rumors about suicide were being considered, but in the end discarded.<br>
<br>
On June 27th 2007, a memorial funeral was held at Aoyama Cemetery.<br>
<br>
<span data-s9e-mediaembed="spotify" style="display:inline-block;width:100%;max-width:320px"><span style="display:block;overflow:hidden;position:relative;padding-bottom:125%;padding-bottom:calc(100% + 80px)"><iframe allow="encrypted-media" allowfullscreen="" loading="lazy" scrolling="no" src="https://open.spotify.com/embed/album/5HUTKtBwSnog4bLOOGRub8" style="border:0;height:100%;left:0;position:absolute;width:100%"></iframe></span></span></span><br>
<br>
The album was released on same day as Zard debut single «Good-bye My Loneliness». This album includes four CDs of the biggest hits from their career such as «Makenaide», «Yureru Omoi» or «Kokoro wo Hiraite» with total 52 tracks.<br>
<br>
Each CD symbolizes nature season such as spring (First CD), early summer (Second CD), later summer (Third CD) and autumn-winter (Fourth CD). This album was released to promote Zard's 25th anniversary debut. In 2017 they were released as individual CDs with different color title.<br>
<br>
All the songs went through digital remastering with new original release on Blu-spec CD format.<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div></span>​</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[WithLoveSNSD]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>