<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】MP3 - Ocean Vuong - On Earth We're Briefly Gorgeous - Unabridged Audiobook]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/ocean-vuong-on-earth-were-briefly-gorgeous-unabridged-audiobook.231930/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/ZhQq3dH/on-earth-we-re-briefly-gorgeous-3.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/ZhQq3dH/on-earth-we-re-briefly-gorgeous-3.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 12px"><i>On Earth We're Briefly Gorgeous</i> - <b>Ocean Vuong</b><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeQuote">
<aside>
<blockquote class="quoteContainer"><div class="quote">Publisher's Summary<br>
<br>
An instant <i>New York Times</i> Best Seller! <br>
<br>
Longlisted for the 2019 National Book Award for Fiction, the Carnegie Medal in Fiction, the 2019 Aspen Words Literacy Prize, and the PEN/Hemingway Debut Novel Award<br>
(...)<br>
Poet Ocean Vuong’s debut novel is a shattering portrait of a family, a first love, and the redemptive power of storytelling.<br>
<br>
On Earth We’re Briefly Gorgeous is a letter from a son to a mother who cannot read. Written when the speaker, Little Dog, is in his late 20s, the letter unearths a family’s history that began before he was born - a history whose epicenter is rooted in Vietnam - and serves as a doorway into parts of his life his mother has never known, all of it leading to an unforgettable revelation. <br>
<br>
At once a witness to the fraught yet undeniable love between a single mother and her son, it is also a brutally honest exploration of race, class, and masculinity. Asking questions central to our American moment, immersed as we are in addiction, violence, and trauma, but undergirded by compassion and tenderness, On Earth We’re Briefly Gorgeous is as much about the power of telling one’s own story as it is about the obliterating silence of not being heard. <br>
<br>
With stunning urgency and grace, Ocean Vuong writes of people caught between disparate worlds and asks how we heal and rescue one another without forsaking who we are. The question of how to survive, and how to make of it a kind of joy, powers the most important debut novel of many years. <br>
<br>
©2019 Ocean Vuong (P)2019 Penguin Audio</div><div class="quoteExpand quoteCut">Click to expand...</div></blockquote>
</aside>
</div><b>Specifications</b>:<br>
<br>
<b>By</b>: Ocean Vuong<br>
<b>Narrated by</b>: Ocean Vuong<br>
<b>Length</b>: 7 hrs and 19 mins<br>
<b>Unabridged Audiobook</b><br>
<b>Release date</b>: 06-04-19<br>
<b>Categories</b>: Literature &amp; Fiction, Historical Fiction, Asian American, LGBTQ+<br>
<b>Language</b>: English<br>
<b>Publisher</b>: Penguin Audio<br>
<b>Format</b>: mp3 64/48 stereo<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div></span>​</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[artlover]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>