<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Roxy Music - Avalon (2003 Remaster) [E-AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz | 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/roxy-music-avalon-2003-remaster-e-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz-1024-kb-s.226115/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/e7/5b/N4SyT9RK_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/e7/5b/N4SyT9RK_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Rock, Pop</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Pop Rock, Art Rock</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1982 (SACD release: 2003)</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">SACD, DSD 5.1 2.8 MHz </span><br>
<b>Format: <span style="color: #0059b3">E-AC-3 5.1</span><br>
Bit rate: <span style="color: #0059b3">1024 kb/s</span></b></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Avalon</b>" is the eighth and final studio album by English rock band Roxy Music, released on 28 May 1982 by E.G. Records, and Polydor. It was recorded between 1981 and 1982 at Compass Point Studios in Nassau, Bahamas, and is regarded as the culmination of the smoother, more adult-oriented sound of the band's later work. It has been credited with pioneering the sophisti-pop genre.<br>
<br>
The first single, "More Than This", preceded the album and was a top 10 hit in Britain, Australia, and several European countries. "Avalon", the second single, reached the top 20; "Take a Chance with Me" reached the top 30. In the United States, "More Than This" and "Take a Chance with Me" reached 103 and 104.<br>
<br>
<i>Avalon</i> is Roxy Music's most successful studio album. It stayed at number one on the UK Albums Chart for three weeks, and stayed on the chart for over a year. Although it reached only No. 53 in the US, <i>Avalon</i> endured as a sleeper hit and became Roxy Music's only million-selling US record, ultimately receiving platinum certification.<br>
<br>
In 2003, Virgin reissued <i>Avalon</i> on Hybrid Super Audio CD with a new 5.1-channel surround sound remix by the original production team of Rhett Davies (the producer) and Bob Clearmountain (the mixing engineer). The original 1982 stereo mix is left intact and is the same for the CD layer and for the HD layer, allegedly being transferred from analogue master tapes to DSD and processed in DSD throughout the process. The surround part of the HD layer includes the full album in the original running order plus the bonus track "Always Unknowing", whose original stereo mix is only available on CD on the 4-CD boxed set <i>The Thrill of It All</i> and in the 2012 <i>Roxy Music Complete Recordings</i> boxed set.<br>
<br>
Except for "India", the short instrumental piece whose original multi-track tape had been lost, all tracks in the surround mix were remixed from multi-track sources, as opposed to two-channel stereo mixes being 'upmixed' to 5.1 as in some DVD-Video releases. For "India," the stereo mix is panned clockwise a few times as the track plays, which ends in the rear right channel, from which the saxophone begins the next piece, "While My Heart Is Still Beating," making up for "India" not being a fully-fledged surround recording.<br>
<br>
The surround mix has roughly the same running times as the ten tracks present in the stereo mix. The main difference is in the stereo image being 360-degrees wide, as opposed to a front image plus rear ambiance, and the levels at which various tracks from the multi-track are mixed into the multi-channel mix. For instance, the guitar parts in "The Main Thing" and "Take a Chance with Me" are noticeably more prominent in the multi-channel mix than in the stereo mix. Guitar, saxophone, synthesizer, and percussion parts are often placed in the rear part of the sound field, while lead vocals tend to stick to the front center, as opposed to being mixed in dual-mono in front left and right like in the somewhat traditional 2.0 stereo mixing.<br>
<br>
In an interview with <i>Sound on Sound</i> regarding the surround-sound remix of <i>Avalon</i>, Clearmountain stated: <i>"This record probably means more to me than anything I've ever done. I've had more comments and compliments on this album by far than anything else I've ever done."</i><br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. More Than This <span style="color: #0059b3">04:31</span><br>
02. The Space Between <span style="color: #0059b3">04:28</span><br>
03. Avalon <span style="color: #0059b3">04:15</span><br>
04. India (instrumental) <span style="color: #0059b3">01:45</span><br>
05. While My Heart Is Still Beating <span style="color: #0059b3">03:25</span><br>
06. The Main Thing <span style="color: #0059b3">03:47</span><br>
07. Take A Chance With Me <span style="color: #0059b3">04:43</span><br>
08. To Turn You On <span style="color: #0059b3">04:10</span><br>
09. True To Life <span style="color: #0059b3">04:20</span><br>
10. Tara (instrumental) <span style="color: #0059b3">01:32</span><br>
Bonus Track<br>
11. Always Unknowing <span style="color: #0059b3">05:22</span><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>