<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【BLU-RAY】BD REMUX - Shakira Live from Paris 2011 1080i BluRay REMUX AVC DTS-HD MA 5.1-SiGLA]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/shakira-live-from-paris-2011-1080i-bluray-remux-avc-dts-hd-ma-5-1-sigla.242759/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><br>
<img src="https://ptpimg.me/5d34nx.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://ptpimg.me/5d34nx.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<a href="https://ibb.co/TBbYXT4" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/TBbYXT4/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-10-28-632.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/TBbYXT4/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-10-28-632.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/vkTzFTz" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/vkTzFTz/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-07-06-691.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/vkTzFTz/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-07-06-691.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/r3ncSc0" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/r3ncSc0/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-07-03-581.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/r3ncSc0/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-07-03-581.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/28K86Gn" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/28K86Gn/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-59-857.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/28K86Gn/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-59-857.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/yXJzYj3" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/yXJzYj3/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-58-778.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/yXJzYj3/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-58-778.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/WWQ4dBy" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/WWQ4dBy/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-56-973.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/WWQ4dBy/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-06-56-973.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/ZBfxjFK" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/ZBfxjFK/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-03-28-764.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/ZBfxjFK/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-03-28-764.png"></a> <a href="https://ibb.co/kgq9VPj" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/kgq9VPj/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-01-54-056.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/kgq9VPj/Shakira-Live-from-Paris-2011-1080p-Blu-Ray-REMUX-AVC-DTS-HD-MA-5-1-Si-GLA-mkv-snapshot-00-01-54-056.png"></a>​</div><br>
<div class="ToggleTriggerAnchor bbCodeSpoilerContainer">
<button type="button" class="button bbCodeSpoilerButton ToggleTrigger Tooltip JsOnly" data-target="> .SpoilerTarget"><span>Spoiler: <span class="SpoilerTitle">Blu-ray review</span></span></button>
<div class="SpoilerTarget bbCodeSpoilerText"><span style="font-size: 18px"><b>Shakira: En Vivo Desde París Blu-ray Review</b></span><br>
<span style="font-size: 15px"><b>Shakira storms Paris.</b></span><br>
<i>Reviewed by Jeffrey Kauffman, December 7, 2011</i><br>
<br>
<br>
The Latin Music market was largely an afterthought for decades, at least in the United States or the United Kingdom, where it was mostly relegated to "specialty" artists like Xavier Cugat, Carmen Miranda or Edmundo Ros. That changed somewhat in the late fifties and early sixties with the explosion of the Bossa Nova, which at least brought a greater global awareness to music south of the Equator, and transplanted artists like Antonio Carlos Jobim and Sergio Mendes became their country's ambassadors to the world music scene, scoring huge single and album successes. But after the Bossa Nova died down, Latin Music was once again mostly the purview of crossover artists like Carlos Santana or the Escovedos, who managed to blend elements of their ethnic heritage with more mainstream pop and rock sounds. The advent of <i>Tejano</i> gave us major chart successes like Selena, but by that time often "Latin Music" simply meant a traditional percussion ensemble playing alongside typical pop or rock consortiums that, aside from offering Spanish language lyrics, could just as easily be any stateside Top 40 act. Something along the same lines could be said of Shakira, the multi-platinum Colombian singer who has had enormous worldwide chart successes since the mid to late 1990's. Shakira's sound is <i>so</i> international, sometimes blending Middle Eastern sounds that are redolent of Ofra Haza, with more traditional Latin motifs and a lot of good ol' American dance and techno elements, that it seems a bit narrow to simply describe her sound as "Latin Music." And yet that's the genre she's been saddled with, for better or worse. The fact is she exploded out of her native country with such a force that she really should be considered an ambassador of World Music, if anything, for she sings in several languages (mostly in Spanish and English on this Blu- ray), and works in a wide enough variety of styles that relegating her to one fairly narrow category doesn't do her justice.<br>
<br>
Shakira makes her entrance out in the audience in a fluffy pink dress and slowly moves among her adoring fans, stopping to hug and kiss a few chosen ones, some of whom cry uncontrollably, others who scream "Yeah!" into her microphone. The music is surprisingly subdued, and longtime followers of this performer may wonder for a moment what exactly is going on. Has Shakira morphed into a laid back lounge singer? Of course not! Within a moment of her getting onstage, the dress has been shorn and we have the Shakira we're all used to, the madly gyrating, spandex-clad woman who's as much a poster girl as she is a pop star. The concert kicks into mostly high gear from then on, with a few relatively calmer ballads thrown into the mix, probably to give Shakira a well deserved chance to catch her breath.<br>
<br>
This isn't an all out assault on the senses, as might be expected from a superstar of Shakira's status. There are no fireworks, and while there <i>is</i> a large projection screen, it's relegated mostly to showing the singer herself so that those in the nosebleed seats can actually see who they came to enjoy. Shakira is in great voice throughout (though I must admit I personally do not like her weird full throated voice which often sounds like she's trying to gulp down a basketball), sounding alternately defiant and vulnerable. As might be expected, she ventures into some proto-Middle Eastern sounds (replete with her signature belly dancing), as well as more straight ahead rock-dance numbers. The quieter Flamenco segment is a standout, with some great acoustic guitar playing and nice dance moves.<br>
<br>
Shakira has an easy rapport with her audience, though she does tend to get into fairly cliché ridden rockstar mode a lot of the time, prancing around the stage like a distaff Steven Tyler, and of course turning the microphone out to the audience so that they can sing along with her on various tunes. (The audience is inordinately loud throughout a lot of this concert, so forewarned is forearmed and/or fore-eared). But Shakira is a walking advertisement for incredible sex appeal and charisma, and while the music itself may not be incredibly innovative or deep, it's well constructed and shows the performer off to her best advantage. There's a touching segment at the very end of the concert featuring African children on the giant screen talking about their dreams of what they want to be when they grow up, which segues into a boisterous "Waka Waka."<br>
<br>
<i>Shakira En Vivo Desde Paris</i> is presented on Blu-ray by Sony Music with an AVC encoded 1080i transfer in 1.78:1 that is one of the nicer looking concert videos in high definition in recent memory. While the opening sequence with the bright pink dress dances just this side of posterizing due to some aggressive lighting, for the most part colors are incredibly robust and stable without being overwhelming or blooming. The image is very sharp an well detailed and close-ups reveal every last inch of Shakira's rather incredible face and body. (In fact fine detail is so sharp that it almost looks like Shakira may have had a tracheotomy at some point—there's evidence of a slight scar on her throat). Black levels are really solid throughout this offering, and contrast is also excellent, so even when a lot of the stage is bathed in darkness, there's still sufficient shadow detail. The one niggling complaint some may have about this release is the general fuzziness of some of the far- and midrange shots, which don't match the sharpness of the closer up footage.<br>
<br>
<i>Shakira En Vivo Desde Paris</i> features two lossless and one lossy soundtrack, a DTS-HD Master Audio 5.1 mix, an LPCM 2.0 stereo fold down, and a standard Dolby Digital 5.1 mix. This is a multilingual concert, with songs and interstitial dialogue in French, English and Spanish (as well as whatever African language is being sung in "Waka Waka"). The best thing about the lossless mixes here is the awesome low end, especially since so many of these songs feature strong beats with powerful bass and drum work. Fidelity is exceptional throughout the DTS-HD Master Audio 5.1 track, though I for one would have much preferred the audience to have been mixed much more in the background. The audience does provide a really nice sense of immersion, however, so it's a bit of a trade off. There's not incredible dynamic range here, since the vast bulk of the tunes are rockers or dance numbers, but when things do quiet down at least a little for some of the ballads, the track sounds just as clear and precise.</div>
</div><br>
<b>Shakira</b>: En vivo desde París (English: Live from Paris) is the concert from the upcoming fourth live album by Colombian singer-songwriter Shakira. It features performances from the June 13 and 14 concerts in Paris, France.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklisting</b>:<br>
1. Pienso en Ti<br>
2. Why Wait<br>
3. Te Dejo Madrid<br>
4. Si Te Vas<br>
5. Whenever Wherever<br>
6. Inevitable<br>
7. Nothing Else Matters<br>
8. Despedida<br>
9. Gypsy<br>
10. La Tortura<br>
11. Ciega Sordomuda<br>
12. Underneath Your Clothes<br>
13. Gordita<br>
14. Sale el Sol<br>
15. Las de lntuición<br>
16. Loca<br>
17. She Wolf<br>
18. Ojos Así<br>
19. Antes de las Seis<br>
20. Hips Don’t Lie<br>
21. Waka Waka (This Time for Africa)<br>
22. Je L'Aime a Mourir<br>
<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeCode">
<div class="type">Code:</div>
<pre>General
Unique ID                                : 272947296651925982113700116795166604893 (0xCD57BCB83B4117FC49C8FA2D9F14BE5D)
Complete name                            : Shakira.Live.from.Paris.2011.1080p.BluRay.REMUX.AVC.DTS-HD.MA.5.1-SiGLA.mkv
Format                                   : Matroska
Format version                           : Version 4
File size                                : 23.8 GiB
Duration                                 : 1 h 39 min
Overall bit rate mode                    : Variable
Overall bit rate                         : 34.1 Mb/s
Movie name                               : Shakira Live from Paris (2011)
Writing application                      : mkvmerge v82.0 ('SiGLA') 64-bit
Writing library                          : libebml v1.4.5 + libmatroska v1.7.1
Cover                                    : Yes
Attachments                              : cover.jpg
IMDb                                     : tt2122472
TMDB                                     : movie/80263
TVDB                                     : 39082

Video
ID                                       : 1
Format                                   : AVC
Format/Info                              : Advanced Video Codec
Format profile                           : High@L4.1
Format settings                          : CABAC / 4 Ref Frames
Format settings, CABAC                   : Yes
Format settings, Reference frames        : 4 frames
Format settings, GOP                     : M=3, N=24
Codec ID                                 : V_MPEG4/ISO/AVC
Duration                                 : 1 h 39 min
Bit rate mode                            : Variable
Bit rate                                 : 27.1 Mb/s
Maximum bit rate                         : 35.0 Mb/s
Width                                    : 1 920 pixels
Height                                   : 1 080 pixels
Display aspect ratio                     : 16:9
Frame rate mode                          : Constant
Frame rate                               : 29.970 (30000/1001) FPS
Standard                                 : NTSC
Color space                              : YUV
Chroma subsampling                       : 4:2:0
Bit depth                                : 8 bits
Scan type                                : MBAFF
Scan type, store method                  : Interleaved fields
Scan order                               : Top Field First
Bits/(Pixel*Frame)                       : 0.436
Stream size                              : 18.9 GiB (79%)
Language                                 : English
Default                                  : Yes
Forced                                   : No
Color range                              : Limited
Color primaries                          : BT.709
Transfer characteristics                 : BT.709
Matrix coefficients                      : BT.709

Audio #1
ID                                       : 2
Format                                   : DTS XLL
Format/Info                              : Digital Theater Systems
Commercial name                          : DTS-HD Master Audio
Codec ID                                 : A_DTS
Duration                                 : 1 h 39 min
Bit rate mode                            : Variable
Bit rate                                 : 5 243 kb/s
Channel(s)                               : 6 channels
Channel layout                           : C L R Ls Rs LFE
Sampling rate                            : 48.0 kHz
Frame rate                               : 93.750 FPS (512 SPF)
Bit depth                                : 24 bits
Compression mode                         : Lossless
Delay relative to video                  : 1 s 101 ms
Stream size                              : 3.66 GiB (15%)
Title                                    : English 5.1ch DTS XLL @ 5 242 kb/s (DTS-HD MA 5.1)
Language                                 : English
Default                                  : Yes
Forced                                   : No

Audio #2
ID                                       : 3
Format                                   : FLAC
Format/Info                              : Free Lossless Audio Codec
Codec ID                                 : A_FLAC
Duration                                 : 1 h 39 min
Bit rate mode                            : Variable
Bit rate                                 : 1 766 kb/s
Channel(s)                               : 2 channels
Channel layout                           : L R
Sampling rate                            : 48.0 kHz
Frame rate                               : 11.719 FPS (4096 SPF)
Bit depth                                : 24 bits
Compression mode                         : Lossless
Stream size                              : 1.23 GiB (5%)
Title                                    : English 2.0ch FLAC @ 1 766 kb/s (FLAC 2.0)
Writing library                          : libFLAC 1.2.1 (UTC 2007-09-17)
Language                                 : English
Default                                  : Yes
Forced                                   : No

Text #1
ID                                       : 4
Format                                   : PGS
Muxing mode                              : zlib
Codec ID                                 : S_HDMV/PGS
Codec ID/Info                            : Picture based subtitle format used on BDs/HD-DVDs
Duration                                 : 1 h 37 min
Bit rate                                 : 1 030 b/s
Count of elements                        : 116
Stream size                              : 737 KiB (0%)
Language                                 : English
Default                                  : Yes
Forced                                   : No

Text #2
ID                                       : 5
Format                                   : PGS
Muxing mode                              : zlib
Codec ID                                 : S_HDMV/PGS
Codec ID/Info                            : Picture based subtitle format used on BDs/HD-DVDs
Duration                                 : 1 h 37 min
Bit rate                                 : 2 223 b/s
Count of elements                        : 198
Stream size                              : 1.55 MiB (0%)
Language                                 : Spanish
Default                                  : No
Forced                                   : No

Text #3
ID                                       : 6
Format                                   : PGS
Muxing mode                              : zlib
Codec ID                                 : S_HDMV/PGS
Codec ID/Info                            : Picture based subtitle format used on BDs/HD-DVDs
Duration                                 : 1 h 34 min
Bit rate                                 : 1 362 b/s
Count of elements                        : 110
Stream size                              : 939 KiB (0%)
Language                                 : French
Default                                  : No
Forced                                   : No

Menu
00:00:00.000                             : en:Pienso en Ti
00:02:39.993                             : en:Why Wait
00:05:27.794                             : en:Te Dejo Madrid
00:08:47.527                             : en:Si Te Vas
00:13:23.803                             : en:Whenever, Wherever
00:21:29.288                             : en:Inevitable
00:25:12.143                             : en:Nothing Else Matters / Despedida
00:31:07.198                             : en:Flamenco
00:33:44.489                             : en:Gypsy
00:40:14.412                             : en:La Tortura
00:43:51.629                             : en:Ciega Sordomuda
00:49:12.349                             : en:Underneath Your Clothes
00:53:13.523                             : en:Gordita
00:57:11.961                             : en:Sale el Sol
01:01:01.658                             : en:Las de la Intuicion
01:04:18.354                             : en:Loca
01:07:24.740                             : en:She Wolf
01:12:05.988                             : en:Ojos Asi
01:18:32.708                             : en:Antes de las Seis
01:21:27.949                             : en:Je L'Aime a Mourir
01:25:14.642                             : en:Hips Don't Lie
01:32:06.521                             : en:Waka Waka (This Time for Africa)
01:38:03.911                             : en:Credits (dedicated to friend SUPREME)</pre>
</div>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[-C.A.A]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - My Girl (2005) K-Drama OST]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/my-girl-2005-k-drama-ost.242758/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Hi,<br>
<br>
Was looking for: <a href="https://music.bugs.co.kr/album/8014246" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://music.bugs.co.kr/album/8014246</a> in either lossless OR iTunes. Can't purchase in my country. <br>
<br>
Thanks!!!
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[kxmonte]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>