<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Off-Topic】New USAC audio standard]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/new-usac-audio-standard.249080/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Well for starting this new standard is a brother of the famous MPEG H 3D Audio.<br>
<br>
The USAC (Unified Speech and Audio Coding)/xHE-AAC codec offers a quite unique experience apart from a better audio quality with less bitrate (equal to Opus).<br>
<br>
Usac offers a spatial audio encoder (MPEG Surround) that works with any content (Mono/Stereo/5.1). The way to work with 5.1 audio is to downmix to stereo and add the spatial information so that 5.1 equipment can reconstruct it, while with stereo and mono content it is possible to expand them to 5.1 with this technology, for headphones we will obtain an exclusive binaural mode using the Head-related transfer function (HRTF) technique, it is worth mentioning that this technology works with stereo and mono bit rates and is fully compatible with stereo or mono equipment as shown in the following image<br>
<br>
<img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/67/52/7ZhOcZQU_o.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/67/52/7ZhOcZQU_o.png" style=""><br>
<br>
MPEG DRC (Dynamic Range Control) technology is also used, this technology softens loud and soft sounds so that they have the same volume, this means that all content under the USAC codec will be at the same volume, even YT uses this technology (Stable Volume) "There are 3 volume settings for DRC that apply depending on the device we use and are automatically configured". <br>
<br>
There is a free encoder for USAC designed for medium and high bitrates without the encoding tools for low bitrates <br>
<a href="https://gitlab.com/ecodis/exhale" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://gitlab.com/ecodis/exhale</a><br>
(All files must be in Wav (PCM) at 48khz maximum in stereo, mono or 5.1) "This encoder does not downmix to stereo so it will work in 5.1 if the source is 5.1".<br>
I recommend the following command<br>
exhale.exe 9 C:\MusicInput.wav C:\MusicOutput.m4a<br>
<br>
(It will create an xHE-AAC file at 192kbps CVBR which is the maximum bit rate for stereo) "you can also change the number 9 to number 5 and get a file at 128kbps CVBR".<br>
<br>
It should be clarified that only certain devices can decode USAC natively and they are as follows.<br>
(Android 9, Android TV 9, Google TV, IOS 13, Windows 11, Xbox one and Series, Amazon's Fire OS 7 (based on Android 9 Pie).<br>
And a decoder is planned to be released soon for USAC via FFMPEG libraries.<br>
<a href="https://ffmpeg.org/index.html#news" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://ffmpeg.org/index.html#news</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Reyn29392]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>