<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】Dolby Atmos - Sting - ...Nothing Like the Sun [E-AC3 JOC | 16-bit 48 kHz | 5.1 | 768 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/sting-nothing-like-the-sun-e-ac3-joc-16-bit-48-khz-5-1-768-kb-s.251371/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/3d/ae/FBD0zY56_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/3d/ae/FBD0zY56_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Rock</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Soft Rock, Pop Rock</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1987</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Apple Music, with help of SonMaxime</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>...Nothing Like the Sun</b>" is the second solo studio album by English musician Sting. The album was originally released on 16 October 1987 on A&amp;M (worldwide) as a double LP and single CD. The album explores the genres of pop rock, soft rock, jazz, reggae, world, acoustic rock, dance-rock, and funk rock. The songs were recorded in March–August 1987 during sessions that took place at AIR Studios, in Montserrat, assisted by record producers Hugh Padgham, Bryan Loren, and Neil Dorfsman. It features a number of high-profile guest guitarists, including former Police member Andy Summers, Eric Clapton, Mark Knopfler, and Hiram Bullock, and is generally regarded as the culmination of the smoother, more adult-oriented sound of Sting's early work.<br>
<br>
The title comes from Shakespeare's Sonnet No. 130 ("My mistress' eyes are nothing like the sun"), which Sting used in the song "Sister Moon". He added that his inspiration for this was a close encounter with a drunk, in which Sting quoted the sonnet in response to the drunk's importunate query, "How beautiful is the moon?"<br>
<br>
On release, the album was received favorably by the majority of music critics and in 1989, the album was ranked No. 90 on Rolling Stone magazine's list of the "100 Best Albums of the Eighties". "We'll Be Together", "Be Still My Beating Heart", "Englishman in New York", "Fragile", and "They Dance Alone" were all released as singles.<br>
<br>
It won Best British Album at the 1988 Brit Awards. In 1989 the album received three Grammy nominations including Album of the Year while the album's second single ("Be Still My Beating Heart") was nominated for Song of the Year and Best Male Pop Vocal Performance.<br>
<br>
In the United States, the album debuted at number 54 on the US <i>Billboard</i> 200 chart on the week of 31 October 1987 and eventually peaked at number nine in its third week of release. The album spent a total of 52 weeks on the chart. On 24 October 1991, the album was certified double platinum by the Recording Industry Association of America (RIAA) for sales of over two million copies in the United States.<br>
<br>
In the UK, the album debuted and peaked at number one on the UK Albums Chart. In the second week the album dropped to number three. It spent a total of 42 weeks on the chart. The album was certified platinum by the British Phonographic Industry (BPI) for sales of over 300,000 copies in the United Kingdom.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. The Lazarus Heart <span style="color: #0059b3">4:35 </span><br>
02. Be Still My Beating Heart <span style="color: #0059b3">5:32 </span><br>
03. Englishman In New York <span style="color: #0059b3">4:27 </span><br>
04. History Will Teach Us Nothing <span style="color: #0059b3">4:59 </span><br>
05. They Dance Alone (Gueca Solo) <span style="color: #0059b3">7:14 </span><br>
06. Fragile <span style="color: #0059b3">3:55 </span><br>
07. We'll Be Together <span style="color: #0059b3">4:53 </span><br>
08. Straight to My Heart <span style="color: #0059b3">3:54 </span><br>
09. Rock Steady <span style="color: #0059b3">4:27 </span><br>
10. Sister Moon <span style="color: #0059b3">3:47 </span><br>
11. Little Wing <span style="color: #0059b3">5:04 </span><br>
12. The Secret Marriage <span style="color: #0059b3">2:04 </span><br>
<br>
<b>Note to the peeps @ RuTracker: Give credit if you post the work of someone else!</b><br>
- Hurby4 aka ADHDerby<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>