<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【SD】PACK - A Date with Sharon Tate (My Sharona &amp; Other Silly Love Songs) VA Vid 60s-00s 2024 S01E01]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/a-date-with-sharon-tate-my-sharona-other-silly-love-songs-va-vid-60s-00s-2024-s01e01.236529/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/(edited)_(edited)_81Xq3lYmXFL._AC_SL1500__huu8YSVP1M1QV3ALdpryUG.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/(edited)_(edited)_81Xq3lYmXFL._AC_SL1500__huu8YSVP1M1QV3ALdpryUG.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
<img src="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/(edited)_(edited)_Back_fDAzTr6QXM7zJVJmhDM3Zs.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/(edited)_(edited)_Back_fDAzTr6QXM7zJVJmhDM3Zs.png" style=""><br>
<br>
________________________________________________________________________________________________​</div><br>
<br>
<b>A Date with Sharon Tate (My Sharona &amp; Other Silly Love Songs) Various Artists Video 1960s-2000s 2024 S01E01</b><br>
<br>
+ 24 January 2024 - Happy Birthday, Sharon - <br>
<br>
Love, DJ/VJ mikedreams AKA mikeburns4U aka thewaymouth aka White Dope On Punk +<br>
<br>
<i>(Originally posted on demonoid, 24 January 2024.)</i><br>
<div style="text-align: center"><br>
___________________________________________________________________________________________________​</div><br>
<b>' b/w '</b><br>
<br>
<b>We will control the audio. We will control the video. AKA A/V matches made in madness er, heaven (and hell).</b><br>
<br>
<b>Glossary:'b/w', as in 'backed with,' signifying the switching out of a video's audio with some other's (as listed).</b><br>
<br>
Videos and audios may come and go appearing in multiple versions and with multiple art-partners in your future.<br>
<br>
This is Part 1 of a Series of 10 (at this point in time). ...If there is a demand here is a man... Now you decide.<br>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center">-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------​</div><br>
All thanks go to the directors, cinematographers, actors, writers, editors, sharers, musicians, singers and dancers. <br>
<br>
<i>Goodness Gracious Great Goddess Almighty thanks so much to ShareMania! </i><br>
<br>
Movies and TV clips in this episode but not listed below include: <br>
<br>
Outer limits (2022); The Trip (1967); Dr. Who (1977-1978); Wormwood (2018); Saturday Night Live (1996); Taxi Driver (1976); The Thrree Stooges (1944).<br>
<br>
SPOILER ALERT You've been warned.<br>
STEREO Unless otherwise.<br>
________________________<br>
<br>
<b>Episode 1: Star / Hostess, Courtney Love (and Hole), <br>
with her special guests, Sir Elton John, Led Zeppelin, Ke$ha, Lady Gaga, Stevie Nicks (and Fleewtood Mac), Blondie, Bob Dylan and Joni Mitchell.</b><br>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center">___________________________________________________________________________________________________​</div><br>
* <b>Lust to Love (Synesthesia to Zzshing!) [The Go-Go's Rules of Attraction</b> || Lust to Love [edit] - The Go-Go's - Side 1, Track 4, Beauty and the Beat (14 July 1981) [Beauty and the Bastille Day Beat - From day one we were free to lose our heads! -md.] - As regards this scene, the film's director and screenwriter Roger Avery: "Because the girls are doing cocaine I decided to speed up the song by 10%, or so" - Synesthesia to Zzshing! - The Rules of Attraction - 2002 film screenplay is based on the 1987 book of the same title by Bret Easton Ellis - Cast incl. Ian Somerhalder as Paul Denton, James Van Der Beek as Sean Bateman, Jessica Biel as Lara Holleran, Shannyn Sossamon as Lauren Hynde, Russell Sams as Richard "Dick" Jared, Swoosie Kurtz as Mimi Jared, Faye Dunaway as Mrs. Eve Denton, Kip Pardue as Victor Johnson, Eric Stoltz as Mr. Lance Lawson - per wiki, the story follows three Camden College students who become entangled in a love triangle with a drug dealer, a virgin, and a bisexual classmate... who give apathetic interior monologues on their lives - US-DE, 2002] * <br>
<br>
* <b>The First Cut is The Deepest (Dial M for Murder) [The Koobas</b> || The First Cut is The Deepest (Cat Stevens cover) - The Koobas - 1967 <br>
b/w <br>
Title scene: Dial M for Murder - US, 1954] * <br>
<br>
* <b>Pretty on the Inside (Hole </b>- band: Courtney Love (vocals/guitar), Eric Erlandson (guitar), Jill Emery (bass), Caroline Rue (drums) - opener, Club Lingerie, LA CA - 10 Oct 1990) [Original video direction/editing by Video Bob | additional audio/video post-production/restoration by sonicboy19, 2019] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Goldie Keif &amp; Tommy Smothers (Dicknail) [Hole Comedy Hour, 1967</b> || Goldie Keif (Leigh French in recurring character debut) - The Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour [US TV, CBS, weekly comedy and variety show] - 11 June 1967 <br>
b/w Dicknail - Hole, Club Lingerie, LA CA - 10 Oct 1990] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Both Sides Now (Joni Mitchell - closer, Isle of Wight Festival</b> 1970) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Backstabber - Party at a Rich Dude's House (Judas Gaga Ke$ha P!nk Party </b>|| BACKSTABBER + PARTY AT A RICH DUDE'S HOUSE - Ke$ha - from, Animal - 2010 b/w JUDAS promo / intro edit - Lady Gaga - 2011 + GET THE PARTY STARTED Ernie's All Night Party Anthem edit [edit] - P!nk - 2001] *<br>
<br>
* <b>I Know What Boys Like (Lady Snowblood) [The Waitresses</b> || I Know What Boys Like - single from, Wasn't Tomorrow Wonderful? - The Waitresses - 1982 b/w Original Trailer (with Eng. subs): Lady Snowblood - JP, 1973] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Untouched (The Veronicas - Freshly Squeezed</b> [UK TV, Channel 4, weekday breakfast show] - 22 May 2009) {special thanks to UCI for the video file} *<br>
<br>
* <b>Whole Lotta Love (Gett Off) (Prince and Led Zeppelin</b> || Whole Lotta Love - lead track, Led Zeppelin II - Led Zeppelin - 22 October 1969 b/w Gett Off promo - Prince and the New Power Generation - 7 June 1991] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Remedy (Touch Me All Night Long Club) [Black Crowes &amp; Cathy Dennis</b> || Remedy - The Black Crowes - show opener - Fox Theatre, Atlanta GA - 4 April 1999 b/w Touch Me (All Night Long) [Club mix] promo - Cathy Dennis - 1991] * <br>
<br>
* <b>Radio Friendly Unit Shifter (Violet) [Nirvana opener &amp; Hole closer</b> || Radio Friendly Unit Shifter - Nirvana - show opener, The LA Forum, Inglewood CA, 30 December 1993 b/w Violet - Hole - set closer, Reading Festival, Little John's Farm, Reading UK, Friday, 25 August 1995] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Too Much of Nothing (Peter, Paul &amp; Mary - The Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour</b> - Bob Dylan cover - 23 Mar 1969) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Silly Love Songs (Mono) [Paul McCourtney</b> || Silly Love Songs - Wings - single from, Wings at the Speed of Sound (26 March 1976) - April Fools' Day (1 April) 1976 b/w Mono promo - Courtney Love - single from America's Sweetheart (10 Feb 2004) - 16 Feb 2004] * <br>
<br>
* <b>About a (Typical) Girl [Slits &amp; Nirvana</b> || About a Girl - Nirvana - Seattle Center Arena, Seatltle WA, 7 January 1994 b/w Typical Girls promo - The Slits - 1979] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Alfie (Cher - The Smothers Brothers Comedy Hour</b> - Burt Bacharach and Hal David song - 21 May 1967) *<br>
<br>
* <b>The Bitch Is Back (She's a Maniac) [Elton John</b> || The Bitch Is Back - Elton John - reached No. 1 CA, 4 US, 15 UK - comes with the Tower of Power horns and backing vocals from Clydie King, Sherlie Matthews, Jessie Mae Smith, and Dusty Springfield - 3 September 1974 b/w Maniac - Michael Sembello - Flashdance promo - US, 1983] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Private Dancer (Tina Turner</b> - promo, 1985) *<br>
<br>
* <b>When the Levee Breaks Part 2 (Niagara) [Led Zeppelin</b> || When the Levee Breaks (edit) - Led Zeppelin - Ultimate track, Led Zeppelin IV - 8 Nov 1971 b/w Trailer (b/w): Niagara - US, 1953] *<br>
<br>
* <b>My Sister, Dame with a Rod coda (Physical) [Juliana Hatfield</b> - My Sister, Dame with a Rod (coda) - The Juliana Hatfield Three - tracks from, Become What You Arev (Recorded at Holywood Sound, LA CA) - 3 August 1993 b/w Physical promo - Juliana Hatfield - from, Juliana Hatfield Sings Olivia Newton-John - 13 April 2018] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Takin' a Ride (The Replacements - 7th St. Entry</b>, First Avenue, Minneapolis MN, 5 September 1981) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Sirens (Gimme Some Love) [Lichtensteiner &amp; Gina G</b> || Sirens [edit] - Lichtensteiner b/w Gimme Some Love promo - Gina G - single from debut lp, Fresh! (4 March 1997, US) - 25 August 1997, UK] *<br>
<br>
* <b>I Just Wanna See His Face (I'm Gonna Love You Too) [Blondie &amp; the Stones</b> || I Just Wanna See His Face [edit] - The Rolling Stones - from, Exile on Main St. - 26 May 1972 b/w I'm Gonna Love You Too (Blondie - Buddy Holly cover - TopPop - 1978-09-09) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Sex Beat (Slow Motion) [Blondie &amp; the Gun Club</b> || Sex Beat - The Gun Club - lead track, debut lp, Fire of Love (Recorded in Pasadena and LA CA) - 31 August 1981 b/w Slow Motion promo - Blondie - 1979] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Alone Again Or (All The Marbles 1981 Trailer) [Love</b> || Alone Again Or - Love - Single/Lead track, Forever Changes (Recorded at Sunset Sound, Hollywood; 1 Nov 1967) - January 1968 b/w Trailer: ...All the Marbles (Intl. title: The California Dolls) - per Wikipedia, re: Production Development: "Director Rober Aldrich said he wanted to make the film "because nobody's done anything about women's wrestling before." <br>
"It's purely, totally commercial," added Aldrich. "It fits in with my philosophy, which is that the process is at best a craft, not art." <br>
Aldrich says he was brought the story by Mel Frohman "and we stole the whole psychological drive and ending from Abe Polonsky's "Body and Soul (1947)", a film on which Aldrich had been an assistant director. Aldrich said the theme of that movie "was that the biggest damage you can suffer is the loss of self-esteem and a fall from grace. The struggle to regain that esteem will fuel any plot. You don't even have to win." Aldrich says he also stole from 'Body and Soul' for the last act of The Longest Yard (1974). Aldrich said that "Rocky was Body and Soul except that an Italian fighter wins, and in the original, a Jewish fighter loses. We have here two girls and a manager of questionable credentials. All three have already fallen from grace, and they struggle to redeem their self esteem. Hopefully, it will take two funny hours to happen." - Movie poster tagline: The California Dolls and their best friend Harry... Together they're going for ...All the Marbles - US, 16 October 1981] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Rock and Roll (The Poseidon Adventure) [Led Zeppelin</b> || Rock and Roll - Led Zeppelin - single from, Led Zeppelin IV - single rel: 22 Feb 1972 (US only) b/w Trailer: The Poseidon Adventure - US, 12 Dec 1972] *<br>
<br>
* <b>She Part 1 (Put The Blame On Mame guitar vers) [Edie Brickel &amp; Gilda</b> || She [edit] - Edie Brickell &amp; New Bohemians - from, Shooting Rubberbands at the Stars - 9 August 1988 - Put The Blame On Mame (guitar version scene) - Rita Hayworth [with the singing voice of Anita Kert Ellis dubbed in] - Gilda - Song by Allan Roberts and Doris Fisher, originally written for Gilda: per wiki, A 1946 American film noir directed by Charles Vidor and starring Rita Hayworth and Glenn Ford. The film is known for cinematographer Rudolph Maté's lush photography, costume designer Jean Louis's wardrobe for Hayworth (particularly for the dance numbers), and choreographer Jack Cole's staging - Editing by Charles Nelson - <br>
Side note: Gilda, the 23-kiloton air-deployed nuclear weapon detonated on 1 July 1946, during Operation Crossroads nuclear test... Attesting to its immediate success, it was widely reported that an atomic bomb to be tested at Bikini Atoll in the Marshall Islands would bear the film's title above an image of Hayworth, a reference to her bombshell status. The bomb was decorated with a photograph of Hayworth cut from the June 1946 issue of Esquire magazine; above it was stenciled the device's nickname, "Gilda", in two-inch black letters... Hayworth was deeply offended. According to Orson Welles, her husband at the time of filming Gilda, Hayworth believed it to be a publicity stunt from Columbia executive Harry Cohn and was furious. Welles told biographer Barbara Leaming: "Rita used to fly into terrible rages all the time, but the angriest was when she found out that they'd put her on the atom bomb. Rita almost went insane, she was so angry. ... She wanted to go to Washington to hold a press conference, but Harry Cohn wouldn't let her because it would be unpatriotic." Welles tried to persuade Hayworth that the whole business was not a publicity stunt on Cohn's part, that it was simply homage to her from the flight crew. - Hayworth later came to resent the film and its effect on her image. Hayworth once said with some bitterness, "Men go to bed with Gilda, but wake up with me." - [Men go to bed with Gilda, but wake up with an Atomic Bombshell. And every now and then we never wake up again. 'Oh, that's the way, uh-huh' ('Uh-huh') 'I like it, uh-huh' ('Uh-huh') -md.] - US, 25 April 1946) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Gimme More Hole Malibu Girlfriend (Britney vs. Avril</b> || Gimme More Girlfriend (N-A mashup mix) - Brtiney Spears vs Avril Lavigne - 2007 b/w Malibu promo - Hole - single from, Celebrity Skin (8 September 1998) - 29 December 1998] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Cannonball (Don't Blame Your Daughter) (Cardigans &amp; Breeders</b> || Cannonball - The Breeders - lead single from, Last Splash (30 August 1993) - 9 August 1993 b/w Don't Blame Your Daughter (Diamonds) [The Cardigans - single from, Super Extra Gravity - 6 Feb 2006] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Blame It on the Boogie (Gilda &amp; the Jacksons</b> || Blame It on the Boogie - The Jacksons - single from, Destiny (18 December 1978) - Song written by Mick Jackson, Dave Jackson [both unrelated to The Jacksons] and Elmar Krohn - Although Mick Jackson recorded the song in 1977, "Blame It on the Boogie" [BIOTB] was written per wiki, in hopes of being sold to Stevie Wonder. The Mick Jackson recording was released in the US in August 1978. Despite the Mick Jackson original reaching a No. 61 peak US in September 1978, Epic Records that month released the Jacksons' version of BIOTB as the advance single from the Destiny album. Although BIOTB returned the Jacksons to the Hot 100 after five flop singles, it was not the single to effect a major comeback for the Jacksons, peaking at #54... In the UK, both the Mick Jackson version and the Jacksons' were released within a few days of each other in September 1978. The Jacksons' version was the more successful version reaching No. 8 on the chart dated 4 November; the Mick Jackson version had peaked at No. 15 on the chart for 21 October - The Jacksons' single rel: August 1978 US, 8 September 1978 UK<br>
b/w Put the Blame on Mame - Gilda - US, 25 April 1946) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds [Elton John with Lucy</b> || Lucy in the Sky with Diamonds (The Beatles cover) - The Elton John Band - band: Elton John: lead and backing vocals, piano, mellotron, harpsichord; John Lennon (as Dr. Winston O'Boogie): backing vocals, guitars; Davey Johnstone: backing vocals, electric guitar, sitar; Dee Murray: bass guitar, backing vocals; Nigel Olsson: drums, backing vocals; Ray Cooper: tambourine, tubular bells, gong, maracas, mark tree, congas - single went to No. 1 CA &amp; US (for 2 weeks each), 3 AU, 10 UK, 11 NZ - 15 November 1974 UK, 18 November 1974 US b/w THE END: Lucy - Writtend and Directed by Luc Besson; Produced by Virginie Besson-Silla; Cinematography: Thierry Arbogast; Edited by Julien Rey; Visual effects: Richard Bluff, Stephen Bevins, Stephen DeLuca, Tiffany Yung - Scene stars in order of appearance: Scarlett Johansson as Lucy Miller, an unwilling drug mule who is accidentally dosed with a drug that activates a myriad of pre-encoded genetic conscious capabilities; Morgan Freeman as Professor Samuel Norman, a scientist and a professor at the University of Paris who has knowledge of different human capabilities; Choi Min-sik as Mr. Jang, a Korean drug lord; Amr Waked as Pierre Del Rio, a French police officer - FR - 25 July 2014 US, 6 August 2014 FR] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Happy Birthday (Altered Images</b> - August 1981) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Birthday (English version) [The Sugar Cubes</b> - August 1987] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Silver Springs (Stand Back) [Fleetwood Nicks mixshow</b> || Silver Springs - Fleetwood Mac - outtake edit - Nov 1976 b/w Stand Back (mixshow) - Stevie Nicks - 19 May 1983] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Midnight Creeper (Sleep Comes Down) [Elton with Psych Furs</b> || Midnight Creeper - Elton John - Fifth/Final track, Side 1, Don't Shoot Me I'm Only the Piano Player - 26 January 1973 b/w Sleep Comes Down promo - from, Forever Now - 24 September 1982] {audio file kindly c/o Pbthal} *<br>
<br>
* <b>Last Day of Magic (The Kills</b> - single from, Midnight Boom (10 March 2008) - 15 June 2008) *<br>
<br>
* <b>That Great Love Sound (The Raveonettes</b> - single from, Chain Gang of Love (25 August 2003) - 18 August 2003) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Love Is the Drug (Roxy Music - Wembley</b> Empire Pool, London, UK - Oct 17-18, 1975) [Restore by Nacho 2022] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Pennyroyal Tea (Hang with Me) [Hole &amp; Robyn</b> || Pennyroyal Tea (Nirvana cover) - Hole - Phoenix Festival, Stratford-upon-Avon UK, 16 July 1993 b/w Hang with Me - Robyn - Berns Salonger, Stockholm, Sweden - 14 December 2010] *<br>
<br>
* <b>The Greatest (Miss World) [Hole with Cat Power</b> || The Greatest - Cat Power - Lead/Title track, The Greatest - 20 January 2006 b/w Miss World promo - Hole - lead single, Live Through This (12 April 1994) - The only music video by Hole that features bassist Kristen Pfaff (26 May 1967 Buffalo NY - 16 June 1994 Seattle WA). Directed by Sophie Muller [who directs as well, The Kills in, Last Day of Magic, and The Raveonettes in, That Great Love Sound] the video was filmed in Los Angeles in February 1994. The video per wiki, is heavily influenced by the style and decorations of the 1976 film Carrie. Much of the latter image bears striking resemblance to the cover of Live Through This - 28 March 1994] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Stutter (Elastica</b> - The song's music video per wiki, was directed by David Mould and filmed in San Francisco CA. It features the band members playfully meandering from Grant Avenue in Chinatown to the Broadway stretch of strip clubs and other adult businesses - 1 November 1993 UK, 20 September 1994 US) * <br>
<br>
* <b>Nothing Was Delivered take 2 (Vienna Calling) [Falco &amp; Bob Dylan</b> || Nothing Was Delivered (take 2) - Bob Dylan and the Band - from, The Basement Tapes Complete - 1967-2014 b/w Vienna Calling - Falco - 11 Sept 1985] *<br>
<br>
*<b> The Red Telphone mix [Love &amp; Lady Gaga ft. Beyoncé</b> || The Red Telephone - Love - from, Forever Changes - 1 Nov 1967 b/w Telephone (mix) - Lady Gaga ft. Beyoncé - 26 January 2010] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Too Much of Nothing take 2 (Union City Blue) [Blondie &amp; Bob Dylan</b> || Too Much of Nothing (take 2) - Bob Dylan and the Band - from, The Basement Tapes Complete - 1967-2014 b/w Union City Blue - Blondie - 23 Nov 1979] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Do It Clean (with Credit &amp; Cars) [Hole &amp; Madonna Megamix</b> || DO IT CLEAN [Echo &amp; the Bunnymen cover - Phoenix Festival, Stratford-upon-Avon UK, 16 July 1993] &gt; CREDIT IN THE STRAIGHT WORLD [Young Marble Giants cover - Phoenix Fest 1993] &gt; CARS (edit) [Gary Newman cover, live 1995 b/w Madonna Megamix - GHV2 Megamix / Johnny Rocks Mac Quayle Mix - 2001] {video file c/o A Time to Remember, 2021} *<br>
<br>
* <b>Whole Lotta Love (Led Zeppelin</b> - Image Promo Film - taken from, 'Led Zeppelin II' (22 Oct 1969) [the lp went No. 1 in several countries incl. the US and UK] - note per wiki: parts of the song's lyrics were adapted from Willie Dixon's "You Need Love", recorded by Muddy Waters in 1962; originally uncredited to Dixon, a lawsuit in 1985 was settled with a payment to Dixon and credit on subsequent releases - WLL was the band's first hit and a smash all over the world, reaching No. 4 in the US (becoming their only Top-10 US single) [note: Zep did not release singles in the UK] - side note: Charlie is arrested and put in jail (for what became for good) 12 October 1969 - Whole Lotta Love rel: 7 November 1969) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Are You Experienced? (The Jimi Hendrix Experience</b> - from the album, Are You Experienced - 12 May 1967 (UK) 23 August 1967 (US) - 1984) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Violet (Hole - Later... with Jools Holland</b> (BBC TV music show) - band: Courtney Love: lead vocals, rhythm guitar; Eric Erlandson: lead guitar; Melissa Auf der Maur: bass, backing vocals; Patty Schemel: drums- 2 May 1995)<br>
<br>
* <b>Sugar Coma (Sisters of the Moon) [The Hole Mac</b> || Sugar Coma - Hole - Reading Festival, Reading UK, Friday, 25 August 1995 b/w Sisters of the Moon - Fleetwood Mac - Checkerdome, St. Louis MO - 1979-11-06) {video file kindly c/o Direct VHS Transfer &amp; Upscale by Fabian Kieper} *<br>
<br>
* <b>Rebel Girl (Celebrity Skin) [Bikini Kill ft. Hole</b> || Rebel Girl - Bikini Kill - Sunday Night Live - WAIF-FM - Cincinnati, OH - 13 September 1992 b/w Celebrity Skin - Hole - 8 September 1998] *<br>
<br>
* <b>Woodstock (The Who Are My Joni Generatio</b>n || Woodstock - Joni Mitchell - from, Ladies of the Canyon - April 1970 b/w My Generation - The Who - closer, Woodstock, 17 Aug 1969) *<br>
<br>
* <b>Olympia (ft. Good King Wenceslas) [Fun For Me - Moloko Hole</b> || Olympia (ft. Good King Wenceslas) - Hole - Live 105's 4th Annual Green Christmas Acoustic Concert (Headliner: Hole // The rest: Simple Minds, The Go Go's, The Jesus &amp; Mary Chain, Bad Religion, Sheryl Crow, Live, Luscious Jackson, Lightning Seeds, Love Spit Love, Tom Jones) - Community Theater, Berkeley CA - 9 December 1994 b/w Fun For Me (party version) - from, Do You Like My Tight Sweater? (20 Oct 1995) - 1995] {video file remastered by Maxis Maximal, 2023} *<br>
<br>
* <b>Punk Rock Girl Take the Skinheads Bowling (Dead Milkmen ft. Camper Van NENA</b> || Punk Rock Girl - The Dead Milkmen - single from, Beelzebubba - December 1988 &gt; Take the Skinheads Bowling [edit] - Camper Van Beethoven - from, Telephone Free Landslide Victory - 1985 b/w Rette mich - NENA - Superstar - 1984-05-25) *<br>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center">_________________________________________________________________________________________________________________________________<br>
​</div><br>
<div style="text-align: center"><img src="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/95f0b32f-2ee0-4895-a092-e46ea17f0ebf.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/95f0b32f-2ee0-4895-a092-e46ea17f0ebf.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
<img src="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/3890581020A-1-1-1.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/3890581020A-1-1-1.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div> <img src="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/8600.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://hosting.photobucket.com/images/k256/thewaymouth/8600.jpg" style="">​</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[mikedreams]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>