<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Bon Jovi - This House Is Not For Sale (Deluxe) [HIGHRESAUDIO 24bits/96.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/bon-jovi-this-house-is-not-for-sale-deluxe-highresaudio-24bits-96-0khz.237694/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://storage.highresaudio.com/web/imgcache/49a9fcaab60f8bf4e4b5d56b1ae41df7/a6n6tn-thishousei-master_550x550.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://storage.highresaudio.com/web/imgcache/49a9fcaab60f8bf4e4b5d56b1ae41df7/a6n6tn-thishousei-master_550x550.jpg" style=""> <br>
Album info<br>
Album-Release:<br>
2018<br>
<br>
HRA-Release:<br>
19.01.2024<br>
<br>
Label: Bon Jovi Profit Split<br>
<br>
Genre: Rock<br>
<br>
Subgenre: Hard Rock<br>
<br>
Artist: Bon Jovi<br>
<br>
Info for This House Is Not For Sale (Deluxe)<br>
<br>
<br>
Deluxe Edition of the fourteenth full-length studio album by legendary American Melodic Rock/Hard Rock band.<br>
<br>
Band's first studio album with Phil X on lead guitar, who replaced longtime member Richie Sambora in 2013. It's also the first album where bassist Hugh McDonald officially replaces original bassist Alec John Such, who left the band in 1994.<br>
<br>
Musically, this is a throwback - not to the '80s, but to 2005's "Have A Nice Day", which is the first album Bon Jovi recorded with producer John Shanks. Often, "This House Is Not for Sale", which is the sixth album Shanks has recorded with Bon Jovi, recalls the exuberant singalongs from "Have A Nice Day" ("God Bless This Mess" is a kissing cousin to "Who Says You Can't Go Home"), but where that 2005 album felt joyful, this 2016 album is driven in part by spite. Thirty years into his career and Jon Bon Jovi still acts like the underdog, and he still sings like he has scores to settle. Presumably, some of these outstanding debts may be with Sambora, who did not leave on good terms, but Jon Bon Jovi is determined that "This isn't how the story ends, my friends, it's just a fork along the road," which goes a long way toward explaining how muscular "This House Is Not for Sale" is. Bon Jovi and Shanks may not have done much to freshen up the band's sound, but that simmering defiance does mean this is the band's liveliest album in years!<br>
<br>
It is Bon Jovi's sixth US number-one album and it also became their fourth album in a row to hit No. 1 in the US after What About Now, The Circle and Lost Highway. "This House Is Not for Sale" debuted at number one on the Billboard 200 with 129000 album-equivalent units, of which 128000 were pure album sales. In the United Kingdom, the album debuted at number five on the UK Albums Chart, selling 21448 units in its first week. As of January 2017, the album had sold 174000 copies in the United States. As of March 2018, the album has sold 326000 pure copies in the US.<br>
<br>
The bonus tracks include "We Don't Run", which was already released on "Burning Bridges", "Real Love", which was still to be found on the previous album as "Blind Love". "I Will Drive You Home" and "Touch Of Grey" are two melancholy songs, but typically for Jon Bon Jovi they radiate a positive mood.<br>
<br>
"This House Is Not For Sale" in the eighteen-song edition is a varied album that will find favour with many fans, but will certainly give the critics plenty of ammunition for negative remarks.<br>
<br>
"Stylistically, too, the roots of the new songs reach back to the 80s again and again, as in the title track, which is about integrity, and Bon Jovi make it clear once and for all that 'this heart, this soul, this house is not for sale'." (Good Times)<br>
<br>
"The production sounds American fat, the drums are aggressively mixed to the front and Schnucki boss Bon bangs with his usual breathless emotional timbre. But the secret star of the old rockers is the new X-Man." (stereoplay)<br>
<br>
Bon Jovi<br>
<br>
Digitally remastered<br>
<br>
<a href="http://tracklist/" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><b>Tracklist</b></a><br>
<ul>
<li>01 When We Were Us</li>
<li>02 Walls</li>
<li>03 This House Is Not For Sale</li>
<li>04 Living With The Ghost</li>
<li>05 Knockout</li>
<li>06 Labor Of Love</li>
<li>07 Born Again Tomorrow</li>
<li>08 Roller Coaster</li>
<li>09 New Year's Day</li>
<li>10 The Devil's In The Temple</li>
<li>11 Scars On This Guitar</li>
<li>12 God Bless This Mess</li>
<li>13 Reunion</li>
<li>14 Come On Up To Our House</li>
<li>15 Real Love</li>
<li>16 All Hail The King</li>
<li>17 We Don't Run</li>
</ul>Download Link:<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[hulimili]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>