<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Carpenters - Singles 1969-1981 [E-AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz | 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/carpenters-singles-1969-1981-e-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz-1024-kb-s.229518/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/87/7e/ZtBZe72Z_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/87/7e/ZtBZe72Z_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Pop</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Vocal</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1999</span><br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">SACD</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Singles 1969-1981</b>" is a compilation album by American vocal and instrumental duo Carpenters, consisting of sister Karen and brother Richard Carpenter. The CD compilation was released in 1999. A Hybrid SACD version with the same name but with some difference in the track listing, was released in 2004. In June 2016, the album was certified Gold in the United Kingdom for sales of 100,000 copies sold.<br>
<br>
<b>Carpenters</b> was a group founded by Richard and Karen Carpenter in 1969. Though often referred to as "The Carpenters," their name on official releases and press materials was "Carpenters." During a period in the 1970's when louder and wilder rock was in great demand, Richard and Karen produced a distinctively soft musical style that made them among the best-selling music artists of all time. Carpenters have sold over 100,000,000 records worldwide to date. Carpenters won three Grammy Awards, had three #1 hits, five RIAA-certified platinum albums, and thirteen RIAA-certified gold singles.<br>
<br>
Originally from New Haven, Connecticut, their parents decided to move the family west to Los Angeles, California. Richard and Karen originally played jazz, with Karen having an interest in playing the drums. They were briefly known as Spectrum and then Carpenters, where they then recorded for a small label, Magic Lamp Records. In their move West, they met Lou Adler who introduced them to Herb Alpert, who signed them to his label, A&amp;M Records in 1969.<br>
<br>
Richard Carpenter arranged the songs and played the piano. Karen Carpenter, Richard's sister, sang and played the drums. The two were the one of the first to implement the overdubbing process with their voices, and Richard was the first to create the power ballad by adding a fuzz guitar part into a soft love ballad. While Richard penned compositions with writing partner, John Bettis, many of the duos' hits were written by others and some were cover versions of established hits for other artists, such as The Beatles and Motown's, The Marvelettes. Their 1973 album, "Now and Then." B-side consists of a 9-song medley of 60's hits recorded like a radio show.<br>
<br>
Carpenters' melodic pop, produced a record-breaking run of hits on the American Top 40 and Adult Contemporary charts, and they became leading sellers in the soft rock, easy listening and adult contemporary genres. Carpenters had three #1 singles on the Billboard Hot 100 and fifteen #1 hits on the Adult Contemporary Chart. In addition, they had twelve top 10 singles (including their #1 hits). To date, Carpenters' album and single sales total more than 100 million units.<br>
<br>
During their 14-year career, Carpenters recorded 11 albums, five of which contained top 10 singles ("Close To You," "Carpenters," "A Song For You," "Now &amp; Then" and "Horizon,") thirty-one singles, five television specials, and one short-lived television series. They toured the United States, United Kingdom, Japan, Australia, The Netherlands and Belgium. Their recording career ended with Karen's death in 1983 from cardiac arrest due to complications of anorexia nervosa. Extensive news coverage of the circumstances surrounding her death increased public awareness of the consequences of eating disorders.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Yesterday Once More (from Now &amp; Then) 3:57<br>
02. We've Only Just Begun (from Close to You) 3:04<br>
03. Superstar (from Carpenters) 3:46<br>
04. Rainy Days And Mondays (from Carpenters) 3:33<br>
05. Goodbye To Love (from A Song for You) 3:55<br>
06. I Believe You (from Made in America) 3:54<br>
07. It's Going To Take Some Time (from A Song for You) 3:00<br>
08. This Masquerade (from Now &amp; Then) 4:53<br>
09. Ticket To Ride (from Ticket to Ride) 4:10<br>
10. Top Of The World (from A Song for You) 3:01<br>
11. Only Yesterday (from Horizon) 3:37<br>
12. Hurting Each Other (from A Song for You) 2:47<br>
13. Please Mr. Postman (from Horizon) 2:47<br>
14. Merry Christmas, Darling (from Christmas Portrait) 3:05<br>
15. Sing (from Now &amp; Then) 3:18<br>
16. Bless The Beasts And Children (from A Song for You) 3:15<br>
17. I Won't Last A Day Without You (from A Song for You) 3:50<br>
18. Touch Me When We're Dancing (from Made in America) 3:18<br>
19. For All We Know (from Carpenters) 2:32<br>
20. (They Long To Be) Close To You (from Close to You) 3:40<br>
21. Calling Occupants Of Interplanetary Craft (from Passage) 7:07<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>