<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - AC/DC - Back In Black (1980) [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/ac-dc-back-in-black-1980-qobuz-hi-res-audio-24-bit-96-0khz.242778/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<span style="font-size: 22px"><b>AC/DC - Back In Black (1980) [QOBUZ HI-RES AUDIO 24-bit/96.0kHz]</b></span><br>
<br>
<img src="https://imgur.com/i88EyGq.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://imgur.com/i88EyGq.jpg" style=""><br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ALBUM REVIEW</b></span><br>
<br>
When an intoxicated Bon Scott died by choking on his own vomit in February, 1980, no one envisaged a future for AC/DC. However, the Anglo-Australian band succeeded in finding a replacement for their legendary lead singer. Brian Johnson from the band Geordie rose to the challenge against all odds and imposed a powerful, primarily high-pitched singing style which differed greatly from that of his predecessor. With its legendary black cover, <i>Back in Black</i> marked the birth of a new AC/DC and contains a series of incredible tracks. On guitar were the Young brothers (Malcolm with his Gretsch and Angus with his unstoppable Gibson SG), constantly trying to outdo each other’s genius both through the effectiveness of their riffs and the precision of their solos (notably on <i>Back in Black</i> and <i>You Shook Me All Night Long</i>). As well as pure AC/DC (<i>What Do You Do for Money Honey</i>), they give us some thick boogie with a ZZ Top twang (<i>Have a Drink on Me</i>), theatrical hard rock à la Led Zep (<i>Shake a Leg</i>), and let us not forget the ode to the God of Blues (<i>Rock and Roll Ain’t Noise Pollution</i>). Cliff Williams and Phil Rudd finish the job by providing the record with a concrete bassline and strong rhythm, doing so with great finesse. Upon the release of <i>Back in Black</i> on July 15th, 1980, fans were, without surprise, torn on the question of Brian Johnson. Could the band go on without Bon Scott? The record’s success and the world tour that followed quelled any debate and, forty years later, no one questions the decision for a second. With 50 million units sold, <i>Back in Black</i> is the second best-selling album of all time, just behind a certain <i>Thriller</i> by Michael Jackson…<br>
<br>
<span style="font-size: 18px"><b>ABOUT THE ALBUM</b></span><br>
<ul>
<li>1 disc(s) - 10 track(s)</li>
<li>Total length: 00:41:59</li>
</ul><ul>
<li>Main artists: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/interpreter/ac-dc/161143" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">AC/DC</a></li>
<li>Composer: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/composer/various-composers/573076" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Various Composers</a></li>
<li>Label: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/label/columbia/download-streaming-albums/4592" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Columbia</a></li>
<li>Genre: <a href="https://www.qobuz.com/us-en/genre/metal/download-streaming-albums" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Metal</a></li>
</ul><br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div><b>Password: musicasylum</b>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Mu$iC @$YLUM]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>