<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Helpdesk】[discussion] Paying for filtered instrumentals/acapellas/stems?]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/discussion-paying-for-filtered-instrumentals-acapellas-stems.231678/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
So I got into a bit of a youtube beef with a Russian in-my-view-scammer, who supposedly created his own AI filter, and proceeded to create a site where he charged people to download his REALLY crappy filtered instrumentals, acapellas &amp; stems.<br>
<br>
He would go as far as charge $40-50 USD for an instrumental album OR charge $20+ USD ongoing monthly subscription for merely a section (Instrumentals or Acapellas or Stems etc). He would upload anything and everything.<br>
<br>
All it took to take that trash down is a well-worded email to the platform host informing them off the mass illegal profiteering being committed by that scamming Russki.<br>
<br>
Now, I'm no hypocrite. I HAVE paid for material in the past, material I couldn't get anywhere else. But it was 100% legit from the studio, not some filtered trash like this.<br>
<br>
I also create my own filtered content (instrumentals &amp; acapellas). But I NEVER upload the raw filtered result! I use limiters and compressors &amp; dynamic plugins to boost the overall sound &amp; fill up those volume dips that remain behind where the vocals used to be. My subs love them, but I would never dream of charging them for a copy. That's just wrong.<br>
<br>
Then I hear his inferior trash and it turns me into Gordon Ramsay.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/Dp4k189.gif" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/Dp4k189.gif" style=""> <br>
<br>
On the other hand, there are sites like Splitter &amp; Lalal that charge for premium splitting or minutes, but this was on a whole 'nother scale.<br>
<br>
How do you feel about this?<br>
<br>
PS: I will not be mentioning the name of this person or his site, so don't bother asking. His site has been taken down anyway.
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[KingOfHell1661]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>