<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Instrumentals / Karaoke (lossless)】WAV - MUSIC SOFT / DJ SOFTWARE/SAMPLES/VST Plugins/Banks Of Sounds]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/music-soft-dj-software-samples-vst-plugins-banks-of-sounds.232577/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_1a361b34ba118cca.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_1a361b34ba118cca.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Mainroom House and; Vocal Essentials provides you with a collection of top tier sounds that will help you produce tracks in line with the current mainstream house trends. This pack includes a range of epic instrumental samples as well as a collection of breathtaking female vocals. In short, this pack includes all the essentials for you to produce a complete festival or radio-ready track that will get anyone up on their feet!<br>
<br>
Expect to find nothing less than cool synth riffs, rumbling bass samples, groovy drums and much much more…Within this release are over 450 samples designed to the highest standard, all with the producer in mind. Furthermore, this release includes 6 highly detailed songstarters construction kits fully broken down into stems, to give you an in-depth look into how these Mainroom House tracks are put together.<br>
<br>
Load up your sample library now with this essential collection of house and vocal samples! We are Sample Tools by Cr2 and this is… Mainroom House and; Vocal Essentials<br>
<br>
467 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/E1ztkka" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/E1ztkka</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/au7XCW" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Sample Tools by Cr2 Mainroom House and Vocal Essentials.rar</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_9cb927e3da76b9e2.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_9cb927e3da76b9e2.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
Introducing the ultimate sample pack for those who love creating edgy and atmospheric tracks with sinister arpeggios, dance floor rumbling baselines, and progressive rhythms. Say hello to "Melodic Techno and; Progressive Essentials" - the perfect tool kit to unleash your creativity and take your music to the next level.<br>
<br>
<br>
Featuring meticulously crafted loops and one-shots, this pack is a one-stop-shop for creating trending melodic techno and progressive tracks. With over 700+ Mb of high-quality samples, you'll find everything you need to produce modern club tracks in the style of some of the most respected electronic music artists in the world, including CamelPhat, ARTBAT, Space Motion, and many more.<br>
<br>
Inside, you'll discover a wide range of expertly crafted loops, including 19 atmosphere and texture loops, 20 bass loops, 17 drum loops (split into kick, hats, percussion, and snare variations), 24 FX loops, 62 melodic loops, and 21 melodic construction kits. In addition, there are 11 bass one-shots, 11 claps, 10 cymbals, 22 hats, 26 kicks, 22 snares, 10 FX one-shots, 20 percussion samples, and 10 synth shots.<br>
<br>
The loops are professionally recorded and processed to deliver the highest quality sound possible, with each element carefully designed to give your productions a modern and unique sound. The one-shots, on the other hand, give you the freedom to create your own drum and synth sounds, allowing you to tailor your tracks to your exact needs.<br>
<br>
Whether you're a seasoned producer, DJ, or electronic music enthusiast, "Melodic Techno and; Progressive Essentials" provides all the tools you need to create club-ready tracks that will leave your audience wanting more. From atmospheric synths and driving basslines to punchy drums and intricate percussion, this pack has it all. So why not elevate your music game and add this pack to your collection today?<br>
<br>
459 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/dez1ZDZ" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/dez1ZDZ</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/051hrk" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Freshly Squeezed Samples Melodic Techno and Progressive Essentials.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_6288b19f1b352baf.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_6288b19f1b352baf.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Inspired by the likes of Meduza, ZHU, Joel Corry, and Selected producers, this production suite includes four sound packs that provide all the necessary tools to help you create professional-sounding Deep Melodic House tracks.<br>
<br>
Here are the packs included in this bundle. Feel free to visit their pages for more info and audio previews:<br>
<br>
<br>
You can expect to find four packs in this pro bundle:<br>
<br>
Serum presets bank<br>
Songwriting samples &amp; midis<br>
Drums sample pack<br>
FX sample pack<br>
A complete toolset to produce pro sounding tracks.<br>
<br>
These bundles are a great way to get a variety of sounds at a lower price.<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/KPGz" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/KPGz</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/wIiI2i" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - FVII Music Deep House Pro.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_549d7ecbbe217cb9.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_549d7ecbbe217cb9.png" style=""><br>
<br>
The 'Sounds' series by Gio Israel is a window to the worlds' last remaining ancient musical traditions of our time.<br>
<br>
The source of Andalusian music is attributed to legendary Persian musician - Ali Iben Nafiaa (AKA "ZRIAB"). Migrating from Syria to the south of Spain (Andalusia) Zriab created 24 musical themes (called "Nubot"), each Nuba represented a different hour in the day.<br>
<br>
<br>
This new musical tradition then expended to several larger musical traditions of Morocco, Algeria, Tunisia and Libya, as well as been influenced by North African music and style.<br>
<br>
The ancient melodies have been managed to survive the test of time due to religious use and mostly through old Jewish communities that have used this types of melodies in their prayers as means to carry their oral traditions, the same that can be heard in old synagogs till this very day.<br>
<br>
This series was recorded by musician and composer Gilad Hazan, a respected scholar of Andalusian Music.<br>
<br>
222 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/cRzzT5l" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/cRzzT5l</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/4f9Sfl" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Gio Israel Andalusian Oud Vol. 1.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_d6e1ddca9c346d18.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_d6e1ddca9c346d18.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Introducing Tech EDM Groover by Incognet and Singomakers, a cutting-edge sample pack designed to ignite your productions with the electrifying energy of the future rave genre. Packed with a massive 1.5 GB of high-quality content, this expansive collection offers an array of one-shots, loops, MIDI files, and presets that will propel your tracks to new heights.<br>
<br>
Within this pack, you will find 20 expertly crafted construction kits, each comprising a wealth of sonic elements meticulously designed to capture the essence of the modern tech house and clubby EDM sound. With a huge number of WAV loops at your disposal, including pulsating basslines, mesmerising synths, punchy drums, dynamic fills, atmospheric FX, and various other elements, you'll have a killer sound palette to create intricate, dancefloor-shaking compositions.<br>
<br>
This is a must-have collection for producers seeking to dive into the thrilling world of modern tech house, future rave, and groovy EDM music. Providing all the essential tools needed to craft powerful &amp; energetic tracks, prepare to blast your way through dancefloors around the globe with the help of Incognet and Singomakers!<br>
<br>
1.5 GB<br>
24-Bit Samples<br>
20 Construction Kits<br>
291 Kit Loops (Bass, Synth, Drums, Fills, FX)<br>
46 Kit MIDI Files<br>
22 Bass Loops<br>
42 Synth Loops<br>
47 Drum Loops<br>
30 Drum Fills &amp; Build-Ups<br>
27 Vocals<br>
67 Serum Presets<br>
17 Sylenth Presets<br>
70 Total One-Shots<br>
18 Clap One-Shots<br>
5 Hi-Hat One-Shots<br>
33 Kick One-Shots<br>
10 Synth One-Shots<br>
4 Tom One-Shots<br>
22 SFX<br>
+ Promo &amp; Discount Folder<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/5jHjKz4" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/5jHjKz4</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/1vI4wd" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Singomakers Tech EDM Groover by Incognet.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_a18fb65c5ca48856.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_a18fb65c5ca48856.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Embark on a captivating journey into the heart of techno realms with HY2ROGEN's latest masterpiece: Melodic Techno Rawness. Dive headfirst into a vast ocean of sound, where inspiration knows no bounds. This colossal 1.95 GB sample pack is your gateway to crafting hypnotic melodic techno tracks that will leave listeners in awe.<br>
<br>
Immerse yourself in the genius of genre masters like Tale Of Us, Adriatique, Massano, Innellea, Artbat, and Anyma, and draw from the legacy of acclaimed labels such as Afterlife, Anjunadeep, Crosstown Rebels, and Upperground. Melodic Techno Rawness isn't just a sample pack; it's an invitation to embark on a sonic odyssey. Let your imagination run wild, create hypnotic grooves, and craft the melodic techno tracks you've always dreamed of. Start your journey today with the definitive toolkit for melodic techno and deep tech producers. Don't just follow the trends; set them!<br>
<br>
With 30 meticulously crafted song-starters, neatly organised into content folders, you'll find the perfect balance between construction kits and multi-content, providing the ultimate creative freedom. We've left no stone unturned, offering you a whopping 132 Serum synth presets, ensuring that you can adapt and customise these melodic marvels to your unique vision. Tailor your tracks with an array of melodic techno flavours found in 20 multi-content folders. Mix and match between arp loops, bass loops, bonus vocals, clap loops, combi mix loops, full drum loops, sound effects, hat loops, kick loops, lead loops, one-shots, pad loops, percussion loops, pluck loops, ride loops, shaker loops, snare loops, string loops, synth loops, and top loops to create endlessly fascinating compositions. Craft your sonic landscapes with the confidence that every element is designed to shine at a captivating 126 BPM.<br>
<br>
What you get is 1.95 GB of content served up as 1,000 total files comprised of 708 WAV files, 134 MIDI files (bass &amp; synths), 26 sampler patches (EXS, Kontakt) and 132 Xfer Serum presets. Everything is key and tempo (126 BPM) labelled where applicable, and the audio files are delivered at a quality of 24-bit/44.1kHz. The content has been exported as 4-8 bars long with dry &amp; wet versions where applicable, as this has been our tradition for many years, and we think it keeps the door open for more flexibility.<br>
<br>
Our sound design is masterfully simple, clean, and tightly engineered, but with one goal in mind: to make an unforgettable impact on your audience. Whether you're delving into the WAV loops, one-shots, MIDI files, presets, or sampler patches, every component is designed to elevate your production to new heights.<br>
<br>
Melodic Techno Rawness is your secret weapon for staying ahead of the musical curve. Dive into the depths of one of the hottest sounds in the industry right now. Unleash your creativity without bounds, knowing that everything in this pack is royalty-free and ready for release without the hassle of additional clearances.<br>
<br>
Please note: the audio demo has been processed to sound loud, compressed and uniform. The individual sounds do not contain the same level of heavy processing and have been left as clean as possible to find their way into any project. All the sounds presented in the audio demo are available in this sample pack. Everything is royalty-free!<br>
<br>
Grab a copy today to upgrade your melodic techno to new dimensions of sonic brilliance!<br>
<br>
HY2ROGEN: NEXT-GENERATION SOUNDS<br>
<br>
Work smarter, make music faster!<br>
<br>
1.95 GB24-Bit / 44.1kHz WAV<br>
1,000 Total Files<br>
708 WAV Files<br>
134 MIDI Files<br>
132 Xfer Serum Presets (For All Synth Sounds)<br>
26 Sampler Patches (EXS &amp; Kontakt)<br>
30 Track-Starters<br>
20 Multi-Content Folders<br>
4-8 Bars Long Exports<br>
Dry &amp; Wet Versions For Bass &amp; Synth Loops<br>
236 One-Shots (Drums &amp; Synths)<br>
73 Bass Loops<br>
40 Synth Loops<br>
37 Hat Loops<br>
31 Lead Loops<br>
31 Pad Loops<br>
30 Combi Mix Loops<br>
30 Kick Loops<br>
28 Full Drum Loops<br>
28 Pluck Loops<br>
27 Top Loops<br>
24 Misc Loops<br>
22 Arp Loops<br>
15 Clap Loops<br>
15 Sound Effects<br>
12 Bonus Vocals<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/c0Le" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/c0Le</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/rWscI2" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - HY2ROGEN Melodic Techno Rawness.rar</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[specialfordjs]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Afterlife Records 2016 - 2023 (77 releases), [FLAC]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/afterlife-records-2016-2023-77-releases-flac.232578/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_f1b434120036f96d.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_f1b434120036f96d.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
Get ready to embark on an extraordinary musical journey with this cutting-edge sample pack, designed to elevate your productions to new heights and captivate dancefloors worldwide, titled Tech House Vocal Anthems.<br>
<br>
<br>
HY2ROGEN unleashes the power of vocals which have been meticulously crafted to be the heartbeat of your next tech house masterpiece and serve as a spark of creative brilliance. These carefully curated vocals have been ingeniously woven into 10 captivating song-starter kits, where loops, one-shots, synth presets, and MIDI files come together in perfect harmony, igniting the fire of your imagination.<br>
<br>
Equipped with 519 MB of content, every element in this pack has been designed to inspire your next chart-topping hit. Our punchy, smacking and carefully crafted drum loops, bass loops, synth loops, effects, instrument loops, and of course the tantalising vocals are all locked in at a compelling 126 BPM, ensuring seamless compatibility and effortless fusion with your existing projects or future creative visions. In the pursuit of perfection, we've also prepared dry and wet versions of the vocals and synths, allowing you complete control over the depth and texture of your productions. For the ultimate personalisation experience, dive into the world of Serum, Sylenth, and Vital with our included synth presets, empowering you to unleash your wildest creative instincts and take these track-starters further. You also get additional bonus vocals and sound effects on the house - even more goodies to play with!<br>
<br>
Designed with a focus on simplicity, clarity, and tight sound design, Tech House Vocal Anthems guarantees maximum sonic impact. Prepare for thunderous drops, groove-infused beats, and hypnotic melodies to keep your audience dancing until the break of dawn. This pack encapsulates the hottest trending sounds, ensuring that your creations resonate with the spirit of this thrilling genre. The possibilities are limitless with this royalty-free treasure trove. Each idea comes as standard with a small pre-drop section, giving your tracks an irresistible edge. Craft these sonic gems into fully blown hit tracks that are primed for release, propelling you into the stratosphere of success.<br>
<br>
What you get is 519 MB of content served up as 344 total files comprised of 27 WAV files (one-shots &amp; loops), 26 MIDI files, 15 sampler patches, and 30 synth presets. Check out the full specifications below for more details. Everything is key and tempo labelled (126 BPM) where applicable. Plus, the audio files are delivered at a quality of 24-bit/44.1kHz. The content has been exported as 4-8 bar long loops with dry and wet versions where applicable, as this has been our tradition for many years, and we think it keeps the door open for more production flexibility.<br>
<br>
Step into a realm of sonic wonder with Tech House Vocal Anthems from HY2ROGEN. Elevate your productions with original vocals and embrace the seamless fusion of extraordinary musical elements. Light the fuse and ignite the dancefloor with captivating rhythms and melodies. The future of tech house is at your fingertips. Are you ready to make history?<br>
<br>
Please note: the audio demo has been processed to sound loud, compressed and uniform. The individual sounds do not contain the same level of heavy processing and have been left as clean as possible to find their way into any project. All the sounds presented in the audio demo are available in this sample pack.<br>
<br>
Everything is royalty-free!<br>
<br>
Grab a copy today and upgrade your tech house game!<br>
<br>
HY2ROGEN: NEXT-GENERATION SOUNDS<br>
<br>
Work smarter, make music faster!<br>
<br>
519 MB<br>
24-Bit / 44.1kHz WAV<br>
10 Construction Kits<br>
344 Total Files<br>
273 Total WAV Files<br>
30 Xfer Serum Presets<br>
26 MIDI Files<br>
15 Sampler Patches (EXS, Kontakt, Halion)<br>
4-8 Bar Long Exports<br>
Dry &amp; Wet Melodic Loops<br>
10 Demo Mixes<br>
49 Synth Loops<br>
44 Vocal Loops<br>
44 Bass Loops<br>
39 Drum Loops<br>
19 Sound Effects<br>
6 Piano Loops<br>
9 Bonus Sound Effects<br>
5 Extra Vocals<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/ttNm" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/ttNm</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/L5K2vs" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - HY2ROGEN Tech House Vocal Anthems.rar</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_1aab3f72e7069d77.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_1aab3f72e7069d77.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Introducing the ultimate house music sample pack! Meticulously crafted to embody the sounds and vibes of renowned record labels such as Toolroom Records, CR2, Insomniac, Defected, Hot Creations, FFRR, and Glasgow Underground. With a massive size of 1.41 GB, this pack offers an expansive collection of 21 high-quality 24-bit WAV kits and bonus content too – set to elevate your productions to new heights.<br>
<br>
Spanning across various tempos, this pack delivers an extensive range of house music essentials, perfectly suited for tracks ranging from the laid-back grooves of 123 BPM to the energetic rhythms of 127 BPM. Whether you're crafting deep house, tech house, or classic house anthems, the diverse BPM selection ensures versatility and flexibility in your productions.<br>
<br>
Featuring 21 meticulously designed construction kits, this pack provides a wealth of inspiration to kick-start your creativity. Kits contain a curated selection of 428 WAV loops including mesmerising basslines, captivating synths, punchy drums, dynamic fills, atmospheric FX, and impactful one-shots. Additionally, MIDI files are included, allowing you to customise and expand upon the provided loops, while Serum presets provide further sound design possibilities.<br>
<br>
With this comprehensive sample pack, you'll have everything you need to create professional-grade house tracks that resonate with the iconic sound of leading labels in the scene.<br>
<br>
Let your creativity soar within the dynamic world This Is House by Incognet!<br>
<br>
1.41 GB<br>
24-Bit Samples<br>
21 Construction Kits<br>
428 WAV Loops (Inc. Bass/Synth/Drums/FX)<br>
28 MIDI Files<br>
22 Bass Loops<br>
31 Synth Loops<br>
36 Drum &amp; Top Loops<br>
20 Xfer Serum Presets<br>
11 SFX<br>
139 Total One-Shots<br>
12 Clap One-Shots<br>
21 Hi-Hat One-Shots<br>
28 Kick One-Shots<br>
17 Percussion One-Shots<br>
61 Synth One-Shots<br>
+ Promo &amp; Discount Folder<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/rsNU" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/rsNU</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/J8VvjU" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Singomakers This Is House by Incognet.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_21aaf5d8d695aee3.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_21aaf5d8d695aee3.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
HY2ROGEN is proud to introduce Drum &amp; Bass Liquidation, a cutting-edge sample pack that takes you on a special journey through the vibrant and soulful world of liquid drum &amp; bass. Created with meticulous attention to detail, this pack carries a diverse range of expertly crafted sounds that will elevate your productions to new heights.<br>
<br>
Drawing inspiration from the works of renowned artists such as Calibre, Netsky, Nusance &amp; Fyber, Logistics, and Hybrid Minds, this sound collection captures the essence of their signature styles while infusing these with our own fresh and innovative elements. Immerse yourself in the sublime melodies, rolling and Reese basslines, vocal choppers and intricately designed drum patterns that have made these artists legends in the genre.<br>
<br>
Inside this remarkable collection, you'll find a wide selection of tools that include punchy drum loops soaked in syncopated rhythmic patterns and broken down to the very last element, lush atmospheric pads and ethereal textures, a proper bass section comprised of warm and meaty rolling basslines, an impressive assortment of melodic loops that includes enchanting piano progressions, soaring synth leads, and hypnotic arpeggios, topped off with mandatory fills &amp; effects and the cherry on top, vocal loops!<br>
<br>
Drum &amp; Bass Liquidation comes as standard in 16 main content folders (atmo loops, bass loops, clap &amp; snare loops, combi loops, fills, full drum loops, effects, hat loops, kick loops, one-shots, percussion loops, piano loops, ride loops, synth loops, top loops, vocal loops). We cannot forget to mention the synth presets for Serum and MIDI files that will come in handy in customising the included sounds and adding a touch of magic to your compositions.<br>
<br>
What you get is 659 MB of content broken down into 16 main folders holding 501 WAV files. Everything is key and tempo (170-176 BPM) labelled where applicable, and the audio files are delivered at a quality of 24-bit/44.1kHz. The content has been exported as 4-8 bar long loops along with dry &amp; wet versions where applicable, as this has been our tradition for many years, and we think it keeps the door open for more flexibility.<br>
<br>
Whether you're a seasoned producer or just starting your musical journey, Drum &amp; Bass Liquidation is an indispensable tool that will take your productions to the next level. Unleash the power of liquid drum &amp; bass and let the inspiration flow through your veins. Get ready to conquer the airwaves and captivate your audience with this exceptional sample pack.<br>
<br>
Please note: the audio demo has been processed to sound loud, compressed and uniform. The individual sounds do not contain the same level of heavy processing and have been left as clean as possible to find their way into any project. All the sounds presented in the audio demo are available in this sample pack.<br>
<br>
Grab a copy today and upgrade your liquid drum &amp; bass game!<br>
<br>
HY2ROGEN: NEXT-GENERATION SOUNDS<br>
<br>
Work smarter, make music faster!<br>
<br>
659 MB<br>
24-Bit / 44.1kHz WAV<br>
661 Total Files<br>
501 WAV Files<br>
103 MIDI Files<br>
30 Xfer Serum Presets<br>
27 Sampler Patches (EXS, Kontakt, Halion)<br>
4-8 Bar Long Loops<br>
Dry &amp; Wet Exports<br>
190 Total One-Shots<br>
69 Synth Loops<br>
29 Bass Loops<br>
24 Combi Synth Loops (Bass &amp; Synth)<br>
24 Vocal Loops<br>
21 Clap &amp; Snare Loops<br>
20 Full Drum Loops<br>
20 Sound Effects<br>
20 Top Loops<br>
20 Hat Loops<br>
20 Kick Loops<br>
6 Ride Loops<br>
16 Piano Loops<br>
5 Atmo Loops<br>
5 Drum Builds<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/HSBk" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/HSBk</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/6S65F4" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - HY2ROGEN Drum &amp; Bass Liquidation.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_7702758d7a7183b4.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_7702758d7a7183b4.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
Introducing the New Era Melodic Techno sample pack - an avant-garde sonic voyage that propels your productions into uncharted musical territories. Immerse yourself in a symphony of intricate rhythms, ethereal melodies, and cutting-edge textures, meticulously crafted to redefine the boundaries of modern electronic music.<br>
<br>
<br>
Dive into a collection of meticulously designed sounds and synth patches, handpicked to fuel your creativity and spark new dimensions in your melodic techno creations. This sample pack encapsulates the essence of the genre's evolution, merging timeless elements with futuristic sonic landscapes.<br>
<br>
Inspired by recent melodic techno tunes by artists like Lane 8, Artbat, Volen Sentir, Sebastien Leger, Gorje Hewek, Marsh, Guy J, Ben Böhmer, Monolink, WhoMadeWho, Tim Green, and many more!<br>
<br>
And one more thing… Singomakers have provided a promo/discount folder with links to free sample packs and codes for their amazing plugins - Kick Tweak, Fatmaker, Magic Stereo, Phat Booster, and Crystal EQ available HERE. These have been used by many a-list producers and sound designers!<br>
<br>
New Era Melodic Techno is your catalyst for innovation - don’t miss it.<br>
<br>
Check out the demo and grab your copy ASAP!<br>
<br>
873 MB<br>
24-Bit Samples<br>
7 Construction Kits<br>
143 Kit Loops (Bass, Synth, Drums, FX, Fills)<br>
21 Kit MIDI Files<br>
17 Bass Loops<br>
28 Drum Loops (Tops, Fills, Claps)<br>
4 FX Loops<br>
18 Synth Loops<br>
9 Clap One-Shots<br>
11 Kick One-Shots<br>
1 Snare One-Shots<br>
36 VST Synth Presets (6 Massive &amp; 30 Serum)<br>
+ Promo &amp; Discount Folder<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/iNZ1td" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/iNZ1td</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/t4knPl" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Singomakers New Era Melodic Techno.rar</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<br>
Sad Girl Sex Tapes is a collection of over 200 vocal samples, expertly crafted and curated to suit a wide range of sonic possibilities. Expect to find lush vocal pads to crisp accapella hooks, instrumental song starters and spoken word sound bites. Sad Girl Sex Tapes is a versatile sample pack that can be used for a variety of genres, including Sad Girl Pop, Dream Pop, R&amp;B, Rap, Electronic Dance, and Soul. The samples are royalty-free and tempo-synced for ease of use.<br>
<br>
<br>
The samples were recorded and engineered by Dylan Wood at Sound Factory studio in Los Angeles using a variety of vintage and modern gear, including the Electro-Voice 664 for the vintage textures, and the Manley Gold for that modern, clear, sparkling fidelity. The warm and wide reverb was created using Sound Factories analogue plate reverb.<br>
<br>
As a producer and a songwriter, Nylo curated the samples from the mindset of creation and momentum, generating sounds that can be the first drop of paint on an empty musical canvas or lyrics to guide a creator into an idea just under the surface. The background vocal arrangements are meant to push a track that's almost there over the finish line, and the vocal adlibs and one-shots can be re-sampled and turned into something entirely new or used as is, to give each song that much needed signature sample.<br>
<br>
Nylo is a platinum artist/producer and early pioneer in the downtempo movement, blending soul, R&amp;B, and electronica. Collaborations include artists like Zhu, G-Eazy, Majid Jordan, and Mac Miller, and outside of the studio she's toured the world as a musical director and multi-instrumentalist for artists like Yuna, Sohn, and many more.<br>
<br>
224 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/iSw9SWF" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/iSw9SWF</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/167cfu" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Jammcard Samples Nylo Sad Girl Sex Tapes Vocal Toolkit WAV.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_4a1ec6b7001c216c.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_4a1ec6b7001c216c.png" style=""><br>
<br>
If you've used NI's Guitar Rig in the past, you already know what a powerful tool it is for guitar and bass. In this Guitar Rig 7 Pro video course, amp sim expert Gary Hiebner gives you an in-depth video manual with examples of everything Guitar Rig 7 Pro, covering all the bases, from all the amp and cabinet models and effects to all the other useful tools such as the new Signal Flow sidebar, MIDI functionality, the new Loop Machine Pro, and much more! By the end of the Guitar Rig 7 Pro course, you'll have a firm grasp on everything this tone powerhouse can do and will be ready to start getting killer sounds right away! These videos are designed for new Guitar Rig 7 Pro users.<br>
<br>
Gary begins by welcoming you to the course and explaining how to set up your audio interface to properly interface with Guitar Rig 7 Pro. You'll then learn the lay of the land with a tour of the interface and a demonstration of how to use the Browser to try out presets, save changes, etc. Then Gary covers the new Signal Flow sidebar view, which allows you to quickly get a complete view of your signal chain and make changes - from simple to complex - quickly and easily.<br>
<br>
Next, Gary dives into the amp components, where you'll see how to tweak parameters like gain, EQ, etc. and also see how to select different cabinets for different tones. Learn also how to load various cabinet impulse responses for even more tonal variation and hear how NI's ICM technology faithfully recreates the sound of coveted vintage gear.<br>
<br>
This only scratches the surface, and there's much more to come, including tutorials dedicated to each type of effect (overdrive, distortion/fuzz, delays/reverbs, modulation, compression, pitch effects, and more), and new lo-fi effects Tape Wobble, Vintage Vibrato, and Noise Machine, the new Loop Machine Pro (looper with advanced features for use in live settings), Tools (helpful for setting up various signal and processing chains), macro assignment, MIDI Learn (for control of effects like wah via an external MIDI controller), and more! To close out the course, Gary shows you how to create several different tones from scratch: vintage clean, dirty overdriven, modern metal, Swedish metal, and more!<br>
<br>
Native Instruments has really thrown down the gauntlet with Guitar Rig 7 Pro, and this course is the quickest way to fully grasp all it can do. With plenty of audio demonstrations, you'll quickly realize how amazing this plug-in truly is when it comes to easily getting the perfect tone for guitar or bass. Check out the individual Guitar Rig 7 Pro video tutorial descriptions for more info and ideas on how you can integrate it into your own workflow for your very next production. Your perfect tone awaits... watch "Guitar Rig 7 Pro Explained®" today!<br>
<br>
What You Will Learn:<br>
<br>
-How to tweak amp parameters and select various cabinets for tonal variation, including impulse response cabinets<br>
<br>
-Detailed explanation of all types of effects (distortion, reverb, delay, modulation, compression, etc.)<br>
<br>
-How to create full guitar arrangements in the studio and on the stage with the new Loop Machine Pro<br>
<br>
-Assigning macros to select parameters for easy, fast tweaking of your most commonly used elements<br>
<br>
-And much more!<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/LHKSUK" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/LHKSUK</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/sDwQRd" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Groove3 Guitar Rig 7 Pro Explained.rar</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[specialfordjs]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Actresses】Ulrike Butz -Muschimaus mag's grad heraus (1973) 720p]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/ulrike-butz-muschimaus-mags-grad-heraus-1973-720p.232579/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_cfb824ddfcb8bdaf.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_cfb824ddfcb8bdaf.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Soulmates - Vintage Classics’ is a curated collection of original soul samples, vintage vocals, live instrument loops, and vinyl cut melodics. Paying tribute to the classic soul records that have shaped hip-hop and continue to inspire. For the crate diggers, vinyl lovers, and modern producers searching for rare gems. Plus select cuts, flipped and resampled into chopped loops, dripping in vinyl and tape nostalgia. Proudly presented by 91Vocals in collaboration with Arthouse Acoustics.<br>
<br>
<br>
This collection builds on the foundations of extensive composition, arrangement, and recording by a team of experienced professional musicians inspired by the rich history of soul music. Arthouse Acoustics used vintage mics and analog preamps to capture live performances and emulate the warmth and character of true-to-era production techniques. Includes full melodic stacks, instrument stems, vocal stacks, resampled loops, and one-shots - all original and royalty-free.<br>
<br>
Loops<br>
24 Melodic Stacks<br>
23 Melodic Stacks with Vocals<br>
16 Resampled Melodic Stacks<br>
48 Vintage Vocal Hooks (including Stacks)<br>
10 Vinyl Loops<br>
34 Vinyl Cut Loops<br>
23 Bass Guitar Loops<br>
27 Electric Guitar Loops<br>
20 Vintage Piano Loops<br>
17 Vintage Strings Loops<br>
16 Vintage Trumpet Loops<br>
<br>
One Shots<br>
12 Melodic Stack Stabs<br>
7 Melodic Stack Phrases<br>
10 Instrument One Shots<br>
5 Vocal One Shots<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/gRZNYMG" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/gRZNYMG</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/1OmmIG" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - 91Vocals Soulmates Vintage Classics WAV.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_19b5b4c6114a5c55.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_19b5b4c6114a5c55.png" style=""><br>
<br>
India born, California raised songstress Zoya brings her unique brand of catchy pop to VOX, delivering an exciting collection of vocal loops including melodically inspiring top-line hooks and phrases (both as wet and dry samples), processed vocoders, chopped, adlibs and one shot vocal FX, pitched and spoken word samples.<br>
<br>
Zoya’s music has been recognised by AR Rahman and The Chainsmokers, featured Grammy Award Winning rapper ‘Jack Harlow’ on her debut album, works closely with Mark Milan (Lady Gaga) and Chuck Inglish (Chance the Rapper) and has supported tours with the likes of Kawehi, Natty, Lucy Rose, Madame Gandhi, Youngr, Submotion Orchestra, Bloc Party, Clean Bandit and Martin Garrix. It is fair therefore to say that Zoya’s impressive impact on popular music is far reaching and shows no signs of slowing down. Find every vocal gem you need to write your next hit in this Zoya Vocal Pack. As described in our Terms of Use, you may not use Zoya’s name, image or likeness without Zoya’s express permission.<br>
<br>
219 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/G37LU" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/G37LU</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/dFyAaW" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - VOX Zoya Vocal Pack.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_89700ac56f5c5247.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_89700ac56f5c5247.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Take a pinch of Ariana Grande vocal melodies, a dash of Lady Gaga style production and a squeeze of Katy Perry’s iconically catchy toplines and you have all the ingredients of ‘Divine Vocal Pop’. Inspired by some of contemporary music’s most gifted and influential pop Queens, this huge collection of vocal hooks, adlibs and phrases have been meticulously recorded offering lead vocal toplines, fresh adlib textures and fully arranged vocal harmony layers in both wet and dry production, serving ultimate pop perfection.<br>
<br>
Engineered at our very own Sound Factory studios in Westlake, Los Angeles by grammy nominated vocal producer Simone Torres (@iamsimonetorres) who has worked with the likes of Chloe, Cardi B and Kelly Rowland; we recorded the stunning vocals of Lia Farrington (@liafarrington) produced by prolific modern pop producer John McLucas (@john_mclucas). All parts of this carefully curated team of Pop royalty and talent has resulted in a premium tier selection of crystal clear and iconic vocal samples to level up your productions. Create your next hit with Divine Vocal Pop today.<br>
<br>
234 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/yoOIj" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/yoOIj</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/YlMcep" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - VOX Divine Vocal Pop.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_dcd62d8ef38e6a75.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_dcd62d8ef38e6a75.png" style=""><br>
<br>
The maak producers team that conquered the beats, song and service market for artists and musicians are expanding their boundaries right now to introduce to your attention the first signature "Carnaval" Sample Pack, which includes 328 unique loops and 27 unique sound sets.<br>
<br>
<br>
maak® - universe for artists, creators, bloggers and brands. The maak® ecosystem includes a song, beat and cover store, digital goods and NFT, recording studio, sound producers, ghostwriters and sound engineers team, distribution and graphic design services, marketing and advertising, promotion, targeting services, educational platform and more.<br>
<br>
328 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/ckn6ad" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/ckn6ad</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/dsddYm" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - TrakTrain maak - Carnaval.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_c9f8b89322a94d57.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_c9f8b89322a94d57.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Africana 2’ is part 2 of a soulful fusion of classic Afrobeat sauce and modern amapiano groove. Africana 2 utilises real instruments alongside electronic synthesis. The funky rhythms and musical excellence are enough to make any dance floor pulsate.<br>
<br>
This pack will give you the opportunity to understand how afrobeats music is made on a deeper level by piecing each deconstructed layer together, sample by sample.<br>
<br>
From emotive and; fun guitar chord progressions to soulful synth melodies, this pack covers a wide array of afrobeat ideas and compositions. There is an eclectic mixture of sounds and instruments throughout the pack, all sure to inspire your next beat.<br>
<br>
If you enjoy this library, make sure to check out ‘Africana’.<br>
<br>
194 Samples<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/lR8G" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/lR8G</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/uJzGXb" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Origin Sound AFRICANA 2.rar</a><br>
<br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_bfba0acbfdfab09e.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_bfba0acbfdfab09e.png" style=""><br>
<br>
<br>
SUITABLE ACROSS GENRES LIKE POP, EDM, TECH HOUSE, TRANCE, HARDSTYLE, HIP-HOP, R&amp;B AND MANY OTHERS<br>
<br>
ABOUT THE PACK:<br>
<br>
<br>
Premium Vocals is a dynamic collection featuring hooks, backing vocals, chops, adlibs, and ambiences. Elevate your tracks across genres like Pop, EDM, Tech House, Trance, Hardstyle, Hip-Hop, and R&amp;B with authentic human essence.<br>
Crafted in collaboration with skilled female vocalists, each element has been carefully captured and refined by our production experts.<br>
<br>
Explore fresh studio acapellas and adlibs, meticulously categorized by both bpm and keys. Use them as a creative resource for chopping, resampling, or drop them right into your mix. All elements are original and Royalty Free.<br>
<br>
Plus, enjoy bonus stems from 3 demos, igniting your creativity instantly.<br>
<br>
THE PACK INCLUDES:<br>
<br>
202 Samples (974mb)<br>
25 DRY Hooks<br>
25 WET Hooks<br>
25 Backing Vocals<br>
25 Vocal Chops<br>
20 DRY Adlibs<br>
20 WET Adlibs<br>
15 Ambiences<br>
47 Bonus samples.<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/nTlOfdz" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/nTlOfdz</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/Aphq2b" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Ghost Producer Edm EDM Premium Vocals.rar</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://imgbb.com/" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><img src="https://i.ibb.co/s3qYyFr/dr-thumb-minimal-house-1689349004.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.ibb.co/s3qYyFr/dr-thumb-minimal-house-1689349004.jpg"></a><br>
<br>
Vocals are one of the most important elements of any music, as they are often where the epicentre of expression in a track is located. When it comes to electronic music, this is perhaps even more true, as they provide the human connection to sounds that could otherwise feel cold and lifeless. This philosophy pertains strongly to the music of D.Ramirez, the magisterial DJ and producer from Sheffield who brings his vocal hook prowess to an action-packed series of courses that cover seven electronic genres. In this course, he dives deep into vocal hooks within the Tech House genre.<br>
<br>
D.Ramirez is a bona fide star whose music has taken him to every corner of the globe in a sparkling career that has seen him operating at full throttle for over twenty years. He's manned the ones and twos in some the worlds' best clubs from Space &amp; Cream Ibiza, Womb in Tokyo and Avalon in LA; and dropped iconic sets at festivals like Glastonbury, Global Gathering and Australia Day in Sydney. Initially known for almost single-handedly coining the famed electrohouse sound, D.Ramirez has moved seamlessly into deep house and techno stylings in the last decade, and his ability to flip an acapella into a chart-topping vocal are unparalleled.<br>
<br>
In this course, D.Ramirez teaches you everything you need to know to find and deploy acapellas to create earworm vocal hooks in your electronic productions. You'll learn the ins and outs of modern sampling techniques, using content platforms like YouTube as well as royalty-free sample subscription services like Splice. Never one to do things by halves, D.Ramirez breaks down the finer points of arrangement, editing and effects processing.<br>
<br>
D.Ramirez production chops have led to him collecting accolades from the likes of DJ Magazine (best producer and best remix), iDJ (player of the year) and even an Ivor Novello nomination for his remix of Bodyrox 'Yeah Yeah'. He's even been on Top of the Pops! All of these accolades only confirm the high regard D.Ramirez is held in in the dance music community, which makes him the ideal instructor for this unmissable vocal hooks masterclass. Whether you want to know how to find the best acapellas out there today, or how to write, record and refine original vocals, this course is the one for you!<br>
<br>
Chapters (all of them compacted in one MP4 file) :<br>
<br>
Chapter 0: Tech House Intro<br>
Chapter 1: YouTube Acapellas<br>
Chapter 2: Search Keywords<br>
Chapter 3: Sourcing and Sampling<br>
Chapter 4: Editing Samples in Ableton<br>
Chapter 5: Further Editing<br>
Chapter 6: Building the Arrangement<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/eWUB1" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/eWUB1</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/eVN3gX" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - FaderPro Vocal Hooks Tech House w D.Ramirez.rar</a><br>
<br>
<img src="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_d07e4da10f492575.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://musicfans.space/uploads/clipboard_image_d07e4da10f492575.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Make a big scene bigger. Create cinematic movie titles, intros, and transitions. Remove an object from a clip. Start a fire or make it rain. Animate a logo or character. With After Effects, the industry-standard motion graphics and visual effects software, you can take any idea and make it move.<br>
<br>
<br>
home page:<br>
<br>
<a href="https://goo.su/UTzqz" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://goo.su/UTzqz</a><br>
<br>
<a href="https://filecat.net/f/K1P6vN" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">FileCat - Adobe After Effects 2024 v24.0.1 Multilingual macOS.zip</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[piqeros]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>