<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【UPSCALED】Band Aid - Do They Know It's Christmas (1984 Version) [1080p AI Upscale | PCM 16-bit 44.1 kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/band-aid-do-they-know-its-christmas-1984-version-1080p-ai-upscale-pcm-16-bit-44-1-khz.233377/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/73/cc/UTDEc4F5_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/73/cc/UTDEc4F5_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic, Pop</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Synth-pop, Holiday</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">1984</span> <br>
Video Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">DVD, 480i</span><br>
Audio Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Qobuz</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Do They Know It's Christmas?</b>" is a charity song written in 1984 by Bob Geldof and Midge Ure to raise money for the 1983–1985 famine in Ethiopia. It was first recorded by Band Aid, a supergroup assembled by Geldof and Ure consisting of popular British and Irish musical acts. It was recorded in a single day at Sarm West Studios in Notting Hill, London, in November 1984. The studio time was donated by studio owner Trevor Horn.<br>
<br>
"Do They Know It's Christmas" was released in the United Kingdom on 3 December 1984. It entered the UK Singles Chart at number one and stayed there for five weeks, becoming Christmas number one. It sold a million copies in the first week, becoming the fastest-selling single in UK chart history; it held this title until 1997, when it was overtaken by Elton John's "Candle in the Wind 1997". UK sales passed three million on the last day of 1984.<br>
<br>
The song also reached number one in thirteen other countries. In the US, it fell short of the top ten in the <i>Billboard</i> Hot 100 due to a lack of airplay, but sold an estimated 2.5 million copies there by January 1985. By 1989, it had sold 11.7 million copies worldwide. Geldof hoped that it would raise £70,000 for Ethiopia; within a year, it raised £8 million. The success led to several other charity singles, such as "We Are the World" (1985) by USA for Africa, and spin-off charity events, such as Comic Relief and the 1985 Live Aid concert. The original version of "Do They Know It's Christmas?" has sold 3.8 million copies in the UK. In a UK poll in December 2012, it was voted sixth on the ITV television special <i>The Nation's Favourite Christmas Song</i>.<br>
<br>
"Do They Know It's Christmas?" was rerecorded and rereleased in 1989, 2004 and 2014. The 1989 and 2004 versions also raised funds for famine relief, while the 2014 version raised funds for the Ebola crisis in West Africa. All three reached number one in the UK, and the 1989 and 2004 versions became Christmas number ones. The 2004 version sold 1.8 million copies.<br>
<br>
Due to the time constraints of releasing the single as quickly as possible, the promotional video for the song simply featured footage from the recording session. David Bowie, who had been Geldof's original choice to sing the song's opening line but who had been unable to attend the recording, flew into England from Switzerland to record a short introduction for the video to be played on the BBC's flagship television music show <i>Top of the Pops</i> on 29 November 1984. However, Geldof was unhappy when he discovered that the show's regulations meant that the song and its video could not be played until it had actually charted. Undeterred, he contacted BBC1 controller Michael Grade directly and persuaded Grade to order that every program preceding that week's episode of <i>Top of the Pops</i> should start five minutes early to make space to broadcast the song's video (complete with Bowie's introduction) just before the show. That evening's <i>Top of the Pops</i> also saw several artists - Nik Kershaw and his band, members of Slade, Kool &amp; The Gang, Alvin Stardust, Jim Diamond and Black Lace - and presenter Peter Powell wearing "Feed the World" T-shirts to promote the single.<br>
<br>
The charity received a further boost during Band Aid's five week tenure at the top of the UK charts with Wham! at number two with their double A-side "Last Christmas"/"Everything She Wants". Wham! singer George Michael had appeared on the Band Aid single and he and fellow band member Andrew Ridgeley donated all the royalties from their single to the Band Aid Trust. As of 2021, "Last Christmas" has sold almost two million copies, and until it reached number one in January 2021 it held the record for the biggest-selling single never to reach number one in the UK.<br>
<br>
<b>Release Info</b><br>
The video track is upscaled from 480i to 1080p (H.264) with Topaz Video AI.<br>
The PCM track is lossless (Qobuz CD quality), synced with Adobe Audition.<br>
The timed lyrics are synced &amp; edited. Enable the subtitles to see the lyrics.<br>
<br>
<div class="ToggleTriggerAnchor bbCodeSpoilerContainer">
<button type="button" class="button bbCodeSpoilerButton ToggleTrigger Tooltip JsOnly" data-target="> .SpoilerTarget"><span>Spoiler: <span class="SpoilerTitle">Media Info</span></span></button>
<div class="SpoilerTarget bbCodeSpoilerText">
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeCode">
<div class="type">Code:</div>
<pre>General
Unique ID                      : 65441645470270909702056779676239493334 (0x313B9A3AF510C28A98E8F9FC110F78D6)
Complete name                  : Band Aid - Do They Know It's Christmas (1984 Version).mkv
Format                         : Matroska
Format version                 : Version 4 / Version 2
File size                      : 481 MiB
Duration                       : 3 min 51 s
Overall bit rate mode          : Variable
Overall bit rate               : 17.4 Mb/s
Frame rate                     : 25.060 FPS
Encoded date                   : 2023-11-28 21:32:00 UTC
Writing application            : mkvmerge v80.0 ('Roundabout') 64-bit
Writing library                : libebml v1.4.4 + libmatroska v1.7.1

Video
ID                             : 1
Format                         : AVC
Format/Info                    : Advanced Video Codec
Format profile                 : Main@L4
Format settings                : CABAC / 4 Ref Frames
Format settings, CABAC         : Yes
Format settings, Reference fra : 4 frames
Format settings, GOP           : N=1
Codec ID                       : V_MPEG4/ISO/AVC
Duration                       : 3 min 51 s
Bit rate mode                  : Variable
Bit rate                       : 16.0 Mb/s
Width                          : 1 302 pixels
Height                         : 1 080 pixels
Display aspect ratio           : 1.286
Frame rate mode                : Constant
Frame rate                     : 25.060 FPS
Original frame rate            : 25.000 FPS
Color space                    : YUV
Chroma subsampling             : 4:2:0
Bit depth                      : 8 bits
Scan type                      : Progressive
Bits/(Pixel*Frame)             : 0.454
Stream size                    : 442 MiB (92%)
Default                        : Yes
Forced                         : No
Color range                    : Limited
Color primaries                : BT.709
Transfer characteristics       : BT.709
Matrix coefficients            : BT.709

Audio
ID                             : 2
Format                         : PCM
Format settings                : Little / Signed
Codec ID                       : A_PCM/INT/LIT
Duration                       : 3 min 51 s
Bit rate mode                  : Constant
Bit rate                       : 1 411.2 kb/s
Channel(s)                     : 2 channels
Sampling rate                  : 44.1 kHz
Frame rate                     : 25.000 FPS (1764 SPF)
Bit depth                      : 16 bits
Stream size                    : 39.0 MiB (8%)
Language                       : English
Default                        : Yes
Forced                         : No

Text
ID                             : 3
Format                         : UTF-8
Codec ID                       : S_TEXT/UTF8
Codec ID/Info                  : UTF-8 Plain Text
Duration                       : 3 min 32 s
Bit rate                       : 45 b/s
Frame rate                     : 0.169 FPS
Count of elements              : 36
Stream size                    : 1.19 KiB (0%)
Title                          : Lyrics
Language                       : English
Default                        : No
Forced                         : No
</pre>
</div></div>
</div><br>
<b>Note to the peeps @ RuTracker: Give credit if you post the work of someone else!</b><br>
- Hurby4 aka ADHDerby<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>