<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】M4A - Ferry Corsten - Blueprint [E-AC3 | 5.1 | 16-bit/48 kHz | 1024 kb/s]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/ferry-corsten-blueprint-e-ac3-5-1-16-bit-48-khz-1024-kb-s.230376/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/2e/04/wktLuyXA_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/2e/04/wktLuyXA_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
Genre: <span style="color: #0059b3">Electronic, Stage &amp; Screen</span> <br>
Style: <span style="color: #0059b3">Trance, IDM, Ambient</span> <br>
Year: <span style="color: #0059b3">2017</span> <br>
Source: <span style="color: #0059b3">Blu-ray, DTS-HD MA 5.1</span></b><br>
<br>
"<b>Blueprint</b>" is the sixth studio album by Dutch trance artist Ferry Corsten, released on 26 May 2017 though Flashover Recordings. It is a science fiction-influenced trance album with tracks containing a storyline narrated by American actor Campbell Scott. The plot narrative, which is unfolded at the beginning of each song, depicts humans on Earth who begin to hear an endlessly repeating sound emitted from space and the creation of an android by a man who had deciphered the sound's hidden message.<br>
<br>
The album features a single from Corsten's side project "Gouryella" titled "Venera (Vee's Theme)", which was the first single released to promote the album. Along with "Venera (Vee's Theme)", four other singles were released with the album, "Reanimate", "Trust", "Waiting", and "Wherever You Are". <i>Blueprint</i> received positive reception from music critics, who praised the album's overall sound design and emotional listening experience evoked by each track.<br>
<br>
Unlike Ferry Corsten's earlier albums, <i>Blueprint</i> is a concept album whose concept is based on a science fiction-themed love story. According to Ferry, the initial inspiration for creating a narrative-focused album came from his father reminding him of <i>Jeff Wayne's Musical Version of The War of the Worlds</i>, an album that they used to listen together. Like the main concept of <i>Blueprint</i>, it is a progressive rock and symphonic rock album which contains narratives from Welsh actor Richard Burton. "As a kid, I grew up looking at the vinyls with all the artwork and paintings of these aliens and stuff. I was fascinated by it!" When Ferry's father reminded him of the old album, a lightbulb went off: "You just said the magic words, I told him. You just gave me an idea," recounted Ferry.<br>
<br>
Being a science fiction fan since his younger days, Ferry decided to base the theme of <i>Blueprint</i> on that very concept. "Ever since I was a little kid, I’ve been a big sci-fi fan. The interest in the unknown and what lies beyond that always grabbed me. For this project I had a chance to work with both my favourite interests, sci-fi and music," said Ferry. The storyline was written by Hollywood screenwriter David Harrington Miller, who was introduced to Ferry by his manager. "We hit it off very well and working together was easy and fun. The flow was fantastic," said Ferry. <i>Blueprint</i> contains illustrations from Canadian visual artist Oska.<br>
<br>
<b>Tracklist</b><br>
01. Reception<br>
02. Blueprint<br>
03. Your Face (feat. Eric Lumiere)<br>
04. Venera (Vee's Theme)<br>
05. Something To Believe In (feat. Eric Lumiere)<br>
06. Waiting (feat. Niels Geusebroek)<br>
07. Here We Are (feat. Haliene)<br>
08. Edge Of The Sky (feat. Haliene)<br>
09. A World Beyond<br>
10. Trust<br>
11. Lonely Inside<br>
12. Piece Of You (feat. Haliene)<br>
13. Wherever You Are (feat. Haliene)<br>
14. Drum's A Weapon<br>
15. Reanimate<br>
16. Another Sunrise (feat. Eric Lumiere &amp; Haliene)<br>
17. Eternity<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>