<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossy)】Dolby Atmos - Stray Kids – ROCK-STAR [WEB MP4 E-AC-3 JOC 768 kBit/s, 48.0 kHz + Apple Music Spatial Audio with Dolby Atmos 5.1 Surround Sound]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/stray-kids-%E2%80%93-rock-star-web-mp4-e-ac-3-joc-768-kbit-s-48-0-khz-apple-music-spatial-audio-with-dolby-atmos-5-1-surround-sound.232241/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<b><img src="https://i.imgur.com/euimDST.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/euimDST.jpg" style=""></b><br>
<span style="font-family: 'Book Antiqua'"><span style="font-size: 15px"><b><b><b><span style="color: #0059b3">Description</span></b></b></b><br>
<br>
Five months after the record-breaking <i>5-STAR</i>, K-pop superstars Stray Kids return with <i>ROCK-STAR</i>, a characteristically energetic EP for JYP Entertainment’s eight-member group. <i>ROCK-STAR</i> features eight tracks, including “Social Path,” a Korean interpretation of the group’s previous collab with Japanese singer LiSA, and two versions of the thumping, punny lead single “LALALALA.” All of the songs on <i>ROCK-STAR</i> were written by at least one member of 3RACHA, Stray Kids’ hip-hop sub-unit comprising group members Bang Chan, Changbin, and HAN. Here the members talk about each of <i>ROCK-STAR’</i>s tracks.<br>
<br>
<b>“MEGAVERSE”</b><br>
Bang Chan: “‘MEGAVERSE’ is a song that represents the vast spectrum of Stray Kids’ music. Having touched the universes of different kinds of music, Stray Kids now welcome listeners to…the SKZ MEGAVERSE. Enjoy!”<br>
<br>
<b>“LALALALA”</b><br>
Seungmin: “This one’s all about one core message, which is: ‘Our rock will go on, no matter how tough things might get.’ It’s the title track from our new album [in Korean, titled ‘락 (樂),’ with 락 meaning ‘rock’ and 樂 meaning ‘joy’ but pronounced the same] with a huge, rock-star-worthy stage performance to go along with it. Be sure to check out our performance as well as the music.”<br>
<br>
<b>“BLIND SPOT”</b><br>
HAN: “This song is about how all the scars we get while striving, unseen, to reach our dreams will end up becoming wonderful trophies. It’s a message of hope and courage. I hope it will both comfort and pump up whoever listens to it.”<br>
<br>
<b>“COMFLEX”</b><br>
Felix: “It’s about how you can flip those things you don’t like about yourself, turning them instead into something you can flex about. So the title’s a portmanteau of ‘COMPLEX’ and ‘FLEX.’ This track really showcases our carefree, cheery side.”<br>
<br>
<b>“Cover Me”</b><br>
Hyunjin: “The message in this one is: ‘That bright moonlight is making the night longer. So stay by my side and cover me from it.’ I like how the track builds up emotionally, with intensifying vocals toward the end. I hope this warm and passionate song will bring comfort to listeners.”<br>
<br>
<b>“Leave”</b><br>
Changbin: “This is a heartbreaking song about lovers saying goodbye. Driven by a forlorn-feeling guitar riff motif, the song really captures the mood of autumn.”<br>
<br>
<b>“Social Path” (feat. LiSA) [Korean Ver.]</b><br>
Lee Know: “This is a song that conveys hopefulness, and it’s about giving all of your youth, working hard to achieve your dreams. It brings together an intense rock sound with powerful vocals. I hope it will inspire listeners with the courage to forge their own paths.”<br>
<br>
<b>“LALALALA (Rock Ver.)”</b><br>
I.N: “This is the rock version of our title track, ‘락 (樂)’ [titled ‘LALALALA’ in English], bringing it closer to the title. If rock’s what you're into, this is the version for you. We upped the energy here, and the track’s buzzing with a thrilling synergy.”<br>
_______________________________________________________________________________________________<br>
<b><img src="https://i.imgur.com/DoOSsgE.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/DoOSsgE.png" style=""></b><br>
<b>Artist</b>: Stray Kids (스트레이 키즈)<br>
<b>Album</b>: 樂-STAR<br>
<b>Release</b>: 2023/11/10<br>
<b>Type</b>: Mini-Album<br>
<b>Format</b>: Enhanced AC-3 with Joint Object Coding<br>
<b>Quality</b>: High Quality, Lossy Audio<br>
<b>Sample Rate</b>: 768 kBit/s, 48.000 kHz - 5.1 Surround Sound<br>
<b>Encoding</b>: mp42 (ISO 14496-1 v.2), Constant Bit Rate<br>
<b>Source</b>: Ripped from <span style="color: #0059b3">Apple Music</span><br>
<br>
<b>TRACK LIST</b><br>
1. MEGAVERSE<br>
2. 락 (樂)<br>
3. 사각지대<br>
4. COMFLEX<br>
5. 가려줘<br>
6. Leave<br>
7. Social Path (feat. LiSA) (Korean Ver.)<br>
8. 락 (樂) (Rock Ver.)<br>
<br>
<b>MORE INFORMATION</b><br>
1 Disc - 8 Tracks.<br>
Artwork - JPEG 4000x4000.<br>
MediaInfo - <a href="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1oO8qAmwqiDz5f5zGKez_ZZUajVMAqJI-/view" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">Preview</a>.<br>
<br>
<b>DOWNLOAD</b> </span><span style="font-size: 12px">*Includes LRC files and Animated Artwork*</span><br>
<span style="font-size: 15px">
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div></span></span>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[samymskzs]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>