<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>sharemania</title>
 <link>http://www.sharemania.us/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - Sarah Harding - Real Wild Child]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/sarah-harding-real-wild-child.283172/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					Anyone have Sarah Harding - Real Wild Child in good quality?
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[rayofgod]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Cinema Center】the toxic avenger 2023 movie download]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/the-toxic-avenger-2023-movie-download.283171/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
				<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
					
					The Toxic Avenger Unrated is a 2023 American superhero black comedy splatter film written and directed by Macon Blair. It is the fifth installment, a reboot of The Toxic Avenger film series, and a remake of the 1984 film. The film stars Peter Dinklage as the title character, alongside Jacob Tremblay, Taylour Paige, Julia Davis, Jonny Coyne, Elijah Wood, and Kevin Bacon.<br>
<br>
The Toxic Avenger premiered as the opening film of Fantastic Fest on September 21, 2023, with a wider theatrical release followed by Cineverse and Iconic Events Releasing in the United States for August 29, 2025.<br>
<br>
The film has received positive reviews from critics.<br>
<br>
<a href="https://blessinspire.com/the-toxic-avenger-film/" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><b> AUDIO AVAILABLE HERE </b></a><br>
<br>
Plot/Description: A horrible toxic accident transforms downtrodden janitor, Winston Gooze into a new evolution of hero: The Toxic Avenger.<br>
<br>
Set in a fantasy world, the film follows janitor Winston Gooze, who, after a freak accident, transforms into a mutant vigilante known as Toxie. Armed with his mop, the unlikely hero battles freaks, gangsters and corrupt CEOs while trying to save his relationship with his son<br>
<br>
On the review aggregator website Rotten Tomatoes, 83% of 106 critics' reviews are positive. The website's consensus reads: "Like the original, The Toxic Avenger isn't for everyone – but viewers seeking an extremely gory, extremely silly good time won't be disappointed."[38] Metacritic, which uses a weighted average, assigned the film a score of 67 out of 100, based on 20 critics, indicating "generally favorable" reviews<br>
<br>
Marina<br>
<br>
<br>
This movie was an absolute blast from start to finish! The Toxic Avenger is everything you’d want from a modern take on a cult classic: funny, ridiculously over-the-top, and full of gloriously gory mayhem.<br>
<br>
<br>
The tone strikes a perfect balance between absurd comedy and full-throttle action-horror.<br>
<br>
<br>
was laughing out loud at some of the one-liners and wild situations, and the violence is so cartoonishly extreme that it never feels mean-spirited—just hilariously insane.<br>
<br>
<br>
The effects deserve a special shout-out. The practical gore is top-tier—oozing, exploding, splattering in all the best ways—and the CG blends in surprisingly well, giving it that polished-yet-playfully-gross aesthetic.<br>
<br>
<br>
You can tell the filmmakers were having a ton of fun with it, and that energy carries through in every scene.<br>
<br>
<br>
Whether you’re a longtime fan of Troma’s original or just in the mood for something outrageous, Toxic Avenger totally delivers. It’s got heart, guts (literally), and a sense of humor sharper than a mop-wielding mutant vigilante. Highly recommended for fans of campy horror, inventive gore, and movies that know exactly what they are—and lean all the way in.
					<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
				</blockquote>
			</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[lareve]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>