<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ VID] - AURORA Lollapalooza 2023 Chile 1080i/25 or 4K or FEED]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/aurora-lollapalooza-2023-chile-1080i-25-or-4k-or-feed.226887/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Has anyone found the recording created March 18, 2023 in Santiago, Chile of AURORA's Lollapalooza 2023 performance? The sound, late sun lighting, videography, and performances by all were extraordinary.<br>
<br>
It was a Youtube livestream, however the conversion of the live video to the stream was botched. I have the original Youtube livestream capture and it appears that the native video streamed to Youtube was 1080i/25 at a reasonable bitrate. However, Youtube does not take interlaced video.<br>
<br>
It should have been deinterlaced (QTGMC or Pro equivalent) to 1080p/25 or 1080p/50 before being compressed to progressive. It was not. They fed an interlaced 1080i/25 to Youtube's VP9 compressor that was set to progressive at 1080p/30... needless to say, it looks like crap. Interlacing is baked into the progressive frames.<br>
<br>
There is noticeable judder from the framerate mismatch. Looking at the stream with Videoredo clearly shows the nature of the damage- blobby blurred interlaced patterns appear in areas of motion. I don't know of any video processing that could fix this (not even Santiag for Avisynth). Topaz claims a new Dione AI model has a mode called Interlaced Progressive specifically made to fix videos suffering this damage. From what I've read, it doesn't work well (yet).<br>
<br>
Additionally, there are multiple gaps in the audio and/or video, as if it was live streamed from the venue without adequate buffering. All posted captures suffer from the exact same gaps (no need to post or link them).<br>
<br>
I'm hoping AURORA's label has realized just how great this recording turned out and has obtained a perfect high quality copy from the on-site Production team. I'm hoping they are streaming it somewhere for free or as Video-On-Demand (VOD). Please post the link if you find one. If you are skilled at stream capture, please post the capture.
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[xenon59247]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【HD Live Performances】HDTV - Celine Dion - My Heart Will Go On (2017 Billboard Music Awards) [1080i, 29.4 Mbps]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/celine-dion-my-heart-will-go-on-2017-billboard-music-awards-1080i-29-4-mbps.226886/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
This is a reupload (Original: <a href="https://sharemania.us/threads/c%C3%A9line-dion-my-heart-will-go-on-live-billboard-music-awards-2017.193132/" class="internalLink">https://sharemania.us/threads/célin...o-on-live-billboard-music-awards-2017.193132/</a>)<br>
<br>
Format : MPEG-TS<br>
File size : 1.08 GiB<br>
Duration : 5 min 14 s<br>
Overall bit rate mode : Variable<br>
Overall bit rate : 29.4 Mb/s<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/RiyeYVP.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/RiyeYVP.png" style=""> <br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[dxd1412]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>