<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Requests】[REQ AUD] - Suzanna Dee – Hero (1997) CDS]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/suzanna-dee-%E2%80%93-hero-1997-cds.233239/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Would anyone be able to help with this cd single, please?<br>
<br>
<a href="https://www.discogs.com/release/903513-Suzanna-Dee-Hero" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://www.discogs.com/release/903513-Suzanna-Dee-Hero</a><br>
<br>
Many thanks in advance!
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[Bouncy73]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Cinema Center】SERIES - The Rookie 2018 S01-S04 [AMZN 1080p HEVC DD+]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/the-rookie-2018-s01-s04-amzn-1080p-hevc-dd.233237/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/original/6EwgFPJRhmv20UyJg4GAPgBBuOV.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://www.themoviedb.org/t/p/original/6EwgFPJRhmv20UyJg4GAPgBBuOV.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
<b>Ripped by me from Paramount+ Channel in Amazon Prime Video.</b><br>
<br>
<b>VIDEO:</b> 1080p H265 Full HD<br>
<br>
<b>AUDIO:</b> English and Latin american <b>(EAC3 224kbps)</b><br>
<br>
<b>SUBTITLES:</b> Latin american<br>
<br>
<b>HOST:</b> Telegram<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[alrl]]></author>
                </item>

                
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Helpdesk】DIY-Acapella Tutorial]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/diy-acapella-tutorial.233238/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Before we had all those different fancy AI filters, the best way to make an acapella was with the DIYAcapella method. For that, you needed the original vocal version of a song &amp; its official instrumental. For this one we're gonna use cd rips of both from a promo single.<br>
<br>
Download link, decode at <a href="https://www.base64decode.org/" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://www.base64decode.org/</a><br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must either reply or click 'Like' to see the hidden information contained here.</blockquote>
</div>It includes the vocal version, the instrumental, the below pics AND the raw result that I created. You can practice in your own time, and use my mixdown for comparison purposes to see if you've done the best possible job. These rips that I've tested myself create an almost-studio acapella.<br>
<br>
You will need an audio editing program that has a multitrack view. This tutorial is for Adobe Audition, but the steps you need to take are the same, regardless of the program you use.<br>
<br>
⚡️First you need to make sure that the Volume Levels of both tracks are the same or as close as possible. Think of it as needing to include equal amounts of Yellow and Red dye to achieve a perfect Orange. Too much on either side and there will be problems.<br>
<br>
You can do this by visually comparing the waveforms of both tracks. Once you're satisfied, Invert one of the tracks (doesn't matter which). Invert (often referred to as "Phase") is a setting that flips the audio samples upside down. It doesn't produce any effect you can actually hear, but it makes all the difference in the world when mixing with another track, like here.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/u5CdCkF.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/u5CdCkF.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Once that is done, import both tracks into the Multitrack view.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/RRdgRj4.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/RRdgRj4.png" style=""><br>
<br>
⚡️Now you have to perfectly allign the two tracks, one above the other. The beefier waverform is the vocal version. On first look, they seem alligned enough<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/zqXdbcw.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/zqXdbcw.png" style=""><br>
<br>
but when you zoom in, you can see that they're not.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/kJmbxUT.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/kJmbxUT.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Drag one of the tracks so that it matches perfectly with the other. The Inverted track is generally a perfect mirror image of the other one, so you simply have to drag it close enough so that they look like a reflection.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/6cQHgqg.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/6cQHgqg.png" style=""><br>
<br>
The trick is to zoom in as close as possible so that you can see the tiniest nodes in the waveform. This might sound a bit excessive, but the tiniest different in allignment will result in background music bleed. The bigger the difference in allignment, the louder the background bleed will be.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/zZUbRKN.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/zZUbRKN.png" style=""><br>
<br>
The most prominent fluctuations (dips and curves) will be at spots where the drums are, so that's a good place to focus. You simply have to look at the zoomed-in waveform to spot identical mirror patterns in what you're looking at.<br>
<br>
You can play it back to hear the real-time result and see how much progress you've made.<br>
<br>
If it doesn't sound right to you, try to re-allign the tracks by moving it back or forth, one tiny step at a time, and just listen to how clear the vocals sound compared to its previous position.<br>
<br>
Also experiment with adjusting the volume level of ONE of the tracks, usually by 0.5 decibels each time, and see if that makes any difference.<br>
<br>
⚡️Once you're satisfied that it's the best it's ever going to get, time to export your acapella!<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/Ex8yRcz.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/Ex8yRcz.png" style=""><br>
<br>
In Adobe Audition, you simply click on a blank spot on the Multitrack View, and select Mixdown to New File - Master Output in Session (session is what you're working on right now).<br>
<br>
It will export a temporary WAV file titled "Mixdown", and it's up to you to save it to your preferred location. This is what mine looks like<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/v0uN1SN.png" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/v0uN1SN.png" style=""><br>
<br>
Looking at the Mixdown's waveform, you can see that the background music is 99.9% gone. And when you playback the Mixdown, you'd think you're listening to a studio acapella.<br>
<br>
Factors that affect the quality of the result<br>
<br>
Quality of the vocal version and/or instrumental. Lower-quality rips are more compressed and will usually cause louder background bleed. If you have lossless rips, USE them.<br>
<br>
Uneven volume levels. I've already explained this, so always make sure they're as even as possible. But, always LOWER the volume of the louder track. Don't increase the volume of the quieter one, because this produces excess artefacting noise.<br>
<br>
Mastering of the vocal version of the instrumental. Sometimes, the rips of the vocal version &amp; instrumental are not created in the same mixdown-session. So while the instrumental might sound the same to your ear, any slight differences in mixing will create problems.<br>
<br>
It might only partially cancel out the backing music, or it might not cancel it out at all. If that's the case, there's very little or nothing you can do about it. If the backing music is only partially cancelled out and a bit of noise remains, you can try to remove it with an audio-cleaning program.<br>
<br>
I use RipX DeepAudio for that, but it is expensive. It is infuriating when this happens, but sometimes it cannot be avoided.<br>
<br>
The worst-case scenario I've personally seen is when the 2 tracks only allign for 1-2 seconds, and then they go out of allignment, and the noise-bleeding begins. Which forced me to chop up one of the songs to 1-2 second pieces, and allign them one by one like that. It is time-consuming and incredibly frustrating. But if you really want that acapella, you'll do it. Just like I did.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://i.imgur.com/8DIcUEk.gif" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://i.imgur.com/8DIcUEk.gif" style="">
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[KingOfHell1661]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>