<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Live Audios (lossless)】WAV - Taylor Swift — Live at The Grand Ole Opry [2007-10-12]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/taylor-swift-%E2%80%94-live-at-the-grand-ole-opry-2007-10-12.223070/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
I recently bought a CD that included official recordings from The Grand Ole Opry. Featured on the CD are two songs by Taylor Swift: "Our Song" and "Picture To Burn," originally performed live on October 12, 2007. I've taken these tracks and compiled a Taylor Swift-specific EP, equipped with tailored tags and cover art. The EP is available in both WAV and ALAC formats.<br>
<br>
<div style="text-align: center"><a href="https://drive.proton.me/urls/AV1XDEWZ2W#9OHIhMfgyl5Q" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow"><b>LINK [ProtonDrive]</b></a><br>
​</div>Although Swift's initial performance occurred in October 2007, the audio I used was sourced from a re-broadcast in February 2008, which is part of the compilation of Opry highlights on the CD I purchased.<br>
<br>
As an integral piece of American cultural history, The Grand Ole Opry has been hosting live radio shows since 1925. Situated in Nashville, Tennessee, this venue is often viewed as the heart of American country music, featuring notable stars of the genre and providing a stage for budding talent. Its longevity and enduring influence make it one of the longest-running radio broadcasts in history, shaping the trajectory and development of country music over the decades.
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[amsterdammer83]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>