<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Music Videos】PACK - ★NSYNC - Thinking of You (JC Version) [4K Upscaled]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/%E2%98%85nsync-thinking-of-you-jc-version-4k-upscaled.242260/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
Hi thanks for letting me joined this incredible site. I can pretty much find hd music video that i wanted.<br>
Here, I wanna share this underrated hidden gem MV that need to be preserved online. SME Just blocked any version of this MV especially JC version to that surfaced on YouTube.<br>
I'm enraged because this JC version is the best. Great singing of JC, great instrumental. Great acting.<br>
But the hd version of it were nowhere to found. There's only one left in YouTube that is reupload and very blurry and even have 60 fps ai hack that u really hate when I found out it's degrading the quality and doesn't aligned with the director's intended.<br>
<br>
Finally I found the original source of that video in full HD , I got it somewhere somehow.<br>
I had to cropped the top part because it has watermark. But it's still better compared to the one in YouTube. It's in original 24 fps. I have changed the colors and made some enhancements including better audio and ai upscaled to 4K format using this incredible site called: Tensorpix.ai. (go check it out it's worth it!)<br>
<br>
I managed to made the best version of this MV since the official account refuse to upload it. (They still hiding JC's talent, shame on them)<br>
Ok Enjoy.<br>
<br>
<img src="https://mega.nz/file/PmIFRB6a#oLJlVIrDI4hYPtEeyUVbjqAgmpve1CfFrj1oEG6e0W8" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://mega.nz/file/PmIFRB6a#oLJlVIrDI4hYPtEeyUVbjqAgmpve1CfFrj1oEG6e0W8" style=""><br>
<a href="https://mega.nz/file/Ci5WjSbY#6QEyzYoFGGWUveJv0nb7kut5UPj5mHCA0LhFISOhfJ8" target="_blank" class="externalLink" rel="nofollow">https://mega.nz/file/Ci5WjSbY#6QEyzYoFGGWUveJv0nb7kut5UPj5mHCA0LhFISOhfJ8</a>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[David Ariyan]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>