<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="rss1.xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
<channel>
 <title>Getty</title>
 <link>http://www.gettyimg.com/</link>
 <atom:link href="http://www.gettyimg.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />

 
                <item>
                <title><![CDATA[【Albums (lossless)】FLAC - Travis Scott - Utopia [Qobuz Hi-Res 24-bit 88.2 kHz]]]></title>
                <link><![CDATA[https://sharemania.us/threads/travis-scott-utopia-qobuz-hi-res-24-bit-88-2-khz.225320/]]></link>
                <description><![CDATA[<article>
<blockquote class="messageText SelectQuoteContainer ugc baseHtml">
<img src="https://images2.imgbox.com/57/1c/xMveNLqJ_o.jpg" class="bbCodeImage LbImage" alt="[​IMG]" data-url="https://images2.imgbox.com/57/1c/xMveNLqJ_o.jpg" style=""> <br>
<br>
“<b>Utopia</b>” is the fourth studio album by American rapper Travis Scott. It is released through Cactus Jack Records and Epic Records on July 28, 2023. The title of the album was revealed in early July 2020 when Scott uploaded an Instagram post with the caption "Utopia". He further teased the "Utopia" title in a thank you letter on the second anniversary of <i>Astroworld</i> In October, Scott continued to tease the album in a series of tweets.<br>
<br>
Recording for the album began in 2019 with Scott posting updates throughout recording sessions on social media.<br>
The album has been delayed following the horrific incident that occurred at Travis' Astroworld Festival. On November 5, 2021, a fatal crowd crush occurred during the first night of the festival that was held at NRG Park in Houston, Texas. Eight people died the night of, and two more died in the hospital over the following days.<br>
In May 2023, Scott reportedly played songs from the record for the Houston Astros, and revealed that the record was in its mastering stage.<br>
On July 23 during Rolling Loud Miami, Scott said that performance would be the end of the <i>Astroworld</i> era and that <i>Utopia</i> alongside it's film would be released on July 28, 2023.<br>
<br>
In August 2021, Scott signed a picture deal with A24 and teased his own film based on the album. In July 2023, after nearly 2 years of no updates, it was reported that the film was complete and directed by Harmony Korine and it was “action oriented” with Scott starring. It was also reportedly shot entirely in infrared. Scott has yet to sign off its release. The following day, Metrograph reported they were invited to a private screening. The same month on July 22, during his Rolling Loud set, he played a teaser for the film titled <i>Circus Maximus</i>. Scott also revealed that the film is scheduled to release simultaneously with <i>Utopia</i> on July 28 in theaters.<br>
<br>
<div class="bbCodeBlock bbCodeVfcHH HiddenContent">
<div class="attribution type">Hidden Content:</div>
<blockquote>You must reply before you can see the hidden data contained here.</blockquote>
</div>
<div class="messageTextEndMarker">&nbsp;</div>
</blockquote>
</article>]]></description>
                <author><![CDATA[ADHDerby]]></author>
                </item>

                </channel></rss>